<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="Eleanor Neale" date="20230310" date_ts="1678477500" views="1693899" title="The White House Farm Family Massacre" likes="45711" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="0" is_ac="false">In 1985 the UK had one of its most infamous 
True Crime cases ever, known as the White House  </p>
  <p time="7380" is_ac="false">Farm murders. Five members of the Bamber family 
were found dead all in one night but was it an  </p>
  <p time="14640" is_ac="false">open and shut murder suicide case or was it a 
complete massacre, with the killer running off  </p>
  <p time="21300" is_ac="false">into the night? This case is technically solved, 
we do technically have an answer but many people  </p>
  <p time="27420" is_ac="false">in this country believe that it was an incorrect 
verdict. A lot of people believe that this could  </p>
  <p time="34020" is_ac="false">be one of the worst miscarriages of justice 
that this country has ever had. So today we're  </p>
  <p time="40200" is_ac="false">going to be talking about the White House Farm 
murders.</p>
  <p time="45363" is_ac="false">Okay before we get into the video, I do  </p>
  <p time="47363" is_ac="false">just want to thank Ritual for sponsoring. Ritual 
are supplements and vitamins brand that I have  </p>
  <p time="52740" is_ac="false">completely fallen in love with recently, for a 
number of different reasons. I've been taking  </p>
  <p time="56640" is_ac="false">the essential for women multivitamin and the 
symbiotic plus supplement which is good for your  </p>
  <p time="62160" is_ac="false">gut health and that is something I've wanted to 
look into for quite a while, now I've been seeing  </p>
  <p time="66600" is_ac="false">it all over Tik Tok about you gut health. So 
yeah I've been taking those two and for years  </p>
  <p time="71220" is_ac="false">now, I have been quite a deficient girlie. I have 
anemia, I'm deficient in vitamin D and I think  </p>
  <p time="76980" is_ac="false">something else, so alongside my doctor prescribed 
like supplements and medications I'm always taking  </p>
  <p time="83280" is_ac="false">a multivitamin. I have done for years, I always 
make sure that I'm getting everything I need  </p>
  <p time="87600" is_ac="false">to be getting. And even if you're not a deficient 
girlie like me, taking a multivitamin every day can  </p>
  <p time="93060" is_ac="false">help to bridge some of the natural gaps in your 
nutrition. So if you're not quite hitting your  </p>
  <p time="98220" is_ac="false">required intake of some vitamins some days, it's 
fine! You've got the support of your multivitamin.  </p>
  <p time="103260" is_ac="false">And these are really really good multivitamins, I've 
become obsessed with them and trust me, I've tried  </p>
  <p time="107820" is_ac="false">so many different types and I love Ritual for so 
many reasons. First of all they have a visible and  </p>
  <p time="114240" is_ac="false">traceable supply chain so you can see where they 
get their ingredients from, why each ingredient  </p>
  <p time="120540" is_ac="false">is in there, you know absolutely everything that 
you're putting into your body. They're incredibly  </p>
  <p time="124920" is_ac="false">well tested through a third party as well, they're 
also a vegan friendly, they're gluten-free, major  </p>
  <p time="130080" is_ac="false">allergen free and non-GMO. And they smell like 
mint which is just a happy little upside, every  </p>
  <p time="136680" is_ac="false">time I go to take my vitamins I'm like, oh nice 
fresh breath as well! The multivitamin actually  </p>
  <p time="141060" is_ac="false">has delay release technology which means it kind 
of waits to release those vitamins until it gets  </p>
  <p time="146700" is_ac="false">to you small intestine I believe, where it's best 
absorbed. So if you want to try out Ritual, they are  </p>
  <p time="152400" is_ac="false">very kindly offering you guys 20% off of your order 
when you go to ritual.com forward slash eneale20  </p>
  <p time="159060" is_ac="false">and use the code eneale20. The link is also down 
below in the description box of this video if you  </p>
  <p time="164280" is_ac="false">want to just go click it, thanks again to Ritual 
for sponsoring this video. Quickly before we get  </p>
  <p time="168660" is_ac="false">into the case, I do just want to give my usual 
disclaimer that I mean absolutely no disrespect  </p>
  <p time="173400" is_ac="false">to anyone that I talk about in this video. This 
video is for educational purposes and everything  </p>
  <p time="178260" is_ac="false">that I'm about to say is just information that I 
have found on the internet and I'm compiling into  </p>
  <p time="183420" is_ac="false">one video. A couple of content warnings before we 
get into this one as well, there's a lot of talk of  </p>
  <p time="188520" is_ac="false">mental illness, specifically schizophrenia so if 
anything relating to that or hospitalisation is  </p>
  <p time="194520" is_ac="false">triggering for you or suicide, talk of suicide, then 
please click out of this video now. I think that's  </p>
  <p time="200280" is_ac="false">all of our content warnings for this one. But yeah, 
hopefully I'll get to see you again at some other  </p>
  <p time="204540" is_ac="false">point with a different case but with all that 
being said, let's get into the case. So today's  </p>
  <p time="209340" is_ac="false">case takes place in Essex in South England, on the 
night of August 6 1985. Well it was more like the  </p>
  <p time="217020" is_ac="false">early hours of the next morning at like 3:30 a.m, 
the police receive a very frantic phone call from  </p>
  <p time="223920" is_ac="false">a man named Jeremy Bamber saying that he was 
worried for his father's safety. Jeremy said that  </p>
  <p time="229680" is_ac="false">he'd just been on the phone to his father who was 
very panicked saying that Jeremy's sister had gone  </p>
  <p time="235560" is_ac="false">crazy with a gun in the house. She was chasing 
everyone around with it and they were scared  </p>
  <p time="240300" is_ac="false">for their safety. Jeremy said he heard gunshots 
on the other end of the phone and then the line  </p>
  <p time="245820" is_ac="false">went dead. So at this point, he's thinking that 
his sister might have just murdered his father.  </p>
  <p time="252060" is_ac="false">So he asked police to meet him at the address, 
his family's home was named White House Farm  </p>
  <p time="258360" is_ac="false">and so he put the phone down and him and police 
made their way there. Police actually beat Jeremy  </p>
  <p time="263820" is_ac="false">to the scene so when they arrived, everything was 
still quiet. In fact it was silent, eerily silent  </p>
  <p time="270540" is_ac="false">at the Manor. The police circled the house you know, 
checking for any windows or doors or signs of forced </p>
  <p time="276780" is_ac="false">entry and there was nothing. In fact everything was 
locked, all the windows were locked, all the doors  </p>
  <p time="282420" is_ac="false">were locked, apart from there was this one window 
on the ground floor that was unlocked and that  </p>
  <p time="288900" is_ac="false">is how police managed to gain entry into White 
House Farm that night. And when police got inside  </p>
  <p time="294300" is_ac="false">that house, it was a total bloodbath. Not only had 
Jeremy's father been shot and killed but the whole  </p>
  <p time="303660" is_ac="false">family had. His father, 61 year old Neville Bamber 
was the first body to be found, he was the only one  </p>
  <p time="310740" is_ac="false">found on the ground floor. He had been beaten and 
shot eight times and six of those shots were in  </p>
  <p time="318540" is_ac="false">his face. He also had defense wounds like all over 
his arms, showing that he really put up a fight  </p>
  <p time="324900" is_ac="false">against his attacker, he was fighting for his life. 
Then as police made their way upstairs, they found  </p>
  <p time="330600" is_ac="false">their second body, Jeremy's mother also a 61 year 
old, June Bamber. She was laying dead in the hallway,  </p>
  <p time="337560" is_ac="false">I believe she was only shot once at point blank 
range, so very close but yeah I think she was  </p>
  <p time="344460" is_ac="false">only shot the once. And then in one of the bedrooms, 
police found two young boys laying in their  </p>
  <p time="351360" is_ac="false">bed. They'd also been shot and killed. These were 
Jeremy's six-year-old nephews, Daniel and Nicholas  </p>
  <p time="358140" is_ac="false">Caffell, his sister's two sons. His sister and her 
children were currently staying with their mum and  </p>
  <p time="364500" is_ac="false">dad at White House Farm. Those two young boys had 
been shot eight times between them and it seemed  </p>
  <p time="370200" is_ac="false">that they had been shot as they were sleeping, 
they were still very much like cuddled up in bed  </p>
  <p time="375300" is_ac="false">when they were found. Then in the main bedroom of 
the house was Sheila Caffell, Jeremy's sister, the  </p>
  <p time="382500" is_ac="false">one that had supposedly gone mad and shot everyone. 
She was found also dead laying on the floor of the  </p>
  <p time="390000" is_ac="false">bedroom with a rifle still in her hands. It seemed 
that she had shot herself twice in the throat and  </p>
  <p time="398340" is_ac="false">she was clinging to a Bible with her other hand, 
so she had the gun and then a Bible next to her.  </p>
  <p time="403680" is_ac="false">What an absolutely harrowing scene for police to 
have just walked in on but it seems very obvious  </p>
  <p time="410100" is_ac="false">what had happened here, I mean Sheila was found 
with the gun still in her hands, they very quickly  </p>
  <p time="415200" is_ac="false">categorised this as a very tragic murder-suicide. 
Jeremy Bamber, the only surviving member of this  </p>
  <p time="423060" is_ac="false">close family, was supposedly in bits all night as 
the searches were going on inside the house, he  </p>
  <p time="429120" is_ac="false">was waiting outside just crying and being soothed 
by the officers. They were giving him whiskey and  </p>
  <p time="434700" is_ac="false">cups of tea to try and calm him but like, he had 
just lost everyone he loved all in one night, like  </p>
  <p time="442080" is_ac="false">his whole family had just been wiped out in the 
blink of an eye and now he had no one. Well no one  </p>
  <p time="448320" is_ac="false">of his close blood family left anyway. When the sun 
came up the following morning, police did another  </p>
  <p time="454260" is_ac="false">like sweep search of the house just to double 
check their theory was correct, that this was a  </p>
  <p time="459420" is_ac="false">murder-suicide and there was no like weird little 
pieces of evidence or clues in the house and they  </p>
  <p time="463980" is_ac="false">didn't find anything. And because it wasn't deemed 
a crime scene, the house was very quickly emptied,  </p>
  <p time="469500" is_ac="false">all of the bodies were taken to the morgue to be 
held until their funerals could be planned and the  </p>
  <p time="475320" is_ac="false">house was then just given back to Jeremy Bamber, 
the only surviving Bamber family member. Everyone  </p>
  <p time="481380" is_ac="false">in that village was so shocked and devastated 
to hear the news of this massacre because the  </p>
  <p time="487980" is_ac="false">Bamber family were like everyone's favourite family. 
They were very well respected, they'd been in that  </p>
  <p time="494580" is_ac="false">community for years and years and years, they 
were regular churchgoers, especially June Bamber  </p>
  <p time="500160" is_ac="false">was very involved in the religious community, the 
church in their area. She was just involved in the  </p>
  <p time="506400" is_ac="false">whole community, she was doing s**t for the town. 
Everyone loved her, everyone thought she was great  </p>
  <p time="510660" is_ac="false">and everyone, by extension, thought that her husband 
was great and that her kids were great. This was  </p>
  <p time="515640" is_ac="false">just a really loved family and no one ever saw 
this coming. Especially because of the way that  </p>
  <p time="523140" is_ac="false">it happened, it's just so tragic for the them all 
to have been killed by their own daughter or their  </p>
  <p time="528840" is_ac="false">own mother, it's- it's so upsetting for her too, 
that her mental illness drove her to this point.  </p>
  <p time="534840" is_ac="false">Everyone was just so devastated for the Bamber 
family. Jeremy said that his sister Sheila had  </p>
  <p time="540420" is_ac="false">had a very very tough life when it came to 
her mental illness anyway. She'd been in and  </p>
  <p time="545880" is_ac="false">out of mental institutions all her teen years and 
she'd never really experienced peace in her brain,  </p>
  <p time="553500" is_ac="false">you know? And on top of just being I think just 
generally quite mentally ill, she always had been  </p>
  <p time="558660" is_ac="false">since a child, Sheila then as she was growing 
up and becoming a woman, she also faced a lot  </p>
  <p time="564780" is_ac="false">of hardships. She was addicted to cocaine for a 
little while, although I do believe she managed to  </p>
  <p time="570540" is_ac="false">get off that. She had several miscarriages, she had 
a cheating husband and on top of that, she just had  </p>
  <p time="577320" is_ac="false">her generally bad mental illness that meant that 
she would have like meltdowns, every now and again.  </p>
  <p time="582540" is_ac="false">She would go into like kind of manic episodes and 
eventually when she was admitted to the hospital,</p>
  <p time="588780" is_ac="false">she was diagnosed with schizophrenia. The last 
time that she was admitted to the hospital was  </p>
  <p time="594300" is_ac="false">just five months before the shooting took place 
and when she was there that time, she was telling  </p>
  <p time="599460" is_ac="false">the hospital workers that she was communicating 
with God. And it's also no secret that Sheila had  </p>
  <p time="606480" is_ac="false">quite a troubled relationship with her mother June. 
So I mean there could be some slight motive there  </p>
  <p time="612360" is_ac="false">if she was already suicidal, maybe that was what 
brought the homicidal aspect into it. But yeah, ever  </p>
  <p time="619140" is_ac="false">since she was young Sheila and June just hadn't 
really gotten on and I believe it was when Sheila  </p>
  <p time="624480" is_ac="false">became like, teenage age and she's becoming a young 
woman. She starts seeing boys and doing things with  </p>
  <p time="633780" is_ac="false">boys and her very, very religious mother June, did 
not like that at all. One time June caught Sheila  </p>
  <p time="642480" is_ac="false">sunbathing naked with a boy. I'm sure they were just 
sunbathing but they were caught and June went  </p>
  <p time="649140" is_ac="false">ballistic, she was calling Sheila the devil's 
child and everything and supposedly from that  </p>
  <p time="655380" is_ac="false">point on, their relationship was never the same, 
June didn't really like Sheila. So the conclusion  </p>
  <p time="661980" is_ac="false">that police came to was, maybe that this was just 
a deadly combination of like, long-held resentment  </p>
  <p time="668640" is_ac="false">and hatred towards her mother plus a particularly 
severe schizophrenic episode that led Sheila Caffell </p>
  <p time="676620" is_ac="false">to want to murder her whole family and then kill 
herself afterwards. So over the next week or so,  </p>
  <p time="682680" is_ac="false">Jeremy Bamber and the rest of his like extended 
family, uncles, aunties, cousins, everyone, they were  </p>
  <p time="690120" is_ac="false">all meeting up at White House Farm to put together 
funeral plans which I was kind of thinking as I  </p>
  <p time="697080" is_ac="false">was like looking into this case, is that not a 
bit odd? I guess it is just kind of the easiest  </p>
  <p time="702660" is_ac="false">place for them all to meet up and I bet there's 
a lot parking and stuff so like, everyone can fit  </p>
  <p time="706920" is_ac="false">in this one place but imagine going back to the 
scene of the murder to plan everyone's funerals?  </p>
  <p time="713160" is_ac="false">There's just something very eerie about that. That 
being said, I know it was their house and it- the  </p>
  <p time="717960" is_ac="false">house had been in their family for generations, so 
I guess it's not like they're gonna like knock the  </p>
  <p time="723300" is_ac="false">house down or I don't know, anyway. And to be fair, 
the house had been semi-redone, it probably hadn't  </p>
  <p time="730560" is_ac="false">actually been redone at this point in time but 
they had ripped out like all the carpets, all the  </p>
  <p time="736320" is_ac="false">linens, all the curtains. Anything that had blood 
on it had been completely ripped out and burned, so  </p>
  <p time="743640" is_ac="false">that like they didn't have to obviously like look 
at that and live amongst that, that's awful. So the  </p>
  <p time="749700" is_ac="false">house is like clean, they didn't think there was 
any evidence of the murders or the suicide left  </p>
  <p time="755040" is_ac="false">behind. That was until Jeremy's cousin David went 
snooping around. He was rummaging around some boxes  </p>
  <p time="763800" is_ac="false">under the stairs when he came across a silencer, 
you know like what you put on the end of the gun  </p>
  <p time="769500" is_ac="false">to make the gunshots quieter. He came across this 
silencer and looked at it closely and he saw that  </p>
  <p time="774780" is_ac="false">it had a speck of blood on the end of it. So he 
secretly turned the silencer over to police and  </p>
  <p time="781440" is_ac="false">he said look, I found this in White House Farm in a 
box under the stairs, I don't know why it's there, I  </p>
  <p time="786660" is_ac="false">don't know whose blood that is. So police take it 
and they test it. Now bear in mind this case is in  </p>
  <p time="792840" is_ac="false">the mid-1980s, so lab technology it was not like it 
is today. It's not like they could run this blood  </p>
  <p time="799800" is_ac="false">on the system and find an exact match but back 
then, they would have been able to tell what blood  </p>
  <p time="805860" is_ac="false">group this sample is you know, like A, B, O... A 
negative? I don't know, what are the blood types? </p>
  <p time="814032" is_ac="false">Um but anyway, they would be able to tell what 
blood group it is. They managed to figure out  </p>
  <p time="818475" is_ac="false">from these tests that the blood on the silencer 
was type A, which was very interesting to learn  </p>
  <p time="824460" is_ac="false">because there was actually only one dead body in 
that house that night with type A blood. It was  </p>
  <p time="831720" is_ac="false">Sheila. Now this turned the whole investigation 
on its head because how the hell could Sheila's  </p>
  <p time="838800" is_ac="false">blood have been on anything downstairs, if she 
was the last one to die. She had shot herself in  </p>
  <p time="846540" is_ac="false">the bedroom and died there, how could the silencer 
off the end of the gun- how could that found its  </p>
  <p time="852960" is_ac="false">way downstairs? So was this evidence that this 
wasn't actually a murder-suicide? Maybe Sheila  </p>
  <p time="860640" is_ac="false">hadn't actually killed herself, maybe she'd been 
framed. Someone had shot her with the silencer on  </p>
  <p time="867180" is_ac="false">and then taking the silencer off before laying 
the gun on her, making it look like she'd shot  </p>
  <p time="872820" is_ac="false">herself and then they went and hid this silencer 
under the stairs. That seems like it could be the  </p>
  <p time="879300" is_ac="false">only explanation. So now that they were faced with 
this like spanner in the works, police decided to  </p>
  <p time="885000" is_ac="false">pull out all of the evidence that they had and 
look back over it all but there wasn't very much  </p>
  <p time="890640" is_ac="false">evidence at all because of course, they thought 
this was a murder suicide, they thought it was an  </p>
  <p time="894960" is_ac="false">open and shut case, they didn't suspect foul play 
so they hadn't really collected evidence from  </p>
  <p time="901020" is_ac="false">the crime scene because it wasn't really a crime 
scene. Well it was, there were four murders there  </p>
  <p time="905700" is_ac="false">but of course, they couldn't bring the suspect 
to justice so they didn't really bother taking  </p>
  <p time="911700" is_ac="false">evidence. But they did take crime scene photos at 
the time and that was one of the main things that  </p>
  <p time="917040" is_ac="false">they were looking back through and they noticed 
something very interesting about the pictures of  </p>
  <p time="922440" is_ac="false">Sheila's body. Now if you remember, I said it was a 
complete bloodbath in that house because it truly  </p>
  <p time="927840" is_ac="false">was, there was blood all over the floors, all over 
like- they had to burn everything. But weirdly  </p>
  <p time="933660" is_ac="false">enough in the crime scene photos of Sheila's 
body, the bottoms of her feet were completely  </p>
  <p time="940140" is_ac="false">clean. No blood. She hadn't been walking around in 
the house, she hadn't been standing in the blood.  </p>
  <p time="945960" is_ac="false">So again, more evidence that she couldn't have been 
the the crazy one on a rampage, running around  </p>
  <p time="952080" is_ac="false">the house shooting everyone because there would be 
evidence of that on her but there wasn't. It seems  </p>
  <p time="957480" is_ac="false">that she was shot in place and fell and died there, 
she didn't move anywhere. Another conclusion that  </p>
  <p time="965520" is_ac="false">police had come to, was that it would actually 
be physically impossible for Sheila to have shot  </p>
  <p time="971580" is_ac="false">herself with that rifle with the silencer on 
because she was quite a small, petite woman and  </p>
  <p time="978840" is_ac="false">just physically her arms, her little fingers will 
not have been able to reach the trigger of this  </p>
  <p time="985620" is_ac="false">really long rifle if the silencer was on there 
and it obviously was because her blood splashed  </p>
  <p time="991260" is_ac="false">back onto it. But again, the gun wasn't found with 
the silencer on it when her body was found. So the  </p>
  <p time="997920" is_ac="false">theory is that maybe someone killed her with the 
silencer on and then went to go and plant the gun  </p>
  <p time="1004280" is_ac="false">on her and realised oh wait s**t, this makes it 
too long, she obviously couldn't have held it like  </p>
  <p time="1009260" is_ac="false">this and then that's why they took the silencer 
off and hid it so that the gun was then physically  </p>
  <p time="1015800" is_ac="false">shorter, so that it would look like Sheila could 
have killed herself with it. Do you get where  </p>
  <p time="1020420" is_ac="false">I'm coming from? But also actually now we bring up 
Sheila's injuries, she had two bullet wounds to her  </p>
  <p time="1027500" is_ac="false">neck, right? And if she was to have killed herself, 
how often do you hear of someone managing to shoot  </p>
  <p time="1034340" is_ac="false">themselves twice, when they're committing suicide? I 
mean it is physically possible sometimes but more  </p>
  <p time="1042080" is_ac="false">often than not, if someone is shooting themselves 
in the neck/throat kind of area, it's only going to  </p>
  <p time="1048560" is_ac="false">take one gunshot. Police think it's very unlikely 
that she shot herself once in the neck and also  </p>
  <p time="1055100" is_ac="false">bear in mind, this is still a very long gun and 
even though she can actually hold it without the  </p>
  <p time="1061160" is_ac="false">silencer on, it would take a lot of like lining up. 
So supposedly she shot herself once, the gun would  </p>
  <p time="1067160" is_ac="false">have like moved out of place so then she, bleeding 
out by the way, managed to then line the gun up  </p>
  <p time="1073340" is_ac="false">again and shoot a second time. Police just don't 
really believe that. So all of this new evidence  </p>
  <p time="1078260" is_ac="false">is pointing to Sheila being a victim too. She was 
murdered too and then someone framed her for her  </p>
  <p time="1085880" is_ac="false">own family's murders. But who would possibly want 
to do such a thing? Well actually, there'd been  </p>
  <p time="1092120" is_ac="false">whispers about town for quite some time at this 
point about the Bamber's own dear son, Jeremy. It was  </p>
  <p time="1099140" is_ac="false">no secret that Jeremy was going to inherit a lot 
from his parents when they passed away. Not only  </p>
  <p time="1105740" is_ac="false">did they have the big White House Farm Manor and 
all of the land that came with it, I think there  </p>
  <p time="1111260" is_ac="false">was 300 acres that came with that house alone 
and it was a house that was passed through their  </p>
  <p time="1116420" is_ac="false">family, Jeremy knew that it was going to be his 
one day. Well, his or his sisters. His parents had  </p>
  <p time="1122720" is_ac="false">more than just that one house though as well, 
I think they also had an apartment in London  </p>
  <p time="1126980" is_ac="false">that they rented out, it was a money maker like he 
was standing to inherit a whole lot of s**t and  </p>
  <p time="1135440" is_ac="false">money from his parents, when they passed. But he 
would have had to have shared all that with his  </p>
  <p time="1141500" is_ac="false">sister Sheila and probably with her two sons, as 
well. So now, all of that inheritance is getting  </p>
  <p time="1147080" is_ac="false">split four ways and the theory is that Jeremy 
didn't like the sound of that, he wanted everything  </p>
  <p time="1154760" is_ac="false">and so he decided to just take everyone out all 
in one night. Both his parents so that he could get  </p>
  <p time="1161240" is_ac="false">all the inheritance and also, the other people that 
might stand to inherit some of that. So that way he  </p>
  <p time="1167840" is_ac="false">gets everything. But all that being said, there was 
absolutely no evidence at this point in time. That  </p>
  <p time="1173120" is_ac="false">was just the theory that police had, that was just 
a suspicion. But actually now that they've come up  </p>
  <p time="1178280" is_ac="false">with this theory, it is very interesting because 
going back to Jeremy Bamber's phone call to the  </p>
  <p time="1183800" is_ac="false">police that night, how can that be true? Jeremy had 
called them saying my father's really worried, like  </p>
  <p time="1190040" is_ac="false">my sister's apparently running around the house 
with a gun, she's going crazy. Police have now  </p>
  <p time="1195200" is_ac="false">figured out that that's not true. So had Jeremy 
lied on the phone? Like, was that just a straight  </p>
  <p time="1201920" is_ac="false">up lie? So suspicions are rising against Jeremy 
Bamber at this point in time but nothing was  </p>
  <p time="1207560" is_ac="false">actually done about it. Um well, not by the time of 
the funeral anyway. On August 16 1985 is when the  </p>
  <p time="1214880" is_ac="false">funeral was held, the funeral for all five victims. 
And naturally because of the suspicions and the  </p>
  <p time="1221780" is_ac="false">whispers about town, all eyes were on Jeremy Bamber 
at this funeral and he was caught grinning to  </p>
  <p time="1230240" is_ac="false">himself at times, when he thought that no one could 
see him. He was also accused of really playing up  </p>
  <p time="1236120" is_ac="false">his grief for the media outside. Like he would be 
like quite calm, put together, maybe a little tear  </p>
  <p time="1242720" is_ac="false">on his face but then he would see the cameras and 
he would be, oh wailing. He would like really ham it  </p>
  <p time="1248840" is_ac="false">up and then apparently as soon as he would go off 
camera, you would like kind of see him snap out of  </p>
  <p time="1253220" is_ac="false">character. On the night of the funeral, Jeremy went 
out drinking um and he actually never mentioned  </p>
  <p time="1259640" is_ac="false">his family at all that whole night. But yeah he was 
out drinking, having a good time and throughout the  </p>
  <p time="1265700" is_ac="false">night, people remember him making a couple of off 
comments about how he runs things around here now.  </p>
  <p time="1273020" is_ac="false">You know like that kind of vibe, like he's the 
only one left and he's happy about it and cocky  </p>
  <p time="1278120" is_ac="false">and confident about what, like be in the heir of all 
of this fortune. In the days following the funeral,  </p>
  <p time="1283700" is_ac="false">fingerprint tests came back on that silencer.
So they'd already tested the blood but now they  </p>
  <p time="1289280" is_ac="false">were looking for fingerprints, they wanted to see 
who had been touching and handling it. And when  </p>
  <p time="1293300" is_ac="false">the fingerprint test came back, it had Sheila's 
fingerprints on it and Jeremy's. So now he had a  </p>
  <p time="1300320" is_ac="false">lot of explaining to do, police brought him into 
the police station and they were like look, how  </p>
  <p time="1305120" is_ac="false">could your fingerprints have been on the silencer? 
But Jeremy had quite a good excuse to be fair, he  </p>
  <p time="1310880" is_ac="false">was like because it's my silencer. Apparently 
it was his gun and his silencer and all of his  </p>
  <p time="1317600" is_ac="false">bullets that Sheila had found and used that day 
when she apparently went crazy, that's what he said  </p>
  <p time="1323720" is_ac="false">because he said that that day, him and his father 
were supposed to go out hunting. They used to go  </p>
  <p time="1328400" is_ac="false">out shooting animals. Um yeah, they were supposed 
to go out hunting but I don't think they ever did  </p>
  <p time="1333776" is_ac="false">um so he just kind of left his loaded gun out 
on the side at his dad's house and that was what  </p>
  <p time="1340100" is_ac="false">Sheila found that night, when she was supposedly 
in this episode. Annoyingly, police couldn't really  </p>
  <p time="1345920" is_ac="false">prove anything here I mean like, as much as they 
didn't entirely believe that, I mean like what can  </p>
  <p time="1351860" is_ac="false">they do? Like of course his fingerprints are going 
to be on his own gun, doesn't necessarily mean it  </p>
  <p time="1357200" is_ac="false">was from that night. So the investigation continues 
and police are really trying to look into Jeremy  </p>
  <p time="1363320" is_ac="false">Bamber as the killer. They really think that he 
killed his own family but they weren't really  </p>
  <p time="1368660" is_ac="false">getting anywhere, the evidence was very hard to 
come by. That was until the evidence brought itself  </p>
  <p time="1375380" is_ac="false">to them, in the form of a phone call from Jeremy's 
own girlfriend Julie Mugford. She said that she and  </p>
  <p time="1383060" is_ac="false">Jeremy had just fallen out, I think they just split 
up and it seems now, she was done covering for him.  </p>
  <p time="1389660" is_ac="false">She spoke with police and told them that she was 
very suspicious that Jeremy was responsible for  </p>
  <p time="1395480" is_ac="false">the murders. She said that she had no proof and 
he'd never like outright said it to her but based  </p>
  <p time="1401120" is_ac="false">on things that he'd been saying over the past 
couple of months, I don't know, he'd been like  </p>
  <p time="1405200" is_ac="false">dropping little hints that she'd definitely picked 
up on. She told police that he'd been joking or not  </p>
  <p time="1410720" is_ac="false">not joking for years now about getting rid of 
his parents, to be able to get all the inheritance  </p>
  <p time="1417140" is_ac="false">and now, it was all a bit too real. But he was very 
like insensitive with it because I guess it's one  </p>
  <p time="1423980" is_ac="false">thing to do like a morbid joke about like, oh when 
all you die I get all the money but like he was-  </p>
  <p time="1429620" is_ac="false">he wasn't- First of all he wasn't joking about it 
with his family, he would joke about it away from  </p>
  <p time="1434120" is_ac="false">them, so it makes it seem a bit more sinister 
but he would say things like, oh his Dad's old  </p>
  <p time="1439520" is_ac="false">anyway and his his mum's going mad. It'd be- it'd 
be better to just put them out of their misery.  </p>
  <p time="1444860" is_ac="false">And that's where it gets very weird. She even told 
police that earlier in the day before the murders,  </p>
  <p time="1451580" is_ac="false">she'd heard him saying it's tonight or never. And 
I don't know what the context of that quote is but  </p>
  <p time="1457160" is_ac="false">that's something that this case is very much clung 
onto. It's tonight or never, very dramatic from him.  </p>
  <p time="1463220" is_ac="false">So Julie alleged to the police that Jeremy had 
gone out and found a hitman to kill his parents  </p>
  <p time="1470480" is_ac="false">and he was going to pay this hitman £2000. 
Well actually, the hitman was for more than just  </p>
  <p time="1475460" is_ac="false">his parents, it was for the whole family that was 
in that house that night. He knew that his sister  </p>
  <p time="1480500" is_ac="false">and her sons were staying with their parents and 
so he had paid this Hitman £2000 to go and  </p>
  <p time="1488060" is_ac="false">take his whole family out in one night. Well this 
is what Julie is telling police, of course at this  </p>
  <p time="1493580" is_ac="false">point they are taking everything with a pinch of 
salt because they don't know this woman. And also  </p>
  <p time="1498440" is_ac="false">they're a little bit suspicious of her because why 
have you kept this a secret this whole time and  </p>
  <p time="1503840" is_ac="false">now you're only coming to to us when you've had 
an argument with him? Like they had to question the  </p>
  <p time="1509240" is_ac="false">validity of all of this. But the more that Julie 
was saying to police, the more things were starting  </p>
  <p time="1514640" is_ac="false">to like make sense and piece together. For example, 
she mentioned to them that Jeremy knew about this  </p>
  <p time="1521660" is_ac="false">one particular window at White House Farm that 
didn't lock. It didn't close properly and it just  </p>
  <p time="1528740" is_ac="false">so happened that it was that one window that the 
killer seemed to have gotten through, it was the  </p>
  <p time="1533600" is_ac="false">same window the police had to use to gain entry 
that day. It was the only thing that was unlocked.  </p>
  <p time="1538280" is_ac="false">So the fact that Jeremy had brought this up to 
his girlfriend before, shows that he knew an easy  </p>
  <p time="1544160" is_ac="false">way to get in and out of that house without having 
to like break in. I mean it could be a coincidence  </p>
  <p time="1549560" is_ac="false">that this like total stranger, mass murderer just 
so happens to try the janky window but I mean it  </p>
  <p time="1556700" is_ac="false">could also be someone that knew there was a janky 
window and knew how to get into that property. By  </p>
  <p time="1562400" is_ac="false">now, police were sufficiently convinced that Jeremy 
Bamber was the killer and so about a month after  </p>
  <p time="1568820" is_ac="false">the murders, they officially arrested him or 
charged him? No just arrested him. And they also  </p>
  <p time="1575000" is_ac="false">arrested another man that they believed could have 
been the hitman that Julie was alleging to exist.  </p>
  <p time="1581177" is_ac="false">Um so they brought this other man in but after a 
very quick questioning, he had a rock solid alibi  </p>
  <p time="1586880" is_ac="false">for the night of the murders and so he was let go. 
so now they've just got Jeremy in custody. Jeremy's  </p>
  <p time="1592520" is_ac="false">alibi for that night was, well he didn't have one 
really. He was just at home, supposedly. He said that  </p>
  <p time="1598760" is_ac="false">earlier in that evening he had been over at White 
House Farm, they'd all been there, the whole family.  </p>
  <p time="1603320" is_ac="false">They had like a dinner together, they were just 
spending the evening together and then Jeremy  </p>
  <p time="1608360" is_ac="false">left and went back to his own house, where he lived. 
And he said he was just there all night until 3:30  </p>
  <p time="1615440" is_ac="false">a.m, when he was woken up to that phone call from 
his father saying that his sister had gone mad. So  </p>
  <p time="1620420" is_ac="false">not a very concrete alibi, I mean there's no one 
there to prove it. There's- there's nothing to  </p>
  <p time="1625520" is_ac="false">prove there. So the police continued to question him 
and at one point they just turned to him and very  </p>
  <p time="1630080" is_ac="false">plainly said look, your girlfriend is currently 
accusing you of hiring a hitman to kill your whole  </p>
  <p time="1636020" is_ac="false">entire family, what do you have to say to that? And 
he essentially kind of says to the police like, oh  </p>
  <p time="1641180" is_ac="false">don't listen to her you know, she's just doing it 
to spite me, she's just mad because we're falling  </p>
  <p time="1645920" is_ac="false">out, she's just trying to ruin my life. Jeremy 
told the police that he had been cheating on  </p>
  <p time="1650900" is_ac="false">Julie for quite some time for like, months before 
she found out and it was literally within like the  </p>
  <p time="1656660" is_ac="false">last week that she had found out about it and so 
that's why she had decided to come to police. He  </p>
  <p time="1661580" is_ac="false">says it was more of a revenge thing, like she's 
just trying to get him in trouble. He said that  </p>
  <p time="1665960" is_ac="false">they'd been arguing and fighting all week, like 
physically fighting, as well. At one point she  </p>
  <p time="1671900" is_ac="false">smashed a mirror and then grabbed one of the glass 
shards and started like chasing him with it, trying  </p>
  <p time="1676820" is_ac="false">to cut him with it. But he wasn't a saint either 
like, he was being physically violent back to her.  </p>
  <p time="1682220" is_ac="false">He like twisted her arm up behind her back, 
she tried to smother him with a pillow, there  </p>
  <p time="1688100" is_ac="false">was just a lot of horrific stuff going on in their 
household that day. That week! That- well ever since  </p>
  <p time="1694880" is_ac="false">she found out he was cheating. So that was Jeremy's 
thing he was like look, she's just crazy like, she's  </p>
  <p time="1700460" is_ac="false">making all this up, she's trying to frame me. And 
police don't believe him because like look, we've  </p>
  <p time="1706100" is_ac="false">got all this evidence here. But you know, they 
didn't have like sufficient enough evidence  </p>
  <p time="1711740" is_ac="false">at this point in time to be able to charge him 
and you know they can only keep- they can only  </p>
  <p time="1716840" is_ac="false">keep people for like three days. I don't know why I 
went Scottish there? But they can only keep people  </p>
  <p time="1721520" is_ac="false">in custody for like three days and then at the end 
of that three days, if they don't have sufficient  </p>
  <p time="1726140" is_ac="false">evidence to charge them, they have to let them go. 
And unfortunately that's what happened here. So  </p>
  <p time="1731660" is_ac="false">Jeremy was released from police custody which was 
very frustrating because they- they knew he'd done  </p>
  <p time="1737600" is_ac="false">it, they just knew he'd done it. And the second he 
was let out or maybe not the second but very soon  </p>
  <p time="1743720" is_ac="false">after he was let out, he jets off to Saint 
Tropez. He just goes on holiday! In and amongst  </p>
  <p time="1749360" is_ac="false">all of this! So he was kicking back on a beach in 
France, blissfully unaware that police were on a  </p>
  <p time="1756680" is_ac="false">takedown mission back home. They were doing their 
research on Jeremy Bamber, they were talking to  </p>
  <p time="1762320" is_ac="false">everyone that knew him, friends, family, colleagues, 
neighbours, people that had known him in the past,  </p>
  <p time="1767720" is_ac="false">people that knew him when they were younger. They 
wanted to know what this guy was like, what his  </p>
  <p time="1772880" is_ac="false">like relationships and attitudes were like and 
also if there'd been any warning signs that had  </p>
  <p time="1777800" is_ac="false">been missed in the run-up to the massacre. Well it 
turns out that Jeremy Bamber had always been quite  </p>
  <p time="1783980" is_ac="false">a problem child ever since he was first adopted. 
That's- that's actually something I haven't even  </p>
  <p time="1789560" is_ac="false">gotten around to telling you, Jeremy and Sheila 
were both adopted by June and Neville because they  </p>
  <p time="1795020" is_ac="false">couldn't have children biologically themselves. 
So yeah they adopted Sheila, she was older and  </p>
  <p time="1800240" is_ac="false">then they adopted Jeremy not long after. But yeah 
apparently Jeremy was a lot of trouble from day  </p>
  <p time="1805700" is_ac="false">one, he was always getting into trouble at school, 
he was always badly behaved. There were reports  </p>
  <p time="1810560" is_ac="false">that said he was bullied in school, although I 
couldn't find any more like specifics on that. </p>
  <p time="1815720" is_ac="false">But it was as he grew into a teenager that this 
like, misbehaving and whatever really started  </p>
  <p time="1821540" is_ac="false">to take a concerning turn. It was turning more 
into like petty crimes and shoplifting and drug  </p>
  <p time="1829100" is_ac="false">smuggling. As he got older, Jeremy seemed to turn 
a lot more narcissistic and selfish and a lot of  </p>
  <p time="1836540" is_ac="false">people commented that he was all about his money. 
Money was all that mattered to him in the world.  </p>
  <p time="1841640" is_ac="false">And it was no secret that he wasn't happy about 
the fact that one day he was gonna have to share  </p>
  <p time="1847160" is_ac="false">his inheritance with his sister Sheila. He'd 
never been happy about that because naturally,  </p>
  <p time="1851840" is_ac="false">we all kind of know that us and our siblings 
are gonna split what we get from our parents  </p>
  <p time="1856460" is_ac="false">one day and from day one, he had not wanted that 
to happen. He would always b**ch about the fact  </p>
  <p time="1861500" is_ac="false">that she would get some of it. By the way, the fact 
that this is like common knowledge among friends  </p>
  <p time="1866360" is_ac="false">of the Bamber family, people that knew the Bamber 
family, Jeremy mustn't have been very secretive  </p>
  <p time="1872120" is_ac="false">about these feelings, like he was vocal. I don't 
know what had changed in the week that Jeremy was  </p>
  <p time="1879200" is_ac="false">away in Saint Tropez but on his arrival, he was jump 
scared at the airport by police, who could finally  </p>
  <p time="1886100" is_ac="false">now charge him with all five murders. The case went 
to trial just over a year after the murders took  </p>
  <p time="1893960" is_ac="false">place in October of 1986 and Jeremy started this 
trial by pleading not guilty. So the prosecution  </p>
  <p time="1901160" is_ac="false">laid out the whole sequence of events that they 
believe that Jeremy went through on the night  </p>
  <p time="1906380" is_ac="false">that he killed his entire family. They believed 
that in the early hours of that morning, Jeremy  </p>
  <p time="1911240" is_ac="false">rode his bike to White House Farm, he already 
had his rifle on him, they think because Jeremy  </p>
  <p time="1918380" is_ac="false">said that he'd left it loaded at his dad's house 
because they were meant to go hunting. Police don't  </p>
  <p time="1923180" is_ac="false">believe that. They actually had evidence for this 
because you know that window that they believe he  </p>
  <p time="1928100" is_ac="false">climbed through, well just as you enter the house, 
there was like a painted red shelf next to this  </p>
  <p time="1934700" is_ac="false">window and it had a big scratch on it and they'd 
actually found tracers of the red paint from this  </p>
  <p time="1939920" is_ac="false">shelf on the gun that killed the whole family. So 
that is evidence that the gun had snuck through  </p>
  <p time="1947000" is_ac="false">the window... obviously on a person, not on its own. 
It's believed that Jeremy did all the shootings  </p>
  <p time="1953420" is_ac="false">with the silencer on because it doesn't appear 
as the the gunshots were waking up the different  </p>
  <p time="1959300" is_ac="false">members of the family. Like I said both of those 
young boys, the six-year-old boys were found dead  </p>
  <p time="1965840" is_ac="false">in their beds and it seemed like they were asleep 
at the time, so they hadn't been awoken by the  </p>
  <p time="1970760" is_ac="false">gunshots. So once Jeremy had gotten into the house, 
he goes room to room shooting different members of  </p>
  <p time="1977600" is_ac="false">his family and it's believed that, you know Neville 
was found downstairs, well it's believed that he  </p>
  <p time="1983900" is_ac="false">was originally upstairs because it's the early hours 
of the morning, they were probably all in bed. But  </p>
  <p time="1988760" is_ac="false">police believe that there is evidence that Neville 
was forced downstairs by Jeremy because they think  </p>
  <p time="1996200" is_ac="false">there's a lot of like scratches in the middle of 
his back that could be from the end of the gun  </p>
  <p time="2001240" is_ac="false">being like pushed up against him, him being like 
pushed by the gun. This also makes a lot of sense  </p>
  <p time="2006280" is_ac="false">actually because Neville was the only member of 
the family to have been beaten as well as shot.  </p>
  <p time="2012280" is_ac="false">Like some of the other ones had been shot in their 
sleep whereas this man had had it really hard, like  </p>
  <p time="2017380" is_ac="false">he was fighting the attacker. So it makes sense 
that he was separated from the rest and isolated.  </p>
  <p time="2023440" is_ac="false">But finally when Jeremy had shot and killed his 
own father, he'd killed everyone in the house, he  </p>
  <p time="2030880" is_ac="false">then starts to stage it as a murder-suicide. 
He goes up to the bedroom where his sister was,  </p>
  <p time="2036460" is_ac="false">he lays the rifle in her hands, realises that the 
silencer makes it too big, pulls the silencer off,  </p>
  <p time="2043360" is_ac="false">leaves the scene as it is and then goes and hides 
the silencer, before sneaking back out of the house.  </p>
  <p time="2048280" is_ac="false">He then goes back home and then pretends to have 
gotten this frantic phone call from his dad. And  </p>
  <p time="2053320" is_ac="false">actually, something very interesting about this 
call that I think should have been a red flag from  </p>
  <p time="2058840" is_ac="false">the very beginning but it wasn't, was that this 
police phone call that they got from Jeremy Bamber  </p>
  <p time="2064420" is_ac="false">that night wasn't a 999 call. So he hadn't picked 
up his phone and gone for that really obvious, easy,  </p>
  <p time="2071380" is_ac="false">quick, emergency number 999, it's obviously meant to 
be quick and easy to do. He had picked up his phone  </p>
  <p time="2078460" is_ac="false">and then probably gone to like a phone book or 
something where they had the police station number  </p>
  <p time="2084460" is_ac="false">in it and then typed that long number in and then 
told them, hi I think my sister just murdered my  </p>
  <p time="2090820" is_ac="false">dad. Like what is all that stalling when you know 
that 999 is there for a reason. Oh and speaking  </p>
  <p time="2096220" is_ac="false">of stalling, one of the police officers stood up 
at the trial and said that when they were like  </p>
  <p time="2102700" is_ac="false">racing to the crime scene, racing out to White 
House Farm to go and like potentially save these  </p>
  <p time="2108160" is_ac="false">people's lives, he had overtaken Jeremy Bamber 
driving to the scene. Now at the time, he didn't  </p>
  <p time="2115780" is_ac="false">realise it was Jeremy Bamber but at this point now 
that he knows Jeremy and his car and everything, he  </p>
  <p time="2121660" is_ac="false">knows that on the night of the murders when they 
were racing to the scene to see if everyone's okay,  </p>
  <p time="2126520" is_ac="false">Jeremy was driving suspiciously slow. Like below 
the speed limit. And this is a man that is known  </p>
  <p time="2135040" is_ac="false">to drive fast at all times but on this particular 
time when he thinks that all of his family are  </p>
  <p time="2140800" is_ac="false">being murdered and he needs to get there ASAP, 
he's driving very very slow. Like to the point  </p>
  <p time="2145900" is_ac="false">where police overtook him. So all of that is the 
prosecution's argument that Jeremy Bamber is a  </p>
  <p time="2151600" is_ac="false">murderer and then came his defense argument which 
mainly relied on the fact that his sister was very,  </p>
  <p time="2159340" is_ac="false">very mentally ill and this was within, you know 
like her character. This- they believe that this  </p>
  <p time="2165220" is_ac="false">is something that she could have and had done. They 
brought up the fact that she had been diagnosed  </p>
  <p time="2170680" is_ac="false">with schizophrenia which actually back then in 
the 1980s, schizophrenia was used very much like an  </p>
  <p time="2177100" is_ac="false">umbrella term. It did mean schizophrenia but it 
could also mean anything from like, BPD to like  </p>
  <p time="2183760" is_ac="false">bipolar disorder or even like postnatal depression 
which is actually what a lot of people believe  </p>
  <p time="2190060" is_ac="false">Sheila had. Schizophrenia was often just used as 
like a blanket diagnosis for any kind of female  </p>
  <p time="2196780" is_ac="false">suffering with a mental illness, so it might not 
necessarily have been that that she had and a  </p>
  <p time="2203620" is_ac="false">lot of the symptoms that I've at least read 
in my research, seemed like she was suffering  </p>
  <p time="2209800" is_ac="false">with postnatal depression. She had confessed at 
one point that she had thoughts of harming her  </p>
  <p time="2216820" is_ac="false">children. Scary thoughts, not thoughts that she 
enjoyed having but that is relatively common  </p>
  <p time="2223060" is_ac="false">after giving birth is like, some women are 
scared to bath their own children because they're  </p>
  <p time="2228400" is_ac="false">having these awful thoughts that they don't want 
to act on. She'd been admitted to hospital so many  </p>
  <p time="2234760" is_ac="false">times throughout her life and the defense really 
just focused on all of this and they said, this is  </p>
  <p time="2240520" is_ac="false">clearly a mentally ill woman that has been proven 
time and time again to be suffering really, really  </p>
  <p time="2246340" is_ac="false">badly and she's even confessed to have had these 
thoughts in the past. So how can you like accuse  </p>
  <p time="2252640" is_ac="false">someone else of doing this, when it's obvious that 
it was her. Jeremy also said that on the night of  </p>
  <p time="2258460" is_ac="false">the murders, you know they were all at White House 
Farm before that having a family dinner, he said  </p>
  <p time="2264280" is_ac="false">that an argument had broken out that same evening 
between his sister and his mother. I don't know the  </p>
  <p time="2270460" is_ac="false">specifics of this argument but I think the general 
idea of it was that June didn't think that Sheila  </p>
  <p time="2276400" is_ac="false">was a good mother or a capable mother and she was 
saying that Sheila should put her kids in care.  </p>
  <p time="2281860" is_ac="false">And of course this caused a huge argument because 
Sheila didn't want to do that. So the defense are  </p>
  <p time="2288460" is_ac="false">trying to say well there you go, that's Sheila's 
motive for wanting to have done this, maybe she did  </p>
  <p time="2293920" is_ac="false">it because she was mad at her mum. She started with 
her mum and then she was just in this- this really  </p>
  <p time="2299500" is_ac="false">bad like episode and she just kills everyone else 
and then herself. And something the defense said as  </p>
  <p time="2305380" is_ac="false">well was that if Jeremy had tried to stage a fake 
suicide, it would have been extremely awkward for  </p>
  <p time="2313060" is_ac="false">him to do that and to be fair, I I actually agree 
with this one. Sheila was shot twice under the  </p>
  <p time="2319600" is_ac="false">chin by the rifle which makes sense for a suicide 
but for a murder, how would Jeremy have managed to  </p>
  <p time="2328480" is_ac="false">get the gunshots there if you're like standing by 
someone and you shoot them it's gonna go like here,  </p>
  <p time="2333640" is_ac="false">he would have had to have shot that from like 
underneath. In fact the evidence suggests that  </p>
  <p time="2339340" is_ac="false">Sheila was laying down at the time of her death 
and her body hadn't moved, it hadn't been dragged,  </p>
  <p time="2345280" is_ac="false">it hadn't you know moved since she died. And 
everyone else in the family was killed in their  </p>
  <p time="2350440" is_ac="false">beds apart from Neville and Sheila. So the defense 
argued that Sheila killed Neville downstairs and  </p>
  <p time="2357460" is_ac="false">then came upstairs, killed everyone upstairs ending 
with her own mother, who was killed on the hallway  </p>
  <p time="2364300" is_ac="false">and then Sheila went into the bedroom and then 
laid herself on the floor and then shot herself  </p>
  <p time="2371080" is_ac="false">twice in the neck. So the defense are trying to say 
here, how could Jeremy have like aimed under her  </p>
  <p time="2378040" is_ac="false">neck and shot her twice under the neck and then 
made it look like a suicide and made it all like,  </p>
  <p time="2382900" is_ac="false">actually, genuinely like biologically accurate, 
you know what I mean? Like the the gun was in  </p>
  <p time="2388180" is_ac="false">the right place, the bullet was in the right place 
to look like a suicide. How could he have staged a  </p>
  <p time="2392980" is_ac="false">murder like that? But I'm gonna burst the bubble, I 
think that can be easily explained because like we  </p>
  <p time="2399760" is_ac="false">said, there's evidence on Neville's back that the 
gun had been pushed into his back and that he'd been  </p>
  <p time="2404860" is_ac="false">moved downstairs. So maybe Jeremy was using this 
gun to threaten people into submission, it seems  </p>
  <p time="2410740" is_ac="false">that's what he'd done with Neville, who's to say he 
didn't do that to Sheila? What if he held the gun  </p>
  <p time="2415840" is_ac="false">up to her and said all right, lay on the floor now. 
And so she might have done and maybe that's when  </p>
  <p time="2421060" is_ac="false">he positioned the gun as he did, to look like 
a suicide. There is a way that that could have  </p>
  <p time="2427540" is_ac="false">happened and I think that is quite believable. I 
don't know, like I say it is just a theory, we don't  </p>
  <p time="2432400" is_ac="false">know what happened but I don't- I don't know that- I 
don't think that's a very good argument. And also I  </p>
  <p time="2437980" is_ac="false">just think if you were to shoot yourself, why would 
you like lay down at the foot of the bed? She was  </p>
  <p time="2443800" is_ac="false">just found in a really odd place, like I don't know 
I feel like if those were going to be your final-  </p>
  <p time="2448900" is_ac="false">final moments, you would probably like sit on the 
bed or something, I don't know? I wouldn't just like  </p>
  <p time="2454300" is_ac="false">lay down in the like, in just some odd space at the 
bottom of the bed, I just find it odd. Anyway at the  </p>
  <p time="2461140" is_ac="false">end of the trial, Jeremy Bamber was found guilt 
guilty of all five counts of murder and he was  </p>
  <p time="2467020" is_ac="false">given five consecutive life sentences in jail. But 
Bamber still to this day maintains his innocence  </p>
  <p time="2473740" is_ac="false">and like I said at the very beginning of this case, 
this is actually regarded as potentially one of  </p>
  <p time="2479980" is_ac="false">the worst miscarriages of justice ever in the UK 
ever. Because if it is a miscarriage of justice,  </p>
  <p time="2487360" is_ac="false">this man has been in jail for like 40 years for 
a crime that he might not have committed but  </p>
  <p time="2494505" is_ac="false">um I for one am not one of those people that 
believe that, I think the right person is in  </p>
  <p time="2499000" is_ac="false">jail. I think it was quite in keeping 
with what we know about his character  </p>
  <p time="2504260" is_ac="false">um and you know evidence, I guess. But that is all 
I have on this case, comment down below, I want to  </p>
  <p time="2511180" is_ac="false">know what you guys think. Do you think that this is 
solved correctly or do you think that there could  </p>
  <p time="2517300" is_ac="false">be more to this? And thank you again to Ritual for 
sponsoring this video, remember they're offering  </p>
  <p time="2523060" is_ac="false">you guys 20% off during your first month 
when you go to ritual.com forward slash eneale20.  </p>
  <p time="2529180" is_ac="false">The link is also down below in the description and 
use the code eneale20 at checkout. A huge thank you  </p>
  <p time="2535360" is_ac="false">to all of my channel members for supporting the 
channel and helping me decide the cases that I  </p>
  <p time="2539680" is_ac="false">cover. All of my tier 2 members are on screen right 
now, so thank you so much. If you want to become a  </p>
  <p time="2544840" is_ac="false">channel member, you can click the join button 
down below. But yeah thank you so so much for  </p>
  <p time="2548500" is_ac="false">watching, if you enjoyed this video please leave 
a thumbs up down below, that would really help me  </p>
  <p time="2552700" is_ac="false">out. If you want to watch another one of my videos, 
here you go! I've picked you one out special or you can  </p>
  <p time="2558160" is_ac="false">subscribe by clicking my face right there, I post 
True Crime content every single week. Okay, bye!</p>
</text>
