<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="Nick DiGiovanni" date="20210602" date_ts="1622649604" views="15707239" title="Tasting Rare Snacks and Drinks" likes="264761" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="170" is_ac="false">Nick:
Snacks. We all love them.</p>
  <p time="1610" is_ac="false">There's something about just cuddling up at
night after a really long day and just eating</p>
  <p time="5570" is_ac="false">a bunch of yummy snacks.</p>
  <p time="6710" is_ac="false">Everybody has their own guilty pleasures,
right?</p>
  <p time="8840" is_ac="false">Some people seem to like cereal at night.</p>
  <p time="10730" is_ac="false">Not joking. I know a bunch of people who
just make a nice big bowl of cereal and</p>
  <p time="14120" is_ac="false">crunch down at night.</p>
  <p time="15380" is_ac="false">Other people are classic.</p>
  <p time="16460" is_ac="false">They go with chips or popcorn, and then you
got that giant bucket of people that love</p>
  <p time="20570" is_ac="false">their sweets. Now, don't get me wrong, I got
a sweet tooth, but I'm not really a big</p>
  <p time="24050" is_ac="false">dessert person. But when I say sweets, this
can literally mean anything.</p>
  <p time="27410" is_ac="false">But I'm a little bit all over the place
right now.</p>
  <p time="29090" is_ac="false">Let's talk about what we're doing today.</p>
  <p time="30620" is_ac="false">Of course it has to do with snacks, but this
video is going to be a little bit different</p>
  <p time="34190" is_ac="false">because yeah, we'll do a little bit of
cooking.</p>
  <p time="35960" is_ac="false">We always have to, but I have worked really
hard for the past month or two to secure some</p>
  <p time="40190" is_ac="false">of the rare snacks from all around the
world.</p>
  <p time="42320" is_ac="false">Some of these things were made in really
small batches by companies we know and love,</p>
  <p time="45860" is_ac="false">only to suddenly be discontinued at some
point.</p>
  <p time="47780" is_ac="false">But somehow I've gotten my hands on one of
them.</p>
  <p time="49550" is_ac="false">Others are products that are sold throughout
the world.</p>
  <p time="51710" is_ac="false">Think really unique flavors of your favorite
bag of chips or Skittles cookies, or really</p>
  <p time="56630" is_ac="false">weirdly flavored Oreos, or even super
interesting sodas like Strawberry Fanta.</p>
  <p time="60950" is_ac="false">Also, a few videos back we made that amazing
creme brulée video, and we got almost 7000</p>
  <p time="65690" is_ac="false">comments on it because I wanted to give back
to you for helping us as a channel to reach 2</p>
  <p time="69210" is_ac="false">million and send one of you with a plus one
to a three Michelin star dinner.</p>
  <p time="73100" is_ac="false">It's a special opportunity that, quite
frankly, even I have only done once in my</p>
  <p time="76970" is_ac="false">entire life because, as we all know, there
aren't even that many three Michelin star</p>
  <p time="80150" is_ac="false">restaurants on the planet. Now, I've picked
out the winner and I'm gonna announce it at</p>
  <p time="83300" is_ac="false">the end of this video. It's my hope that we
can do many more giveaways like this down the</p>
  <p time="86630" is_ac="false">road, but check that out at the end of the
video to see who won.</p>
  <p time="89000" is_ac="false">I am so excited for you.</p>
  <p time="90350" is_ac="false">Now enough talking because I know you want
to see the goods.</p>
  <p time="92840" is_ac="false">So here they are.</p>
  <p time="94490" is_ac="false">Now before we dive in and start eating, I
want to show you a couple of what we're</p>
  <p time="97550" is_ac="false">dealing with today. Since I already
mentioned it.</p>
  <p time="99350" is_ac="false">Let's start first with these Skittles
cookies.</p>
  <p time="101360" is_ac="false">Now, theoretically, this is exactly what it
sounds like.</p>
  <p time="103940" is_ac="false">It's cookies made by the company Skittles.</p>
  <p time="106040" is_ac="false">It says they're crunchy and not chewy, and
it looks like it's literally just plain old</p>
  <p time="109310" is_ac="false">cookies with some Skittles inside.</p>
  <p time="110630" is_ac="false">So I'm curious to try these out.</p>
  <p time="112190" is_ac="false">Next, we have something that I am incredibly
excited for, and those are a good old bag of</p>
  <p time="116240" is_ac="false">Doritos, which frankly, are one of my guilty
pleasures.</p>
  <p time="118520" is_ac="false">But these aren't just any regular Doritos.</p>
  <p time="120650" is_ac="false">These are nacho, cheesier Doritos.</p>
  <p time="123170" is_ac="false">You can see that this is quite clearly from
a different country.</p>
  <p time="125690" is_ac="false">And like I said, that's how we get a lot of
these things.</p>
  <p time="127820" is_ac="false">These are probably constantly sold elsewhere
in several countries, but I was somehow lucky</p>
  <p time="131600" is_ac="false">enough to find a set of them.</p>
  <p time="132740" is_ac="false">Next we got some Cheetos, mac and cheese.</p>
  <p time="134870" is_ac="false">Now, the idea of Cheetos making something
that you actually have to cook yourself.</p>
  <p time="138260" is_ac="false">It's pretty funny to me, especially
considering you can go into any gas station</p>
  <p time="141500" is_ac="false">or any market out there and grab a bag off
the shelf and eat it like that, but I believe</p>
  <p time="145490" is_ac="false">this is the only thing in all of our snacks
that we actually have to cook today.</p>
  <p time="148730" is_ac="false">So it looks like they're still gonna put me
to work a little bit.</p>
  <p time="150830" is_ac="false">Here we have some doctor Pepper cotton
candy.</p>
  <p time="153110" is_ac="false">Honestly, I'm actually a huge fan of cotton
candy myself, so this one's going to be a</p>
  <p time="156710" is_ac="false">treat. The last thing I'm going to call out
before we begin tasting are these Sour Patch</p>
  <p time="160340" is_ac="false">Kids that are mango flavored.</p>
  <p time="162140" is_ac="false">I love mango, and I'm not sure why this
isn't a flavor literally everywhere.</p>
  <p time="166490" is_ac="false">Let's first start with our chips.</p>
  <p time="167960" is_ac="false">We're going to go through in categories.</p>
  <p time="169460" is_ac="false">I'm gonna open this thing up here.</p>
  <p time="170810" is_ac="false">And what looks to be is chips and dip,
clearly Doritos.</p>
  <p time="173840" is_ac="false">I open this thing up and there's this silver
bag inside, which is actually really</p>
  <p time="177560" is_ac="false">interesting. I've never seen that colored
packaging for Doritos, literally.</p>
  <p time="180740" is_ac="false">It's almost as if you took a normal Doritos
bag and sucked out all the color on it,</p>
  <p time="184490" is_ac="false">except for a few little orange triangles.</p>
  <p time="186410" is_ac="false">This container itself is also pretty cool, I
must say.</p>
  <p time="188960" is_ac="false">If you look closely right here, you can see
the word dipping.</p>
  <p time="191390" is_ac="false">So my guess is that this has no color,
because you haven't yet added all that</p>
  <p time="194420" is_ac="false">Doritos flavor to them yet.</p>
  <p time="195830" is_ac="false">Think about it. The Cool Ranch bag is bright
blue.</p>
  <p time="198080" is_ac="false">The Nacho cheese bag is bright yellow and
orange.</p>
  <p time="200450" is_ac="false">This doesn't have that flavor yet.</p>
  <p time="201980" is_ac="false">Here's the flavor and it's yellow.</p>
  <p time="203630" is_ac="false">To start, I'm gonna open up my dip, which
pretty much looks to be your run of the mill</p>
  <p time="207020" is_ac="false">salsa. Then into our Doritos bag we go.</p>
  <p time="209630" is_ac="false">First, I want to try one of these chips
plain because quite honestly, it already</p>
  <p time="212630" is_ac="false">smells and looks like they have a ton of
seasoning on them.</p>
  <p time="216730" is_ac="false">Wow. Honestly, I can't entirely tell what
the flavor is here.</p>
  <p time="219940" is_ac="false">It's a little bit cheesy, a little bit
tomatoey, but let's do what they've told us</p>
  <p time="223270" is_ac="false">to do and give it a little dip.</p>
  <p time="226240" is_ac="false">Okay, I'm gonna be honest.</p>
  <p time="227620" is_ac="false">This kind of tastes like the chips and salsa
you get out of a lunchable.</p>
  <p time="230350" is_ac="false">Is that a good thing? Is that a bad thing?</p>
  <p time="232000" is_ac="false">I'll leave you to decide.</p>
  <p time="233140" is_ac="false">After doing this, we found out there's a
little container here for your sauce, and</p>
  <p time="236800" is_ac="false">then it looks like you actually dump the
chip back into the container.</p>
  <p time="239740" is_ac="false">Just a little bit of Doritos innovation.</p>
  <p time="242470" is_ac="false">Next we got some Lay's.</p>
  <p time="243970" is_ac="false">And this flavor, I have to admit looks
fantastic.</p>
  <p time="246280" is_ac="false">Yogurt vamsam.</p>
  <p time="248350" is_ac="false">Yesillikli, honestly, I'm not sure what
language this is, but these chips look</p>
  <p time="252730" is_ac="false">incredible. First, let's get a little bit of
that flavor.</p>
  <p time="256120" is_ac="false">Evidently it looks to be some sort of yogurt
flavor.</p>
  <p time="259390" is_ac="false">Here's what I'm getting. Not yogurt, that's
for sure.</p>
  <p time="261580" is_ac="false">Honestly, to me, these feel like you're
pretty run of the mill sour cream and onion</p>
  <p time="264610" is_ac="false">chips. I see a little bit of parsley right
on the side of the back here, and then I see</p>
  <p time="267880" is_ac="false">some yogurt and also what looks to be mint,
which makes really no sense to me.</p>
  <p time="271870" is_ac="false">There's no mint in here, but these are
pretty good chips.</p>
  <p time="274630" is_ac="false">I'm gonna rate them on par with the pretty
solid bag of Lay's sour cream and onion</p>
  <p time="278560" is_ac="false">chips. Our next bag here is another bag of
Doritos, because really, we're bouncing</p>
  <p time="282190" is_ac="false">between Doritos and Lay's right now.</p>
  <p time="284080" is_ac="false">This one I am incredibly excited for,
because what it looks like we have here are</p>
  <p time="287980" is_ac="false">these poppy seed Doritos.</p>
  <p time="289630" is_ac="false">Clearly, it's some mix between tomatoes and
poppy seeds.</p>
  <p time="292360" is_ac="false">And I actually kind of like this guessing
game that I'm playing by tasting the chips,</p>
  <p time="295840" is_ac="false">not really knowing what countries or
languages these are.</p>
  <p time="298690" is_ac="false">Again, we have another metallic Doritos bag,
which is super interesting.</p>
  <p time="302080" is_ac="false">And here's what I'm gonna say. At first
glance.</p>
  <p time="303760" is_ac="false">The poppy seeds that you see in the back
here, and the poppy seeds that are on the</p>
  <p time="306700" is_ac="false">counter here, I have to say I'm a little bit
let down, but it's fine.</p>
  <p time="309940" is_ac="false">I can tell that there's poppy seeds in the
chips.</p>
  <p time="311830" is_ac="false">I just like the look of it better when
they're on the outside of them.</p>
  <p time="314530" is_ac="false">Let's take a little bite.</p>
  <p time="317050" is_ac="false">Hmm. This is cool because you can actually
taste the poppy seeds, like, a lot.</p>
  <p time="321040" is_ac="false">This is really interesting.</p>
  <p time="322720" is_ac="false">What you have here is this very slight
flavor of salsa.</p>
  <p time="325840" is_ac="false">Very, very ever so slight.</p>
  <p time="327280" is_ac="false">Tiny bit of tang, tiny bit of acid.</p>
  <p time="329050" is_ac="false">But really, you actually get a lot of that
poppy seed flavor.</p>
  <p time="332200" is_ac="false">And I'm not really sure if you can tell, but
these chips are a little bit thicker, more</p>
  <p time="335320" is_ac="false">substantive than regular Doritos.</p>
  <p time="336790" is_ac="false">You might find that definitely changes the
overall mouthfeel of these chips.</p>
  <p time="340180" is_ac="false">Quite good. Now, what we have here is a
crisp bag of Lay's potato chips, specifically</p>
  <p time="345070" is_ac="false">sea salt and black pepper.</p>
  <p time="346480" is_ac="false">Number one baby, I'm gonna gently open the
side of this bag because I don't want to ruin</p>
  <p time="349840" is_ac="false">this bag. It's actually quite beautiful, and
I don't know why.</p>
  <p time="352390" is_ac="false">It was very plump and packed with plenty of
air, which I liked.</p>
  <p time="355090" is_ac="false">Now, I know salt and pepper are a pretty
classic flavor for chips, and if we look up</p>
  <p time="358480" is_ac="false">close, we can definitely see they have that
speckled pepper on there.</p>
  <p time="361000" is_ac="false">But let's give it a try.</p>
  <p time="362830" is_ac="false">Now these are really good.</p>
  <p time="363970" is_ac="false">And what I like about these is that these
are genuinely well seasoned potato chips.</p>
  <p time="367480" is_ac="false">This is as if a legitimate chef was given
plain Lay's potato chips and told to season</p>
  <p time="371740" is_ac="false">them perfectly with salt and pepper.</p>
  <p time="373330" is_ac="false">You get this. I know it seems simple, but of
all the chips we've tried, these are my</p>
  <p time="377260" is_ac="false">favorite so far. Let me get some water one
second.</p>
  <p time="379270" is_ac="false">Yeah. Did you see the chip?</p>
  <p time="384140" is_ac="false">What do you do? You're fired.</p>
  <p time="385760" is_ac="false">What are you doing? You're fired again.</p>
  <p time="387830" is_ac="false">Now there is going to be nothing like a
crisp bag of nacho cheesier chips.</p>
  <p time="392810" is_ac="false">You know, I feel like Nacho Cheesier is such
a funny name.</p>
  <p time="395390" is_ac="false">Think about all the executives sitting in
this Doritos room.</p>
  <p time="398030" is_ac="false">And one of the guys is like, I got it.</p>
  <p time="400160" is_ac="false">We're gonna call it Nacho Cheesier.</p>
  <p time="403670" is_ac="false">You gotta love the sound of opening a fresh
bag of chips.</p>
  <p time="407600" is_ac="false">Taking some of that beautiful steam I can
look right now, and I can tell you right now</p>
  <p time="411110" is_ac="false">that this is disappointing.</p>
  <p time="412130" is_ac="false">And I'll tell you why. Take a look inside
that bag.</p>
  <p time="414230" is_ac="false">All right. Just take a look inside that bag.</p>
  <p time="416030" is_ac="false">I've just opened it. You've seen me.</p>
  <p time="417620" is_ac="false">Does that look Nacho cheesier to you?</p>
  <p time="419480" is_ac="false">Because these right here do not look Nacho
cheesier to me.</p>
  <p time="422120" is_ac="false">Now, these chips right here are from Japan.</p>
  <p time="423890" is_ac="false">And Japanese food is number one on my list.</p>
  <p time="426050" is_ac="false">But how on earth can you be telling me that
this is Nacho cheesier?</p>
  <p time="428810" is_ac="false">If this clearly has less cheese than regular
nacho cheese chips, what are we doing?</p>
  <p time="432680" is_ac="false">But I'm not going to be biased.</p>
  <p time="433760" is_ac="false">I'm gonna close my eyes and I'm gonna eat
it.</p>
  <p time="437620" is_ac="false">No, no, really.</p>
  <p time="439300" is_ac="false">What I'm looking for when I eat this chip
is.</p>
  <p time="441460" is_ac="false">Is this nacho cheesier?</p>
  <p time="442900" is_ac="false">And it's not. It's not nacho cheesier.</p>
  <p time="444700" is_ac="false">It's nacho cheese.</p>
  <p time="445780" is_ac="false">It's fantastic. Nacho cheese, in fact.</p>
  <p time="447790" is_ac="false">But first of all, the Doritos are clearly
made in a different way.</p>
  <p time="450820" is_ac="false">These chips are not the same chips that we
get in the US.</p>
  <p time="453070" is_ac="false">And second of all, they are absolutely,
positively not cheesier.</p>
  <p time="456340" is_ac="false">But they're dang good. Now we're almost done
with the chip category here, but we do have</p>
  <p time="460300" is_ac="false">these cucumber flavored chips.</p>
  <p time="461680" is_ac="false">And I have to say, this bag is badass.</p>
  <p time="464620" is_ac="false">I'm not sure what sort of animal this is.</p>
  <p time="466210" is_ac="false">I don't know if it's an owl or some sort of
cat, I really don't know.</p>
  <p time="469450" is_ac="false">So maybe some sort of mythical creature.</p>
  <p time="471040" is_ac="false">But it is beautiful.</p>
  <p time="472420" is_ac="false">I mean, this bag is gorgeous.</p>
  <p time="474280" is_ac="false">It is an absolute work of art.</p>
  <p time="476500" is_ac="false">Inside it looks beautiful and clean.</p>
  <p time="478600" is_ac="false">But let's pull out these cucumber flavored
chips.</p>
  <p time="480760" is_ac="false">I don't think I'm going to be able to fit
this in my mouth.</p>
  <p time="487940" is_ac="false">Nope, don't like that.</p>
  <p time="489080" is_ac="false">These are really, really sweet.</p>
  <p time="490790" is_ac="false">They definitely taste like cucumber, but
it's like if you had cucumber and then added</p>
  <p time="494150" is_ac="false">a bunch of sugar onto it, which they say
actually tastes like watermelon.</p>
  <p time="497210" is_ac="false">As a fun little fact, take a slice of
cucumber, put some sugar on it, take a bite</p>
  <p time="500420" is_ac="false">out of it. Tastes like watermelon.</p>
  <p time="501500" is_ac="false">I have to be honest. These are also doing
something extraordinarily weird to my tongue.</p>
  <p time="504980" is_ac="false">You know, when you eat one of those gums,
ice breakers or something that is supposed to</p>
  <p time="508040" is_ac="false">cool down your mouth a bunch?</p>
  <p time="509300" is_ac="false">They put that in these freaking chips.</p>
  <p time="511310" is_ac="false">Why would they do that?</p>
  <p time="512360" is_ac="false">That's so not what you want with a bag of
chips.</p>
  <p time="514760" is_ac="false">When you suck in air, all of a sudden your
mouth and tongue is really cool.</p>
  <p time="517880" is_ac="false">This whole experience is weird.</p>
  <p time="519560" is_ac="false">The look of this bag, the taste of them.
Manny: Did they actually do that?</p>
  <p time="523970" is_ac="false">Yeah, well, I'm not gonna make that up.</p>
  <p time="526550" is_ac="false">Okay? We have our last food that I would
classify as a chip.</p>
  <p time="529310" is_ac="false">Now, I'm not sure where these are from, but
they're clearly new in some sense.</p>
  <p time="532130" is_ac="false">They're Doritos crackers.</p>
  <p time="533210" is_ac="false">And I know none of you have seen these in
the stores around you, because these are</p>
  <p time="535910" is_ac="false">pretty much impossible to find right now, at
least as far as I know.</p>
  <p time="538520" is_ac="false">First, let's open up the top slide these bad
boys out, getting that same metallic look</p>
  <p time="543050" is_ac="false">that we got from the other packaging.</p>
  <p time="544520" is_ac="false">But you know what? I'm gonna note first out
of anything else here is that this is</p>
  <p time="547700" is_ac="false">extremely heavy.</p>
  <p time="549020" is_ac="false">And the reason I say that is because of
this.</p>
  <p time="550760" is_ac="false">Anytime you have Doritos or Lay's or anything
like that, usually the bag is pretty light,</p>
  <p time="554600" is_ac="false">but they actually really pack these in.</p>
  <p time="556430" is_ac="false">So I feel like you're kind of getting your
bang for your buck here.</p>
  <p time="558680" is_ac="false">Now, right there are our little crackers and
they're clearly seasoned with something and</p>
  <p time="562250" is_ac="false">they actually look quite good.</p>
  <p time="563390" is_ac="false">They also have the Doritos logo on them.</p>
  <p time="564920" is_ac="false">But when I smell them, they have this kind
of weird, tangy flavor that I don't really</p>
  <p time="568310" is_ac="false">love with chips, typically.</p>
  <p time="569510" is_ac="false">But let's give it a try with an open mind.</p>
  <p time="572420" is_ac="false">Really nice crunch. They do have that
artificial flavor and tang that again, I</p>
  <p time="576320" is_ac="false">don't love it. In fact, the best thing I can
give you to describe it is if you've ever had</p>
  <p time="579290" is_ac="false">those pizza flavored goldfish kind of tastes
a little bit like that.</p>
  <p time="582020" is_ac="false">And I do not like those at all, but these
are actually pretty good.</p>
  <p time="584900" is_ac="false">They have that butteriness that a Ritz
cracker has, and they're actually seasoned</p>
  <p time="588200" is_ac="false">really, really well. So you're basically
just getting Doritos here, but in cracker</p>
  <p time="591410" is_ac="false">form. Pretty cool. Now it's time we've
entered a new category.</p>
  <p time="594680" is_ac="false">And that category is cookies.</p>
  <p time="596330" is_ac="false">If you can't tell, I've been pretty excited
to try these Skittles cookies, so I'm just</p>
  <p time="600170" is_ac="false">gonna cut right to the chase here.</p>
  <p time="601460" is_ac="false">We can't blame it for having a couple of
broken ones, because I ship these from all</p>
  <p time="604340" is_ac="false">around the world. When I'm first gonna note
is the smell.</p>
  <p time="607400" is_ac="false">It's weird. It's weird.</p>
  <p time="608960" is_ac="false">It smells like Skittles.</p>
  <p time="610040" is_ac="false">Now, if I take one of these cookies out, you
could literally see that there are Skittles</p>
  <p time="613670" is_ac="false">inside here. I know I've tried a lot of
foods out there, but this this is weird, but</p>
  <p time="618020" is_ac="false">hey, sweet goes with sweet, and, you know,
let's give this a shot.</p>
  <p time="624250" is_ac="false">Ah, no.</p>
  <p time="625480" is_ac="false">Do you see that right there? That is a red
skittle.</p>
  <p time="627940" is_ac="false">And I ate a cookie and it had several
Skittles inside it.</p>
  <p time="630490" is_ac="false">I mean, basically these cookies are just
very, very sweet.</p>
  <p time="633340" is_ac="false">And they have Skittles in them.</p>
  <p time="635050" is_ac="false">The Skittles are clearly a little bit
different from the regular Skittles you might</p>
  <p time="637870" is_ac="false">normally find. But again, this is weird.</p>
  <p time="639880" is_ac="false">I'm happy I tried them.</p>
  <p time="641050" is_ac="false">I probably won't buy them again.</p>
  <p time="642550" is_ac="false">Next up, chocolate cream Oreos.</p>
  <p time="644230" is_ac="false">Now we have a lot of Oreos to try today.</p>
  <p time="645880" is_ac="false">And right off the bat I thought I was gonna
pull out the whole sleeve.</p>
  <p time="648250" is_ac="false">But I got this little cutie and I kind of
like that because that way you don't have to</p>
  <p time="650980" is_ac="false">sit on the couch and feel like you have to
binge eat an entire sleeve of Oreos in one</p>
  <p time="654310" is_ac="false">sitting. I thought, I've ever done that or
anything.</p>
  <p time="655990" is_ac="false">I have to say, these Oreos look really good.</p>
  <p time="658090" is_ac="false">And to the people out there that dip Oreos
and milk, I'm gonna be honest.</p>
  <p time="660970" is_ac="false">I do not understand that in the slightest.</p>
  <p time="663070" is_ac="false">It's like dipping your hand in water.</p>
  <p time="664810" is_ac="false">None of the milk actually sticks to the
Oreos.</p>
  <p time="666940" is_ac="false">Why do people do that? I get dipping cookies
and milk, but not to worry about.</p>
  <p time="670510" is_ac="false">Anyway, chocolate cream?</p>
  <p time="671590" is_ac="false">Oreos. Let's give these a try.</p>
  <p time="674530" is_ac="false">I am on a roller coaster of flavors right
now.</p>
  <p time="676840" is_ac="false">It seems like I wouldn't be because this
entire little cookie is all chocolate.</p>
  <p time="679840" is_ac="false">The Oreo on the outside is the same as any
regular Oreo you'd eat, but the problem is</p>
  <p time="683170" is_ac="false">that on the inside, whatever chocolate cream
they put inside there is not very good.</p>
  <p time="686890" is_ac="false">Something about it is just super artificial.</p>
  <p time="688690" is_ac="false">It's got some weird flavors in there and I
don't love it.</p>
  <p time="690910" is_ac="false">Let's balance those Oreos out with something
a little bit different and something a little</p>
  <p time="693970" is_ac="false">bit lighter. Now, I'm guessing most of you
can't read this side here, but what we got</p>
  <p time="697240" is_ac="false">here are vanilla mousse Oreos, and they're
the thin kind, which quite frankly, I kind of</p>
  <p time="701440" is_ac="false">love. I keep forgetting there's two little
things inside each one of these.</p>
  <p time="704410" is_ac="false">Now. I feel like with this little guy, I
have to be kind of delicate.</p>
  <p time="706690" is_ac="false">And they're really, really cute.</p>
  <p time="708010" is_ac="false">How many thin ones are inside here?</p>
  <p time="709450" is_ac="false">But let's take one of the Oreos out,
appreciate just how thin it is, and then eat</p>
  <p time="713410" is_ac="false">it all in one bite.</p>
  <p time="716140" is_ac="false">To me, these tastes a little bit like
cheesecake at least once you bite it all</p>
  <p time="719500" is_ac="false">together. And they have an extremely,
extremely different flavor to your regular</p>
  <p time="723580" is_ac="false">Oreos that you find at the store.</p>
  <p time="724930" is_ac="false">Again, I mean, it really kind of is vanilla
cream.</p>
  <p time="727690" is_ac="false">I'll rate these pretty high up on the Oreos
I've tried, but they're definitely in the</p>
  <p time="730510" is_ac="false">more unique side of things.</p>
  <p time="732040" is_ac="false">Next up, Ritz Bits s'mores version.</p>
  <p time="734800" is_ac="false">First of all, I'll start by saying that I
love that on the back, that I love that each</p>
  <p time="738130" is_ac="false">side has the same name, but in different
languages.</p>
  <p time="740380" is_ac="false">Either way, I've definitely never seen
S'mores Ritz, so I am very curious to try how</p>
  <p time="744610" is_ac="false">these are. Now let's start by pouring out a
few on our counter just to see what these</p>
  <p time="747850" is_ac="false">look like. Because if the box isn't lying,
we should get a nice split right down the</p>
  <p time="751420" is_ac="false">middle. So it's time for the moment of
truth.</p>
  <p time="753760" is_ac="false">This is bullshit. Let's try a few more.</p>
  <p time="755710" is_ac="false">Ah, okay, so they definitely didn't split it
down the middle, but on this one at least it</p>
  <p time="759040" is_ac="false">has both. What's funny about this one right
here is that whoever put these two things</p>
  <p time="762490" is_ac="false">together, and I don't know if it was a
person or a machine, this piece right here is</p>
  <p time="765850" is_ac="false">upside down. Notice that both sides should
look like the top here.</p>
  <p time="768790" is_ac="false">For instance, take this one right here where
you can see the little dimples on both sides.</p>
  <p time="772210" is_ac="false">But this one, that's not the case.</p>
  <p time="773830" is_ac="false">This is the flat, ugly part that's supposed
to be on the inside.</p>
  <p time="776560" is_ac="false">Sorry to really dive in on you here, Ritz,
but you know, you got to step it up a little</p>
  <p time="779830" is_ac="false">bit in those factories. Time to give this a
little taste.</p>
  <p time="783430" is_ac="false">Do I get some moreish?</p>
  <p time="785110" is_ac="false">Okay. I was waiting and waiting and waiting.</p>
  <p time="787600" is_ac="false">See if I would get that s'mores flavor.</p>
  <p time="789100" is_ac="false">And here's what I do get as you continue to
eat this little guy for a while, you're</p>
  <p time="792610" is_ac="false">really just tasting a little bit of vanilla,
a little bit of chocolate, but at the end you</p>
  <p time="795730" is_ac="false">get that graham cracker flavor.</p>
  <p time="797050" is_ac="false">So that's the only thing I would say they
did right with these little s'mores</p>
  <p time="800050" is_ac="false">sandwiches. They're okay.</p>
  <p time="801190" is_ac="false">They're not great. But I guess now that we
do look a little bit closer at them, they</p>
  <p time="804310" is_ac="false">have that almost granular, sandy like
texture that you'd find in a graham cracker.</p>
  <p time="807850" is_ac="false">So they nailed that part. Chocolate peanut
butter pie.</p>
  <p time="809980" is_ac="false">Oreos I love the creativity there.</p>
  <p time="812140" is_ac="false">And you know, I wanted to do these next
because just like those little Ritz crackers</p>
  <p time="815080" is_ac="false">that we just looked at, they're supposed to
have a nice split down the center of that</p>
  <p time="817960" is_ac="false">color of the two different types of frosting
in there.</p>
  <p time="820120" is_ac="false">So let's see if Oreo got it right.</p>
  <p time="821530" is_ac="false">Let's take out our first one.</p>
  <p time="822760" is_ac="false">You'll notice right away that it's a
different colored shell, but they nailed the</p>
  <p time="826120" is_ac="false">split down the middle Oreo.</p>
  <p time="827530" is_ac="false">You get huge brownie points for that.</p>
  <p time="829330" is_ac="false">Question is does this taste like a chocolate
peanut butter pie?</p>
  <p time="833650" is_ac="false">Immediately you're hit with that Nutter
Butter like flavor.</p>
  <p time="836200" is_ac="false">If you've ever had those before.</p>
  <p time="837400" is_ac="false">I'm waiting for pie crust more.</p>
  <p time="838840" is_ac="false">I just can't not think about Nutter Butter
there with maybe a little hint of chocolate.</p>
  <p time="842200" is_ac="false">And only really at the end you start to get
some of that short, bready like flavor that</p>
  <p time="845680" is_ac="false">you might find in a pie crust.</p>
  <p time="846700" is_ac="false">So these are okay.</p>
  <p time="847780" is_ac="false">The idea is there, but the execution is not
fully there.</p>
  <p time="850600" is_ac="false">I have to say, I am very excited for these
Strawberry Frosted Donut Oreos.</p>
  <p time="854920" is_ac="false">And this right here is right up my alley
pink colored cream with glitter.</p>
  <p time="858790" is_ac="false">They put glitter inside their food and also
note that there is a double layer stack in</p>
  <p time="863620" is_ac="false">these ones. So these are double stuffed.</p>
  <p time="866230" is_ac="false">Now the smell is actually pretty great.</p>
  <p time="868450" is_ac="false">You get a little bit of that strawberry
flavor and it's very, very sweet and sugary.</p>
  <p time="872080" is_ac="false">I can already tell you right now that these
are going to be extraordinarily sweet, but</p>
  <p time="875650" is_ac="false">they actually look pretty good.</p>
  <p time="876730" is_ac="false">So let's give it a try.</p>
  <p time="879070" is_ac="false">Where's the glitter? I don't really like
these.</p>
  <p time="881200" is_ac="false">We got a few more Oreos, mint cream and
raspberry mousse.</p>
  <p time="883810" is_ac="false">I'm gonna give these a quick power try
because we want to get on to the next thing</p>
  <p time="886630" is_ac="false">here. First thing I'll immediately say is
that the packaging shows there will be this</p>
  <p time="889690" is_ac="false">pinkish filling inside these Oreos, but
that's really not, in fact, the case.</p>
  <p time="892630" is_ac="false">It's white. Does it taste like a raspberry
mousse?</p>
  <p time="894670" is_ac="false">Whoa. Wow.</p>
  <p time="896440" is_ac="false">These are cool.</p>
  <p time="897550" is_ac="false">Oreo, bring these to the US.</p>
  <p time="899800" is_ac="false">You see this video?</p>
  <p time="900970" is_ac="false">Bring that on over here.</p>
  <p time="902320" is_ac="false">Oh, no.</p>
  <p time="905130" is_ac="false">Isabelle: Wow. 
Nick: Isn't that</p>
  <p time="906330" is_ac="false">Cool?
Isabelle:
 Very interesting.</p>
  <p time="907950" is_ac="false">It's so thin. 
Nick: That's not...</p>
  <p time="910740" is_ac="false">It is. It's like half the size of another
Oreo.</p>
  <p time="912930" is_ac="false">But that is really good.</p>
  <p time="914250" is_ac="false">Nick:
She's missing the point.</p>
  <p time="915870" is_ac="false">Isabelle:
They're so good. Just like raspberry ice cream.</p>
  <p time="918240" is_ac="false">Nick:
Yeah, that's the point.</p>
  <p time="919650" is_ac="false">Isabelle:
Yeah, those are crazy.</p>
  <p time="920970" is_ac="false">Nick:
Next up we have pop tarts.</p>
  <p time="922170" is_ac="false">And I'm gonna be honest, I am not the
biggest Pop Tarts fan, but these just so</p>
  <p time="925470" is_ac="false">happen to be some extraordinarily rare
strawberry milkshake.</p>
  <p time="929190" is_ac="false">Shake that ass. Let's open these bad boys
up.</p>
  <p time="931680" is_ac="false">And wherever these are from, they've clearly
taken a long trip, so they're a little bit</p>
  <p time="934920" is_ac="false">mangled, but they're actually still kind of
intact.</p>
  <p time="936810" is_ac="false">At least enough. I'm gonna take a little
piece out.</p>
  <p time="938670" is_ac="false">They've got this nice little strawberry
milkshake filling, but let's give them a try.</p>
  <p time="943110" is_ac="false">Yeah. Actually tasted a little bit like a
strawberry milkshake.</p>
  <p time="945390" is_ac="false">And again, I'm not the biggest fan of Pop
Tarts, but these are pretty good.</p>
  <p time="948210" is_ac="false">All right. We're almost done with cookies
here.</p>
  <p time="949500" is_ac="false">But we got M&amp;Ms cookies.</p>
  <p time="951090" is_ac="false">And you imagine I mean, compared to
Skittles, I feel like M&amp;Ms has kind of a leg</p>
  <p time="954840" is_ac="false">up on cookies. Now, let's first say that
these are different.</p>
  <p time="957120" is_ac="false">These are chocolate based as opposed to the
vanilla ones that Skittles gave us, but it</p>
  <p time="960150" is_ac="false">just looks way more correct to have M&amp;Ms
inside a cookie instead of Skittles.</p>
  <p time="964740" is_ac="false">Look, we got the full color spectrum across
these.</p>
  <p time="966840" is_ac="false">They smell really chocolatey.</p>
  <p time="967920" is_ac="false">They look really interesting.</p>
  <p time="969270" is_ac="false">They taste pretty stale.</p>
  <p time="970290" is_ac="false">With that said though, I mean, sure, having
M&amp;Ms and cookies is fine.</p>
  <p time="973710" is_ac="false">And do I get that double chocolate flavor?</p>
  <p time="975540" is_ac="false">Absolutely. So I'm happy.</p>
  <p time="977370" is_ac="false">Now let's move on to the drink category of
things.</p>
  <p time="979830" is_ac="false">And I know this seems kind of crazy, but I
mean, can you not tell me that it's pretty</p>
  <p time="983100" is_ac="false">shocking. We have a literal Snickers drink,
i.e.</p>
  <p time="985950" is_ac="false">a drink that is supposed to taste like a
Snickers bar.</p>
  <p time="988530" is_ac="false">That's pretty cool. So which one do you want
to do first?</p>
  <p time="990660" is_ac="false">I wish you could shout out and tell me, but
unfortunately that's going to be difficult,</p>
  <p time="993480" is_ac="false">so I'm just gonna start with a Fanta.</p>
  <p time="995340" is_ac="false">Mango Fanta.</p>
  <p time="996420" is_ac="false">Funnily enough, Fanta used to be one of my
favorite drinks, especially as a kid.</p>
  <p time="1000140" is_ac="false">But never in my life did I think I was going
to taste mango Fanta.</p>
  <p time="1003410" is_ac="false">It's time to give this a little try.</p>
  <p time="1005000" is_ac="false">Cheers. It's pretty good.</p>
  <p time="1008510" is_ac="false">But the weird thing here is too much of that
artificial mango flavor, which kind of bums</p>
  <p time="1012500" is_ac="false">me out a little bit if I'm being perfectly
honest.</p>
  <p time="1014330" is_ac="false">I'm so spoiled right now with food, and I'm
so lucky to try so many amazing fresh</p>
  <p time="1017960" is_ac="false">ingredients all the time. And honestly, I
can't really be fooled by fake mango.</p>
  <p time="1021530" is_ac="false">So not a huge fan of this, but I like the
idea.</p>
  <p time="1023900" is_ac="false">Next we got a strawberry and kiwi Fanta
which this can has clearly been pretty beat</p>
  <p time="1028040" is_ac="false">up and I wonder where it came from.</p>
  <p time="1029420" is_ac="false">But let's give it a little shot into our
glass.</p>
  <p time="1031790" is_ac="false">We go with that beautiful pinkish color, and
then we look for that strawberry and kiwi</p>
  <p time="1035840" is_ac="false">flavor. Yeah it's there.</p>
  <p time="1038210" is_ac="false">It's not amazing. And it's not as much
strawberry kiwi flavor.</p>
  <p time="1040970" is_ac="false">So I'm kind of looking for but it's there.</p>
  <p time="1043130" is_ac="false">I'd love a little bit more of the Kiwi to be
totally honest, but I'd still rate this a</p>
  <p time="1046610" is_ac="false">little notch above the mango because it's
less artificial in that flavor.</p>
  <p time="1049580" is_ac="false">In here. Strawberry Fanta crack this baby
open and into our glass with that deep cherry</p>
  <p time="1054830" is_ac="false">red color we go.</p>
  <p time="1056000" is_ac="false">Now I have to say I am quite excited for
this one.</p>
  <p time="1059450" is_ac="false">Mhm mhm. The only fault in this strawberry
Fanta is they may have gone a little bit</p>
  <p time="1063200" is_ac="false">overboard with the sweetness and flavoring
there.</p>
  <p time="1065120" is_ac="false">But if I had to choose any of these, this
actually tastes a lot like strawberry.</p>
  <p time="1068390" is_ac="false">And it is really really good.</p>
  <p time="1070640" is_ac="false">This gets me just almost excited as those
raspberry mousse Oreos and of course the</p>
  <p time="1074270" is_ac="false">absolute wild card here, our dragon fruit
Fanta and perhaps some mango in the back</p>
  <p time="1079940" is_ac="false">there too. I will say the canned here is
really, really pretty with that pink and red.</p>
  <p time="1084440" is_ac="false">Just like what you'd see on a dragon fruit.</p>
  <p time="1086030" is_ac="false">And I like that they've mimicked the actual
fruit itself on the can.</p>
  <p time="1089150" is_ac="false">I'm curious to see what color this will be,
and it looks like we're getting that yellow</p>
  <p time="1092540" is_ac="false">color because there's some mango in here.</p>
  <p time="1094310" is_ac="false">Now, I know we got a big fat ice chunk, but
that's totally fine.</p>
  <p time="1097100" is_ac="false">It'll just be extra crisp and cold.</p>
  <p time="1098900" is_ac="false">Let's give it a try.</p>
  <p time="1101840" is_ac="false">I don't really know what we're looking for
here.</p>
  <p time="1103940" is_ac="false">Dragonfruit itself is kind of watery and
doesn't actually have that much flavor to me.</p>
  <p time="1107660" is_ac="false">So really, this this flavor here is more of
a dream.</p>
  <p time="1110120" is_ac="false">It's more of the the idea of trying to
believe that this can have this amazing mango</p>
  <p time="1113960" is_ac="false">and dragonfruit flavor in here.</p>
  <p time="1115250" is_ac="false">And honestly, it's not very good.</p>
  <p time="1117020" is_ac="false">So I'd go for the strawberry if I was gonna
try one of these rare sodas.</p>
  <p time="1120290" is_ac="false">So far, our last Fanta drink that we have
here is a white peach.</p>
  <p time="1123890" is_ac="false">Now the color very clearly artificial.</p>
  <p time="1126290" is_ac="false">I don't know how you'd get blue from a white
peach, but I guess it's kind of a cool color.</p>
  <p time="1129800" is_ac="false">It just doesn't help me get there to believe
that this is white peach.</p>
  <p time="1132530" is_ac="false">The shape of the bottle is pretty cool, and
I remember seeing this shape often when</p>
  <p time="1135470" is_ac="false">visiting China. The last thing I will say is
that it doesn't look that carbonated to me.</p>
  <p time="1139310" is_ac="false">There's no bubbles in here and it just
really doesn't seem like there's much</p>
  <p time="1141830" is_ac="false">carbonation. The smell, however, smells
exactly like a peach.</p>
  <p time="1146180" is_ac="false">The flavor is really good, and honestly, I
think having a bunch of more carbonation</p>
  <p time="1149900" is_ac="false">would help this a lot. But do I get peach?</p>
  <p time="1151760" is_ac="false">Absolutely. Is it pretty artificial?</p>
  <p time="1153860" is_ac="false">Absolutely. But do I love that flavor?</p>
  <p time="1155930" is_ac="false">Do I love peach?</p>
  <p time="1157010" is_ac="false">Yeah. So this is really, really interesting.</p>
  <p time="1159560" is_ac="false">It's a good drink now. Last but not least,
with our drinks we have Snickers and we have</p>
  <p time="1163040" is_ac="false">Mars. And theoretically these should both
taste like their respective bars that you</p>
  <p time="1166910" is_ac="false">could buy in any convenience store.</p>
  <p time="1168350" is_ac="false">I actually really want to start with the
Snickers.</p>
  <p time="1170210" is_ac="false">It's got one of those classic little lids
that you'd find on the end of a water bottle.</p>
  <p time="1173570" is_ac="false">It says to shake it well, so let's shake it
up, shake it up, shake it up.</p>
  <p time="1177380" is_ac="false">Turn the camera off for a second.</p>
  <p time="1179390" is_ac="false">Do you remember the shake weight when it was
like.</p>
  <p time="1182970" is_ac="false">Let's give the stickers. Drink a try.</p>
  <p time="1184500" is_ac="false">I don't really know what to say.</p>
  <p time="1186450" is_ac="false">Nothing came out. Ah, yes.</p>
  <p time="1188100" is_ac="false">Classic Snickers.</p>
  <p time="1189120" is_ac="false">Drink. Take two. Action.</p>
  <p time="1192180" is_ac="false">Weird. Picture this.</p>
  <p time="1193590" is_ac="false">You go to the store, you buy ten Snickers
bars, you bring them home, you stick them in</p>
  <p time="1197370" is_ac="false">your blender and you blend them up with a
little bit of milk and water.</p>
  <p time="1200040" is_ac="false">That's exactly what I just tasted.</p>
  <p time="1201720" is_ac="false">I get that peanut flavor, I get that
chocolate flavor.</p>
  <p time="1204210" is_ac="false">I get that nougat flavor in a Snickers bar.</p>
  <p time="1206190" is_ac="false">Everything's there and it's a Snickers bar
to drink.</p>
  <p time="1208950" is_ac="false">That's what it is. Cool.</p>
  <p time="1210240" is_ac="false">Now, before I try this Mars here, I should
mention that my friend at Rare Munchies</p>
  <p time="1213360" is_ac="false">helped me find them because, again, these
are not the easiest things in the world to</p>
  <p time="1216150" is_ac="false">find. If you go on his or other people's
websites, you'll see that pretty much</p>
  <p time="1219120" is_ac="false">everything is always sold out because these
are so hard to get.</p>
  <p time="1221790" is_ac="false">And when I say these, I mean all of the
stuff that we're trying today.</p>
  <p time="1224370" is_ac="false">But again, I just want to thank him for
helping out because it is hard to track this</p>
  <p time="1227700" is_ac="false">many rare snacks down.</p>
  <p time="1228990" is_ac="false">Now let's try the Mars bar.</p>
  <p time="1231090" is_ac="false">Wait, I didn't really remember what a mars
bar has in it.</p>
  <p time="1234180" is_ac="false">A mars bar is a candy bar with nougat and
toasted almonds covered with milk chocolate.</p>
  <p time="1238410" is_ac="false">So that's what we should taste here.</p>
  <p time="1240210" is_ac="false">That just tastes like chocolate milk.</p>
  <p time="1241650" is_ac="false">The Snickers team did it right, but I was
about to say the Mars team didn't.</p>
  <p time="1244680" is_ac="false">But when I look in the bottom, both of these
are owned by the company Mars.</p>
  <p time="1247770" is_ac="false">So somehow they nailed the Snickers drink.</p>
  <p time="1249390" is_ac="false">But the Mars drink just literally tastes
like a plain old chocolate milk.</p>
  <p time="1252630" is_ac="false">Next up, we got our candies and I want to
start out with these white chocolate M&amp;Ms</p>
  <p time="1256350" is_ac="false">because frankly, they look very, very
interesting.</p>
  <p time="1259440" is_ac="false">Let's make a little tear in the corner and
dump out a few into my hand.</p>
  <p time="1262530" is_ac="false">Now, at first glance, these look just like
regular old M&amp;Ms.</p>
  <p time="1265560" is_ac="false">I mean, nothing different about these,
right?</p>
  <p time="1267240" is_ac="false">But let's take a bite.</p>
  <p time="1269280" is_ac="false">Whoa. That's cool.</p>
  <p time="1271350" is_ac="false">Just inside you have white chocolate.</p>
  <p time="1273720" is_ac="false">And that is so weird.</p>
  <p time="1275430" is_ac="false">I don't know what's so strange about that to
me, but the fact that these are white</p>
  <p time="1278250" is_ac="false">chocolate is kind of crazy.</p>
  <p time="1279930" is_ac="false">Look at that. When I chop these in half,
M&amp;Ms are supposed to have chocolate inside.</p>
  <p time="1283680" is_ac="false">What is this? That's pretty cool.</p>
  <p time="1285480" is_ac="false">That's what it is. Fun little fact.</p>
  <p time="1286920" is_ac="false">While we're on the topic, white chocolate is
just the cocoa butter.</p>
  <p time="1289620" is_ac="false">So when you get cacao, you get the cocoa
nibs, and then you get cocoa butter that's</p>
  <p time="1292950" is_ac="false">pressed out of it. And all this is, is just
cocoa butter with some sugar in there.</p>
  <p time="1295890" is_ac="false">Cool little factoid for the day.</p>
  <p time="1297330" is_ac="false">Next up we have a sprinkles and cream
Hershey's bar.</p>
  <p time="1299640" is_ac="false">I mean, that alone is insane.</p>
  <p time="1301230" is_ac="false">This is a birthday cake.</p>
  <p time="1302490" is_ac="false">Hershey's bar. I will say that the second I
opened this thing, it just smells like a</p>
  <p time="1306180" is_ac="false">birthday cake. You can see all the sprinkles
through the bar and it actually looks so, so</p>
  <p time="1310500" is_ac="false">cool. I like how it's divided into these
kind of triangles, so I might as well cut it</p>
  <p time="1314400" is_ac="false">the way that it's asking me to cut it.</p>
  <p time="1315960" is_ac="false">Let's take out one of these little slices
and give it a try.</p>
  <p time="1319380" is_ac="false">Oh, that's so cool.</p>
  <p time="1321150" is_ac="false">The sprinkles actually give texture.</p>
  <p time="1322980" is_ac="false">So again, while I don't love white
chocolate, it's actually a really, really</p>
  <p time="1326280" is_ac="false">interesting Hershey's bar.</p>
  <p time="1327360" is_ac="false">Not the best thing I've ever tasted, but
certainly not the worst.</p>
  <p time="1330180" is_ac="false">Next up, Reese's peanut butter lovers.</p>
  <p time="1332550" is_ac="false">Now, I know this may not look rare, but you
probably never seen peanut butter lovers in</p>
  <p time="1336630" is_ac="false">the store. Let's see what the middle of this
thing looks like.</p>
  <p time="1338790" is_ac="false">Because I'm very, very curious.</p>
  <p time="1340680" is_ac="false">It looks really pretty much like nothing in
there.</p>
  <p time="1343350" is_ac="false">Although if you do look more carefully,
there's this layer of chocolate at the</p>
  <p time="1346080" is_ac="false">bottom. Well, I love peanut butter, so let's
see if I'm satisfied.</p>
  <p time="1349800" is_ac="false">It's like a super charged Reese's.</p>
  <p time="1351660" is_ac="false">So if you already like the peanut butter
aspect of Reese's, this pretty much doubles</p>
  <p time="1355710" is_ac="false">it up. It's more powerful peanut flavor.</p>
  <p time="1357690" is_ac="false">There's more of that peanut butter chewiness
overall, and it really does double down on</p>
  <p time="1361530" is_ac="false">the peanut butter. Next we have a mars bar
caramel sundae.</p>
  <p time="1364410" is_ac="false">The whole thing is kind of smashed.</p>
  <p time="1365730" is_ac="false">And quite honestly, it's gonna be difficult
for me to even eat this.</p>
  <p time="1368460" is_ac="false">Let me just take a little bite out of the
end.</p>
  <p time="1371490" is_ac="false">It says vanilla ice cream flavored nugget
with a cooling sensation.</p>
  <p time="1375120" is_ac="false">My mouth has been again extremely
unexpectedly blasted with with menthol.</p>
  <p time="1379950" is_ac="false">So awesome.</p>
  <p time="1381030" is_ac="false">Why would you do that?</p>
  <p time="1382200" is_ac="false">Next up we got Kit Kat Gold.</p>
  <p time="1384450" is_ac="false">Let's chop off the top and slide out a few
of those Kit Kat bars.</p>
  <p time="1387540" is_ac="false">Now, I would have liked if the gold was a
little bit more metallic type gold, because</p>
  <p time="1391260" is_ac="false">that would have been pretty badass.</p>
  <p time="1392550" is_ac="false">And quite honestly, my mouth is still
destroyed from the cooling Mars bar.</p>
  <p time="1395760" is_ac="false">I don't understand why you'd put that in a
candy bar.</p>
  <p time="1397680" is_ac="false">That's all right. Let's give this Kit Kat a
try.</p>
  <p time="1399750" is_ac="false">This is just that caramel white chocolate on
the outside.</p>
  <p time="1402510" is_ac="false">And again, not a big fan of white chocolate,
so I don't love it.</p>
  <p time="1404910" is_ac="false">But it's kind of cool seeing a bar that we
all kind of know being turned to gold.</p>
  <p time="1407850" is_ac="false">The bar that I am most excited for today is
this Kit Kat popcorn flavored bar.</p>
  <p time="1413310" is_ac="false">I mean, come on, that's pretty cool.</p>
  <p time="1414870" is_ac="false">Let me chop off one of these chunks of the
Kit Kat and show you the inside here, which</p>
  <p time="1418380" is_ac="false">actually looks quite appetizing.</p>
  <p time="1419910" is_ac="false">If you look carefully, you can see that
they've literally put real pieces of popcorn</p>
  <p time="1423900" is_ac="false">in the top of this Kit Kat.</p>
  <p time="1425010" is_ac="false">The real question is, will I get that popcorn
flavor?</p>
  <p time="1429890" is_ac="false">That is good.</p>
  <p time="1431390" is_ac="false">Yeah, I do get the popcorn flavor that makes
me happy.</p>
  <p time="1434060" is_ac="false">It's the same milk chocolatey goodness that
you get on the outside of the Kit Kat bar.</p>
  <p time="1437900" is_ac="false">But then right there, when you bite down,
you get that crunchy pop that you get.</p>
  <p time="1441080" is_ac="false">If you were eating a crispy piece of
popcorn, and then you really do get that</p>
  <p time="1444350" is_ac="false">popcorn flavor. Good creativity.</p>
  <p time="1445970" is_ac="false">Kit Kat I like it. Last but not least, we
have a Kit Kat Caramel Crisp.</p>
  <p time="1449720" is_ac="false">Of all the bars that I got, this looks like
it's in the best shape, so maybe it didn't</p>
  <p time="1452870" is_ac="false">come from all that far away.</p>
  <p time="1454130" is_ac="false">I really like the matte finishing on the
packaging here, because it just kind of</p>
  <p time="1457190" is_ac="false">brings everything a little bit up in
quality.</p>
  <p time="1459140" is_ac="false">It feels a lot fancier.</p>
  <p time="1460400" is_ac="false">Let's listen for that snap.</p>
  <p time="1462440" is_ac="false">That was a little bit underwhelming, but it
was there.</p>
  <p time="1465380" is_ac="false">Oh wow.</p>
  <p time="1466760" is_ac="false">Two bangers in a row.</p>
  <p time="1468350" is_ac="false">So literally you're getting these crunchy
pieces of butterscotch in there that totally</p>
  <p time="1472010" is_ac="false">change up the texture of the KitKat yet
again.</p>
  <p time="1473930" is_ac="false">You still have that kind of dense milk
chocolate on the top and bottom, but then</p>
  <p time="1476690" is_ac="false">that middle layer is that light, fluffy
KitKat all spotted with these really, really</p>
  <p time="1480950" is_ac="false">crunchy and crispy pieces of hard caramel.</p>
  <p time="1483320" is_ac="false">That's really, really, really good.</p>
  <p time="1485150" is_ac="false">We have made it to that time that I've been
waiting for to make this Cheetos, mac and</p>
  <p time="1488690" is_ac="false">cheese. I got my boiling water and before I
do anything, I'm gonna salt it like the</p>
  <p time="1492530" is_ac="false">ocean. They're not going to be telling you
that on the Cheetos box, but that's what I'm</p>
  <p time="1495440" is_ac="false">here for. You got to season our food
properly.</p>
  <p time="1497210" is_ac="false">Still, even if we're making Cheetos, mac and
cheese now, I'll rip open this box.</p>
  <p time="1501170" is_ac="false">And it looks to me as if they've picked out
Rotini, which is a great, great, great shape.</p>
  <p time="1505250" is_ac="false">All we have in here is one seasoning packet
and our pasta, which I'll now pour right into</p>
  <p time="1509180" is_ac="false">this boiling water. Now I might as well
follow the directions.</p>
  <p time="1512330" is_ac="false">So it looks like we're gonna cook this for
about seven minutes or so.</p>
  <p time="1514940" is_ac="false">Then add a little bit of butter at the end,
as well as a little bit of milk.</p>
  <p time="1517670" is_ac="false">I have a feeling this is actually going to
be pretty good.</p>
  <p time="1519620" is_ac="false">It is now time to drain our pasta and for
that we of course need a strainer.</p>
  <p time="1523100" is_ac="false">Now we are of course going to be applying
some high level cooking techniques.</p>
  <p time="1526160" is_ac="false">So as you can see, we've saved a little bit
of pasta water in our pan for all that</p>
  <p time="1529550" is_ac="false">flavor. Even though we're making Cheetos mac
and cheese, we need to be cooking smart.</p>
  <p time="1532940" is_ac="false">Now, the Cheetos box says to put in two
tablespoons of butter, which I'll add to that</p>
  <p time="1536450" is_ac="false">pasta water to emulsify into a beautiful
thickened sauce that will be used as the base</p>
  <p time="1540440" is_ac="false">of our cheese sauce. Then I'll added about a
quarter cup of milk, which they've also told</p>
  <p time="1544430" is_ac="false">us to add. And then, of course, our neon
orange Cheetos cheese, which quite honestly</p>
  <p time="1549050" is_ac="false">is a little bit scary.</p>
  <p time="1550160" is_ac="false">I mean, that is just plain wrong.</p>
  <p time="1552200" is_ac="false">The steam coming off of this literally
smells exactly like Cheetos, but I'm having a</p>
  <p time="1556430" is_ac="false">tough time getting over the color.</p>
  <p time="1557870" is_ac="false">Either way, once it's in a beautifully
thickened sauce and it's all emulsified, I'm</p>
  <p time="1561620" is_ac="false">gonna turn off the heat and drop in my
pasta.</p>
  <p time="1563810" is_ac="false">Then I'll slowly fold this all together to
evenly coat my rotini.</p>
  <p time="1566930" is_ac="false">And we've officially made it Cheetos, mac
and cheese.</p>
  <p time="1569660" is_ac="false">Let's add a little bit to our bowl and enjoy
this amazing mac and cheese that we've worked</p>
  <p time="1573440" is_ac="false">so incredibly hard to make.</p>
  <p time="1577760" is_ac="false">Tastes exactly like cheese balls.</p>
  <p time="1579500" is_ac="false">And I love cheese balls.</p>
  <p time="1581480" is_ac="false">I know I'm supposed to be some sort of chef,
and I know I'm supposed to appreciate high</p>
  <p time="1584750" is_ac="false">end food, but I sit in bed every night.</p>
  <p time="1586790" is_ac="false">I'm not kidding. And I eat cheese balls.</p>
  <p time="1588620" is_ac="false">I don't really know why, but they're my
guilty pleasure.</p>
  <p time="1590780" is_ac="false">And they look just like this pasta.</p>
  <p time="1592610" is_ac="false">They're fantastic.</p>
  <p time="1596270" is_ac="false">Last but not least, we have our sweets to
finish all of this on a sweet note right here</p>
  <p time="1600590" is_ac="false">I got Chupa Chups bubble gum.</p>
  <p time="1602330" is_ac="false">Normally, you've probably only ever seen
these little lollipops made by this company,</p>
  <p time="1605840" is_ac="false">but today we have kola lemon flavor.</p>
  <p time="1608060" is_ac="false">Now it's a little weird that we're going to
be tasting gum, but honestly, this just looks</p>
  <p time="1611360" is_ac="false">so unique to me that I had to try it.</p>
  <p time="1613250" is_ac="false">And the idea of mixing lemon and kola is so,
so interesting.</p>
  <p time="1617870" is_ac="false">That is weird, very artificial and very
tough to chew.</p>
  <p time="1621410" is_ac="false">A little stale but horrible.</p>
  <p time="1623210" is_ac="false">Next, Mike and Ikes cotton candy.</p>
  <p time="1625160" is_ac="false">I'd heard the rumor a while back that Mike
and Ike split up.</p>
  <p time="1627530" is_ac="false">I feel like everyone heard that rumor, but
this makes it seem like they're back</p>
  <p time="1630200" is_ac="false">together. And of course, with cotton candy,
we have our pink and we have our blue.</p>
  <p time="1633110" is_ac="false">So naturally, I'm gonna try them together.</p>
  <p time="1635720" is_ac="false">Uh huh. Wow, these are really good.</p>
  <p time="1637910" is_ac="false">And apparently it's really difficult to find
and only available for a limited time.</p>
  <p time="1641660" is_ac="false">At least that's what the back of the
packaging says.</p>
  <p time="1643370" is_ac="false">But these do taste like cotton candy, and
they remind you of being at the fair.</p>
  <p time="1646340" is_ac="false">But speaking of cotton candy, I have a
really interesting snack I want to try next.</p>
  <p time="1649640" is_ac="false">Doctor pepper. Cotton candy.</p>
  <p time="1651350" is_ac="false">That's crazy. Let's just rip off a nice big
hunk of this.</p>
  <p time="1654140" is_ac="false">Now, this certainly looks like the
insulation that you put in your house.</p>
  <p time="1657080" is_ac="false">What are you laughing about? You fired.</p>
  <p time="1658280" is_ac="false">What are you doing? And it's just.</p>
  <p time="1659390" is_ac="false">Overall looks kind of weird to me, but let's
give it a try.</p>
  <p time="1663920" is_ac="false">Wow. I've always been a fan of doctor Pepper
and that is a treat.</p>
  <p time="1667250" is_ac="false">I cannot tell you how excited I am to try
these churro Cheetos, and we can only hope</p>
  <p time="1671930" is_ac="false">that these are gonna be at least a tad bit
better than the Cheetos pasta we just made.</p>
  <p time="1675500" is_ac="false">Well, let's see what these bad boys look
like.</p>
  <p time="1677150" is_ac="false">So funnily enough, when I saw this on the
packaging, I was expecting them to look like</p>
  <p time="1680570" is_ac="false">this. But then you look over here and you
see what they really are supposed to look</p>
  <p time="1683900" is_ac="false">like, something that comes out of your dog.</p>
  <p time="1687090" is_ac="false">They smell like churros, but they taste like
churros, too.</p>
  <p time="1691260" is_ac="false">Those are cool.</p>
  <p time="1692340" is_ac="false">In fact, I'm gonna go so far as to say that
I like these a heck of a lot better than</p>
  <p time="1696270" is_ac="false">regular Cheetos. I don't know who on the
Cheetos team thought of this.</p>
  <p time="1698880" is_ac="false">Number one, though. You nailed the idea and
number two, you executed perfectly.</p>
  <p time="1702750" is_ac="false">These are fantastic.</p>
  <p time="1704160" is_ac="false">Little bit of cinnamon. It's got that
fattiness that coats your mouth when you do</p>
  <p time="1707130" is_ac="false">bite into a churro. That amazing buttery
flavor.</p>
  <p time="1709470" is_ac="false">Yet deep, deep down you still have that
corny flavor of a Cheeto.</p>
  <p time="1712770" is_ac="false">Next up, we have what looks to be a caramel
and white chocolate Twix bar, which again, is</p>
  <p time="1716550" is_ac="false">super, super interesting because you break
open a Twix bar thinking it's gonna be</p>
  <p time="1719700" is_ac="false">chocolate, but no, suddenly it's white
chocolate.</p>
  <p time="1723390" is_ac="false">Unless you like white chocolate.</p>
  <p time="1724620" is_ac="false">No birthday cake.</p>
  <p time="1725880" is_ac="false">Rice Krispie treat. I'm hopeful that this
thing will be covered in sprinkles.</p>
  <p time="1729150" is_ac="false">It turns out they read my mind.</p>
  <p time="1732120" is_ac="false">This is quite literally the most regular
Rice Krispie treat possible, just with a few</p>
  <p time="1735930" is_ac="false">sprinkles on top. Now we have Haribo
milkshakes and squid squids.</p>
  <p time="1741750" is_ac="false">Let's. Oh wait, wait, sorry.</p>
  <p time="1743340" is_ac="false">They explained it on the packaging.</p>
  <p time="1744750" is_ac="false">It's a soft mix of squid.</p>
  <p time="1746190" is_ac="false">That's what they. That's the explanation for
what these things are.</p>
  <p time="1748740" is_ac="false">So that makes sense. And then in the back it
says we are the squidgy squad.</p>
  <p time="1751620" is_ac="false">So they really do a good job kind of telling
you and filling you in.</p>
  <p time="1754170" is_ac="false">Let's try. Oh okay.</p>
  <p time="1757320" is_ac="false">My best description of these these tastes
just as weird as the packaging might suggest.</p>
  <p time="1761640" is_ac="false">I really don't know how to describe these.</p>
  <p time="1763020" is_ac="false">I'm sorry. It's pillowy.</p>
  <p time="1764160" is_ac="false">It's almost like marshmallowy.</p>
  <p time="1765330" is_ac="false">It's almost like a hybrid between a fruit
snack and a marshmallow.</p>
  <p time="1767700" is_ac="false">Now, we can only hope that these milkshakes
are actually gonna taste like milkshake.</p>
  <p time="1770880" is_ac="false">Well, let's give them a try.</p>
  <p time="1772110" is_ac="false">Now, these are good. They have that same
consistency as the squid.</p>
  <p time="1775170" is_ac="false">It's almost a little bit chewier.</p>
  <p time="1776670" is_ac="false">They actually really do have that creamy,
milkshake y flavor, which I really, really</p>
  <p time="1780360" is_ac="false">like. This is the homestretch.</p>
  <p time="1781530" is_ac="false">We are almost there. But we have
Butterfinger popcorn now.</p>
  <p time="1784230" is_ac="false">Some of you might not be a big fan of
Butterfinger, so you're probably sighing and</p>
  <p time="1786960" is_ac="false">waiting for the next thing at this point.</p>
  <p time="1788370" is_ac="false">I, on the other hand, happen to love
Butterfinger, so it is my hope that this is</p>
  <p time="1791940" is_ac="false">basically if you melted a bunch of
butterfingers over some popcorn.</p>
  <p time="1795090" is_ac="false">And honestly, that's kind of what it looks
like.</p>
  <p time="1798330" is_ac="false">This is actually underrated.</p>
  <p time="1799680" is_ac="false">Really good. And I'll be honest, if it was
at my store up the road, I probably wouldn't</p>
  <p time="1802740" is_ac="false">buy it that often. But if I ever really had
a sweet tooth that night, this would be one</p>
  <p time="1806100" is_ac="false">of the first things that I would grab off
the shelf, because it's exactly pretty much</p>
  <p time="1809280" is_ac="false">what it says, crumbled and melted a bunch of
butterfingers over a bunch of fresh popcorn.</p>
  <p time="1813120" is_ac="false">These are our last few candies, and I
figured we'd do it all in one little bunch</p>
  <p time="1816000" is_ac="false">because we're getting to the end, and we've
tried so many things.</p>
  <p time="1818310" is_ac="false">And quite honestly, I am getting extremely,
extremely full.</p>
  <p time="1821220" is_ac="false">I've eaten so much sugar and I've had a lot
of fun trying all these things.</p>
  <p time="1824070" is_ac="false">But it's not easy trying this many things in
one sitting.</p>
  <p time="1826380" is_ac="false">The thing that I do want to try and then I
will happily dive into immediately are these</p>
  <p time="1830070" is_ac="false">Sour patch mangoes.</p>
  <p time="1831120" is_ac="false">I wish they made them look a little bit more
like actual mangoes, but damn do they taste</p>
  <p time="1835920" is_ac="false">good. It says sour than sweet on the
packaging, and you absolutely get that blast</p>
  <p time="1839700" is_ac="false">of sourness, that citric acid right as you
bite into it.</p>
  <p time="1842250" is_ac="false">But then the finish is this really good,
mangoei, sweet, delicious, lasting flavor at</p>
  <p time="1846570" is_ac="false">the end. So honestly, I love it here.</p>
  <p time="1849000" is_ac="false">I have chocolate caramel mentos, but I'm
really excited about are these root beer</p>
  <p time="1852750" is_ac="false">float mechanics, which I'm gonna finish
everything off for you.</p>
  <p time="1855360" is_ac="false">The thing about all these rare snacks is
that so many of them have these really</p>
  <p time="1857820" is_ac="false">unique, interesting names.</p>
  <p time="1859050" is_ac="false">And for me, what's fun is trying to figure
out, do they actually taste like that?</p>
  <p time="1862740" is_ac="false">Now, right off the bat, with these root beer
float things, I totally get the root beer.</p>
  <p time="1865800" is_ac="false">In fact, it'd be almost impossible for them
to mess that up.</p>
  <p time="1868140" is_ac="false">The part I unfortunately don't get is the
float.</p>
  <p time="1870060" is_ac="false">A root beer float has a bunch of root beer
with a big hunk of vanilla ice cream in</p>
  <p time="1873570" is_ac="false">there, so for me, they need to put more
vanilla in this to make me believe.</p>
  <p time="1877050" is_ac="false">All right. It's been so amazing tasting, all
of those incredible, incredible snacks.</p>
  <p time="1881310" is_ac="false">And I really mean it when I tell you that.</p>
  <p time="1882660" is_ac="false">I tried extremely hard to source those
things from all over the place, it was</p>
  <p time="1886380" is_ac="false">seriously difficult. And I wanted to shoot
this video about a month and a half ago, but</p>
  <p time="1889650" is_ac="false">we had to wait for things to keep coming in.</p>
  <p time="1891630" is_ac="false">I just had this box in my room piled up with
all these unique, amazing things, and I was</p>
  <p time="1895440" is_ac="false">protecting them because I was so excited
about trying them with you.</p>
  <p time="1898590" is_ac="false">Now, as promised, I want to tell you the
winner for the giveaway to the three Michelin</p>
  <p time="1901920" is_ac="false">star dinner. Now, this creme brulée video
was really, really fun to make.</p>
  <p time="1905670" is_ac="false">And like I mentioned, we got nearly 7000
comments on this video right here.</p>
  <p time="1909750" is_ac="false">And I get it. A lot of people want to go to
a three Michelin star meal, but for me, it</p>
  <p time="1913380" is_ac="false">was really fun hearing all of your stories.</p>
  <p time="1915480" is_ac="false">Now, like I said, we're going to pick a
winner to go to a three Michelin starred</p>
  <p time="1918690" is_ac="false">meal, plus a guess, which is extremely
exciting.</p>
  <p time="1921150" is_ac="false">So I look through all of these comments, and
one that stood out to me was from Nathan</p>
  <p time="1925050" is_ac="false">O. Nathan's dad is almost 50 years old now
and had a heart operation about a year ago.</p>
  <p time="1929250" is_ac="false">Nathan, it sounds like you have an
absolutely incredible father and as you've</p>
  <p time="1932520" is_ac="false">written here, you're super interested in the
food industry and food world itself.</p>
  <p time="1935700" is_ac="false">Now, I know you're in the Netherlands and
I'm not sure how to pronounce the restaurant</p>
  <p time="1938640" is_ac="false">you picked out. Liberica, but let me say
this.</p>
  <p time="1941010" is_ac="false">I want you to take your dad there and send
me a clip of your experience.</p>
  <p time="1944010" is_ac="false">I'm super, super excited for you.</p>
  <p time="1945810" is_ac="false">But for everyone else, hold up just a
second.</p>
  <p time="1947610" is_ac="false">Nathan had a fantastic story, as did so many
people, so I couldn't pick just one winner.</p>
  <p time="1951840" is_ac="false">And that's why I want to give away a second
three Michelin star dinner.</p>
  <p time="1954570" is_ac="false">So as I was scrolling, I also saw a comment
from Super Meow.</p>
  <p time="1957810" is_ac="false">She's always dreamt of taking her mom to 11
Madison Park in New York City.</p>
  <p time="1961500" is_ac="false">Evidently, her mom named her Madison because
of Madison Avenue, and I've already reached</p>
  <p time="1965460" is_ac="false">out to Madison as well and let her know that
she's won this.</p>
  <p time="1967620" is_ac="false">And she and her mom are super, super
excited.</p>
  <p time="1969840" is_ac="false">So, Madison, just like Nathan, I want you to
send a clip or two and share your experience</p>
  <p time="1973110" is_ac="false">so that I can show everyone else on the
channel how you guys like those meals.</p>
  <p time="1976050" is_ac="false">And I'm so, so excited for you.</p>
  <p time="1978060" is_ac="false">Congratulations to our not one, but two
winners.</p>
  <p time="1981480" is_ac="false">I've read all of your stories, I've read all
those comments, and honestly, I was just</p>
  <p time="1984840" is_ac="false">really excited about both of these.</p>
  <p time="1986340" is_ac="false">Not to mention about many of your stories and your
willingness to go try such amazing food</p>
  <p time="1990410" is_ac="false">somewhere. Now again, I want to do giveaways
like this more down the road, and this one's</p>
  <p time="1993620" is_ac="false">really special to me because I feel like I'm
giving away an experience that's going to be</p>
  <p time="1996620" is_ac="false">so transformative for these people that are
going to those of you that won,</p>
  <p time="1999470" is_ac="false">congratulations. And to all of you that just
watched this video, make sure you smack that</p>
  <p time="2003130" is_ac="false">subscribe button because you don't want to
miss any videos or any giveaways for that</p>
  <p time="2006250" is_ac="false">matter down the road. Please, please, please
also toss the video like that just helps so</p>
  <p time="2010750" is_ac="false">much to get these videos to keep going the
way that they are.</p>
  <p time="2012910" is_ac="false">And I work so incredibly hard to get as many
videos as I do.</p>
  <p time="2015730" is_ac="false">Out to all of you each and every week.</p>
  <p time="2017530" is_ac="false">And all I ask of your support is that you
like the video again.</p>
  <p time="2020200" is_ac="false">All of these snacks were so much fun to try.</p>
  <p time="2022030" is_ac="false">Maybe I'll do another one with different
snacks next time because I know there's more</p>
  <p time="2024820" is_ac="false">out there. I just need to find them.</p>
  <p time="2026080" is_ac="false">Till then. Thank you for watching.</p>
  <p time="2027490" is_ac="false">I'll see you soon.</p>
</text>
