<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="The Italian Diaries" date="20220306" date_ts="1646566933" views="422950" title="Why You should not come Italy to Study| Study abroad in English" likes="5393" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="0" is_ac="false">Don't come to Italy </p>
  <p time="1834" is_ac="false">Hey guys, welcome to your channel "Travel with Megh". It's been a long long day</p>
  <p time="6477" is_ac="false">since I've made a video, I was busy with my exams </p>
  <p time="9102" is_ac="false">But I'm quite active on Instagram so if you want to know about University applications, deadlines, scholarships then</p>
  <p time="16597" is_ac="false">please follow me on my Instagram "TravelWithMegh". Now in today's topic I'm going to tell you</p>
  <p time="21550" is_ac="false">about "Don't Come To Italy", why don't come to Italy ?, you will come to know after this video ends</p>
  <p time="29119" is_ac="false">Many of you just decide, that you've to go to some foreign country and you have to start studying okay but then </p>
  <p time="35589" is_ac="false">when you come here and when you face the reality like I've faced and many other students,which I'm seeing that they have faced</p>
  <p time="41964" is_ac="false">the reality is very different, to be honest okay so now their should be someone who should convey the reality, right</p>
  <p time="50031" is_ac="false">and not in terms of tuition fee, scholarships, affordable and no racist but something which is more important</p>
  <p time="57125" is_ac="false">to students for their future and for their career, okay</p>
  <p time="59468" is_ac="false">My first point is, if you have a short term goal of earning money then Italy is not a place for you</p>
  <p time="68068" is_ac="false">don't come to Italy, you're not to make huge amount of money staying in Italy, as a student</p>
  <p time="73892" is_ac="false">I can explain you this by giving you an example of a student A and B, so student A</p>
  <p time="79075" is_ac="false">came in Italy and he has a purpose of earning money and student B has a purpose of finishing his/her degree</p>
  <p time="85318" is_ac="false">and moving on his/her career path, Okay. So they came for 2 years Master's degree program</p>
  <p time="90146" is_ac="false">after 2 years, the student A has savings, a lot of savings in his hand</p>
  <p time="96105" is_ac="false">student B doesn't have a lot of savings on his hand but he has survived for 2 years on the base of the scholarship that he has gotten</p>
  <p time="103382" is_ac="false">and how he got the scholarship ? because he was continuously giving the exam, upgrading his skills, he was doing actively the projects</p>
  <p time="109713" is_ac="false">given in the universities and after 2 years now, he is in that phase where he can apply in companies, and any other organizations </p>
  <p time="118382" is_ac="false">and he can start his career, Okay. and he is going to land on a good package but</p>
  <p time="124097" is_ac="false">student A, what's happening to student A ?. 2 years has finished, he has no degree in his hand, he just have money</p>
  <p time="130380" is_ac="false">and how many days can he survive on that amount of money, so he has no career plan, nothing.</p>
  <p time="134548" is_ac="false">Now you will say it's better right because everybody needs money, I can understand but what is A doing, A is doing a part time job</p>
  <p time="140394" is_ac="false">he's doing delivery job, he's sometimes working also in restaurants as a waiter/ waitress, Okay</p>
  <p time="144799" is_ac="false">but after 2 years what ?. He can not continue doing this, right</p>
  <p time="147835" is_ac="false">So just imagine, you were doing engineering in India or Pakistan or wherever country you were</p>
  <p time="154272" is_ac="false">and now here, you've money, you're doing just part-time jobs, you're working as a waiter/waitress in a restaurant or you're doing delivery job</p>
  <p time="160753" is_ac="false">but where is the future growth ?, what are you going to do in the next 3, 4, or 5 years ?</p>
  <p time="165686" is_ac="false">So now it depends upon you, which student you want to be. If you are a type of student A then don't come to Italy</p>
  <p time="172457" is_ac="false">this is not a place for you, but if you're a type of student B then you are welcome here in Italy, okay.</p>
  <p time="177320" is_ac="false">Now again from the money perspective also, if you're thinking that coming to Italy, you're going to earn whole lot of money then that's not true</p>
  <p time="184934" is_ac="false">because what a student earns is minimum 5 euro per hour, and due to not many people speak here English, </p>
  <p time="192076" is_ac="false">you don't have much English speaking opportunities so you need to learn Italian, and without Italian you're not going to survive</p>
  <p time="198710" is_ac="false">for a long period of time, okay. Now another reason I'm telling you, to not come to Italy</p>
  <p time="203896" is_ac="false">if you're a type of student who are afraid of studying, okay because in Italy</p>
  <p time="209012" is_ac="false">study is difficult, believe me it's not easy for you to study to bring marks</p>
  <p time="214455" is_ac="false">and to get passed basically, because here the study is totally conceptual base</p>
  <p time="218837" is_ac="false">that if you're studying a subject, the concept should be clear, okay. So mugging up the subject</p>
  <p time="225108" is_ac="false">the one who is very good in mugging up and remembering the definitions, types, won't work</p>
  <p time="231263" is_ac="false">even if I compare the quality of education of Italy, with US and UK. The pattern of study that they have is totally different from what we have in Italy</p>
  <p time="238722" is_ac="false">although the study will be very difficult, but still the student don't have pressure in their mind because </p>
  <p time="245037" is_ac="false">even though you've not passed the exam this time, you will get many number of opportunities to pass the same exam again and again</p>
  <p time="251480" is_ac="false">until and unless you are satisfied with that marks, okay. So this is again a very good benefit in comparison to what other countries are offering</p>
  <p time="260735" is_ac="false">If you just want to come abroad, you're feeling that Italy will be easier for you to come, they have low tuition fee</p>
  <p time="268054" is_ac="false">so please don't come here</p>
  <p time="268924" is_ac="false">you will be wasting your 2 years or 3 years or 4 years of education </p>
  <p time="274313" is_ac="false">I hope this explanation is clear for you now and I hope now you will be able to decide if you should come to Italy or not</p>
  <p time="282483" is_ac="false">because judging only on the purpose of tuition fee, affordability, accommodation is not quite enough as a student</p>
  <p time="289789" is_ac="false">You've to see a future, you know. Your career growth and if it's not there then its baseless</p>
  <p time="296647" is_ac="false">then you can be in your home country only, and you can start some business or whatever you want to do, right</p>
  <p time="301984" is_ac="false">So yeah that's it guys for today, and don't forget to subscribe to the channel and don't forget to follow us on "TravelWithMegh"</p>
  <p time="309173" is_ac="false">Instagram channel and you can also visit our website, and we are also providing the additional services where you can </p>
  <p time="318497" is_ac="false">take a session with me, you can ask any number of questions and you can get all your doubts cleared in half an hour session with me</p>
  <p time="325912" is_ac="false">so guys thank you so much for watching Travel With Megh, till the time ByeBye CiaoCiao</p>
</text>
