<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="Project Happiness " date="20240923" date_ts="1727091032" views="1893936" title="SULLE STRADE PIÙ PERICOLOSE DEL MONDO - I camionisti immortali del Pakistan 🇵🇰" likes="41263" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="13900" is_ac="false">It's harder than expected to find... immortal truck drivers here, huh?</p>
  <p time="23400" is_ac="false">I found one!</p>
  <p time="26200" is_ac="false">How do you feel when you have to cross such narrow roads?</p>
  <p time="30400" is_ac="false">Absolutely terrified!</p>
  <p time="35233" is_ac="false">This time we weren't lucky.</p>
  <p time="36800" is_ac="false">We have to climb up back there... to hitch a ride.</p>
  <p time="39633" is_ac="false">Now I totally understand</p>
  <p time="40600" is_ac="false">what it means to be loaded onto a cattle wagon.</p>
  <p time="44200" is_ac="false">When I travel on dangerous roads</p>
  <p time="46100" is_ac="false">with the mountain on one side and a sheer drop on the other,</p>
  <p time="49000" is_ac="false">it’s a game of life and death.</p>
  <p time="53600" is_ac="false">My name is Giuseppe, and I have a mission:</p>
  <p time="55833" is_ac="false">to travel the world meeting the most extraordinary people on the planet</p>
  <p time="59633" is_ac="false">and ask them one simple question: What does happiness mean to you?</p>
  <p time="64000" is_ac="false">Welcome to "PROJECT HAPPINESS."</p>
  <p time="74933" is_ac="false">This time it’s going to be really hard</p>
  <p time="76300" is_ac="false">to convince you that this is Pakistan's largest beauty center.</p>
  <p time="81300" is_ac="false">Here, Pakistani trucks are decorated and transformed into</p>
  <p time="83500" is_ac="false">incredibly unique vehicles, often dubbed the most beautiful trucks in the world.</p>
  <p time="87300" is_ac="false">In these workshops work the finest craftsmen in the country,</p>
  <p time="89733" is_ac="false">who with meticulous precision</p>
  <p time="91400" is_ac="false">transform the body of these trucks, making them unique.</p>
  <p time="94933" is_ac="false">It can take up to three months of work</p>
  <p time="96800" is_ac="false">to go from this...</p>
  <p time="98800" is_ac="false">to this.</p>
  <p time="100233" is_ac="false">They say that in Pakistan, it’s impossible to find two trucks alike.</p>
  <p time="103800" is_ac="false">And it's believable because each of the over 200,000 registered trucks</p>
  <p time="107966" is_ac="false">that cross mountains, deserts, and cities, aren’t just simple vehicles;</p>
  <p time="112600" is_ac="false">they’re moving works of art, a real expressive language for the drivers,</p>
  <p time="117900" is_ac="false">a way to show their identity and pride.</p>
  <p time="121233" is_ac="false">Hearts, flowers, animals, Bollywood stars,</p>
  <p time="123500" is_ac="false">folk singers, politicians, angels, and prayers.</p>
  <p time="126600" is_ac="false">And often these decorations include elements that remind the truck drivers</p>
  <p time="130200" is_ac="false">of their home, their family, so they don’t feel lonely during the long and dangerous journeys.</p>
  <p time="136400" is_ac="false">All these stories and emotions are told through the decorations of master craftsmen, who for a century now</p>
  <p time="143100" is_ac="false">have passed this art down from generation to generation.</p>
  <p time="157200" is_ac="false">I learned this craft back in 1987.</p>
  <p time="159700" is_ac="false">From the finest artisans in the country.</p>
  <p time="163300" is_ac="false">Just like a person</p>
  <p time="164500" is_ac="false">our trucks want to go around well-groomed.</p>
  <p time="169400" is_ac="false">It's like we’re giving them a bit of perfume to make them stand out when they pass.</p>
  <p time="172800" is_ac="false">We sew a suit on them to make them elegant and beautiful.</p>
  <p time="176300" is_ac="false">When our works of art travel across the country,</p>
  <p time="179200" is_ac="false">we bring honor and glory to our homeland, Pakistan.</p>
  <p time="182300" is_ac="false">I think you can feel how much we love our work.</p>
  <p time="189800" is_ac="false">For example, now we’re working on an old truck that will become wonderful.</p>
  <p time="191800" is_ac="false">The owner trusts us. He just told us he wants it to be unique.</p>
  <p time="195400" is_ac="false">Everyone wants their truck to be the most beautiful. It’s like a competition between them.</p>
  <p time="207033" is_ac="false">But Pakistan’s roads are among the most dangerous in the world,</p>
  <p time="210300" is_ac="false">and the good luck decorations</p>
  <p time="211800" is_ac="false">are often not enough to keep the drivers safe.</p>
  <p time="214500" is_ac="false">In fact, Pakistani truck drivers risk their lives every day to deliver their loads,</p>
  <p time="219100" is_ac="false">and that’s why they’re known and celebrated as the immortals here.</p>
  <p time="224300" is_ac="false">The goal of this mission is to hitchhike</p>
  <p time="226733" is_ac="false">to get onto one of these trucks</p>
  <p time="228800" is_ac="false">and accompany one or more immortal drivers along their journey</p>
  <p time="232500" is_ac="false">on one of the most dangerous roads on the planet.</p>
  <p time="244600" is_ac="false">Okay, the real adventure starts here.</p>
  <p time="246800" is_ac="false">Because we’re at a crucial crossroad</p>
  <p time="248900" is_ac="false">for immortal truck drivers who stop here,</p>
  <p time="251400" is_ac="false">apparently to drink their favorite drink,</p>
  <p time="254100" is_ac="false">which is the truckers' energy drink: sugarcane juice.</p>
  <p time="258000" is_ac="false">They say it’s the best here,</p>
  <p time="259800" is_ac="false">I don’t understand how, because it’s just one ingredient.</p>
  <p time="262833" is_ac="false">But now we’ll try it and ask the sellers at these stalls</p>
  <p time="267300" is_ac="false">how we can approach these truck drivers and get on their trucks.</p>
  <p time="270933" is_ac="false">Let’s go.</p>
  <p time="273800" is_ac="false">By the way, we shouldn’t use the ice</p>
  <p time="276400" is_ac="false">because it might cause stomach problems.</p>
  <p time="279133" is_ac="false">But I want the full experience.</p>
  <p time="288033" is_ac="false">Here it is, let’s try it.</p>
  <p time="295000" is_ac="false">It’s delicious.</p>
  <p time="296200" is_ac="false">They even add a touch of lime,</p>
  <p time="298800" is_ac="false">and it’s a powerful sugar concentrate that helps keep truck drivers alert</p>
  <p time="303500" is_ac="false">during their long hauls.</p>
  <p time="308033" is_ac="false">Often loaded to the point of bursting,</p>
  <p time="310200" is_ac="false">these trucks make their way through small villages,</p>
  <p time="312733" is_ac="false">up and down rugged mountain roads, and across deserts,</p>
  <p time="316700" is_ac="false">carrying tons of goods ranging from gravel, cement, and iron to wheat, cotton, and fruit.</p>
  <p time="322233" is_ac="false">Most of them are majestic old Bedford trucks,</p>
  <p time="325400" is_ac="false">no longer in production, of course, but here they defy time,</p>
  <p time="328333" is_ac="false">remaining faithful allies to the immortal truck drivers.</p>
  <p time="332133" is_ac="false">It’s harder than expected to find... the immortal truck drivers here, huh?</p>
  <p time="345266" is_ac="false">We found one, after two hours we did it, he stopped here.</p>
  <p time="350633" is_ac="false">and he said he’s going to Chitral.</p>
  <p time="353800" is_ac="false">Let's go...</p>
  <p time="354500" is_ac="false">Look at the details, beautiful, made of wood.</p>
  <p time="360600" is_ac="false">It’s so small, wow, what excitement.</p>
  <p time="363833" is_ac="false">There might be some communication problems, but we’ll try to manage.</p>
  <p time="367833" is_ac="false">Ah, he took the camera, “you keep it.”</p>
  <p time="370733" is_ac="false">Okay, nice, thank you.</p>
  <p time="372666" is_ac="false">We can go?</p>
  <p time="374700" is_ac="false">Oh, and there's also... there’s a fan, hahaha... there’s a fan.</p>
  <p time="383133" is_ac="false">He can't even change gears because... here we go.</p>
  <p time="386500" is_ac="false">How long have you been driving trucks?</p>
  <p time="389000" is_ac="false">It’s already been 13 years.</p>
  <p time="390833" is_ac="false">Do you see your truck as a good friend in some way? Is it your work partner?</p>
  <p time="396900" is_ac="false">This truck is literally my heart.</p>
  <p time="400600" is_ac="false">How do you feel when you have to drive on narrow, very dangerous roads?</p>
  <p time="406300" is_ac="false">Terribly scared!</p>
  <p time="407800" is_ac="false">I’m always afraid.</p>
  <p time="411000" is_ac="false">I’m even afraid of this busy road.</p>
  <p time="413000" is_ac="false">But I have a mission to complete.</p>
  <p time="416600" is_ac="false">And even though I’m scared, I do it anyway.</p>
  <p time="420000" is_ac="false">The windshield is very small and narrow, how do you manage to see well?</p>
  <p time="424900" is_ac="false">Sometimes I can’t see anything and have to rely on memory or intuition.</p>
  <p time="428400" is_ac="false">Sometimes I even close my eyes.</p>
  <p time="430400" is_ac="false">And even though I have mirrors everywhere, it’s often my sixth sense that guides me.</p>
  <p time="433400" is_ac="false">Would you ever sell it for any amount of money? Would you ever sell it to someone?</p>
  <p time="438700" is_ac="false">No, no! I wouldn’t sell it for anything in the world!</p>
  <p time="440800" is_ac="false">How could I sell my heart?</p>
  <p time="444333" is_ac="false">There are so many of us here.</p>
  <p time="446900" is_ac="false">There’s another one over there...</p>
  <p time="448200" is_ac="false">Ali has practically become a sardine.</p>
  <p time="450500" is_ac="false">Another brother of Nayyat... another brother of Nayyat...</p>
  <p time="453533" is_ac="false">We’re five, and...</p>
  <p time="456833" is_ac="false">There should be at most three people here.</p>
  <p time="460600" is_ac="false">Brother, your brother... Brother.</p>
  <p time="463800" is_ac="false">Uh, maybe it’s better if...</p>
  <p time="467733" is_ac="false">My new friend tells me a really moving story.</p>
  <p time="470733" is_ac="false">In recent years, the art of Pakistani trucks has been used to help find missing children.</p>
  <p time="476000" is_ac="false">They painted their portraits on the trucks, with all the contact information,</p>
  <p time="479800" is_ac="false">and so each truck became a true messenger of hope on the roads of Pakistan.</p>
  <p time="484900" is_ac="false">A truly touching story that makes the history of these trucks even more fascinating.</p>
  <p time="489700" is_ac="false">Let's take a look; I'm really curious to peek inside here. He has papers,</p>
  <p time="495133" is_ac="false">but look how beautiful these... these compartments are.</p>
  <p time="500133" is_ac="false">This is the plaque.</p>
  <p time="507100" is_ac="false">There’s some junk but...</p>
  <p time="509033" is_ac="false">Can I try?</p>
  <p time="533366" is_ac="false">The kids asked him to honk... the horn... and I helped him.</p>
  <p time="554366" is_ac="false">Tobacco? Yes.</p>
  <p time="556933" is_ac="false">All truckers put some...</p>
  <p time="560733" is_ac="false">tobacco paste in their mouth.</p>
  <p time="564733" is_ac="false">Like this... and then... here.</p>
  <p time="568400" is_ac="false">Here.</p>
  <p time="569800" is_ac="false">It's a tobacco paste, they put it here and slowly it releases nicotine.</p>
  <p time="574866" is_ac="false">Here? Yes.</p>
  <p time="577500" is_ac="false">Well, it’s... obviously addictive like cigarettes.</p>
  <p time="580100" is_ac="false">But here in Pakistan, truck drivers use it... to relax.</p>
  <p time="586133" is_ac="false">I think we’ll have to get off soon</p>
  <p time="587900" is_ac="false">because there’s no room for his brothers he works with.</p>
  <p time="591100" is_ac="false">But we need to ask him one last question.</p>
  <p time="593500" is_ac="false">Nayyat, I have a question for you: what makes you truly happy?</p>
  <p time="600500" is_ac="false">This truck is my happiness!</p>
  <p time="602500" is_ac="false">It’s like a friend that keeps me company.</p>
  <p time="606800" is_ac="false">And I'm proud of it because it's my vehicle.</p>
  <p time="609700" is_ac="false">I bought it with my life savings.</p>
  <p time="612200" is_ac="false">And every time I get in, I smile, remembering it.</p>
  <p time="614600" is_ac="false">I had only ever read about these trucks.</p>
  <p time="617700" is_ac="false">I had studied their history, their culture, but I had never ridden in one.</p>
  <p time="621100" is_ac="false">And it’s really an emotion being here because you see the world</p>
  <p time="624400" is_ac="false">and the road from a different perspective... from above.</p>
  <p time="627033" is_ac="false">And especially from a work of art,</p>
  <p time="629300" is_ac="false">this is truly one of the most beautiful I’ve ever seen.</p>
  <p time="633000" is_ac="false">Furnished down to the smallest details as they used to be.</p>
  <p time="636000" is_ac="false">But I think we’ll have to get off soon.</p>
  <p time="637600" is_ac="false">He hinted at it very politely, very kindly,</p>
  <p time="641333" is_ac="false">but... his brothers can’t fit inside,</p>
  <p time="644700" is_ac="false">the younger brother is squashed there,</p>
  <p time="647500" is_ac="false">while he's half outside,</p>
  <p time="649900" is_ac="false">so in a little while, Ali and I will have to get off, and rightfully so.</p>
  <p time="659733" is_ac="false">Well, our journey with him ends here.</p>
  <p time="665400" is_ac="false">Because otherwise, his brothers won’t be able to fit inside the truck, poor guys,</p>
  <p time="669000" is_ac="false">so we say goodbye to him, and now we need to find another one.</p>
  <p time="680633" is_ac="false">So, can I stay behind?</p>
  <p time="683466" is_ac="false">This time we weren’t lucky.</p>
  <p time="684600" is_ac="false">The truck driver isn’t alone, he's with all his colleagues,</p>
  <p time="687633" is_ac="false">so I have to climb in the back to, to hitch a ride.</p>
  <p time="700500" is_ac="false">Could it have gone worse?</p>
  <p time="702600" is_ac="false">There could have been, wow!, oxen...</p>
  <p time="707533" is_ac="false">But now the goal is to not fall off the truck.</p>
  <p time="711800" is_ac="false">I don't need to tell you that we’re flying here.</p>
  <p time="714000" is_ac="false">We certainly don’t go unnoticed on the back of a truck</p>
  <p time="716933" is_ac="false">in a remote village in the mountains of Pakistan.</p>
  <p time="720400" is_ac="false">People might be wondering, like... what are they doing?</p>
  <p time="723700" is_ac="false">A short journey, but definitely intense.</p>
  <p time="730133" is_ac="false">Okay, bye.</p>
  <p time="735866" is_ac="false">And now we need to find another one, because they’re continuing on.</p>
  <p time="739500" is_ac="false">What an adventure, guys, what an adventure!</p>
  <p time="747233" is_ac="false">I’m becoming an expert on trucks now.</p>
  <p time="748900" is_ac="false">This one is much newer than the others, it even has a rearview camera.</p>
  <p time="754300" is_ac="false">And he’s taking us a bit further north.</p>
  <p time="756400" is_ac="false">He already explained that he can only take us a few dozen kilometers,</p>
  <p time="760700" is_ac="false">because for example, he’s afraid of the checkpoints.</p>
  <p time="763133" is_ac="false">He’s afraid the police will stop us and give him trouble,</p>
  <p time="765933" is_ac="false">so he doesn’t want to take any risks, but he was kind enough to take us a bit further.</p>
  <p time="769866" is_ac="false">Now we’re trying to talk, even though there will be big</p>
  <p time="774700" is_ac="false">communication and language barriers, but we’ll try.</p>
  <p time="779000" is_ac="false">It’s been almost six or seven years.</p>
  <p time="781000" is_ac="false">I’ve been driving for six, seven years now,</p>
  <p time="783000" is_ac="false">but I just bought this vehicle to transport stones from one part of the country to another.</p>
  <p time="788400" is_ac="false">Driving makes me feel alive. Especially when it’s dangerous.</p>
  <p time="791400" is_ac="false">For me, it becomes a mission to deliver the load to its destination.</p>
  <p time="798500" is_ac="false">But these are the roads of Pakistan. Not everyone is capable of driving in these conditions.</p>
  <p time="806200" is_ac="false">Only the best truck drivers can master them. Maybe only the craziest have the courage to drive here.</p>
  <p time="812700" is_ac="false">What’s the secret to being a good truck driver?</p>
  <p time="816700" is_ac="false">You have to consider that these are very heavy trucks, and on these mountains, every small mistake can be fatal.</p>
  <p time="824700" is_ac="false">But I love that thrill. That’s why I love my job.</p>
  <p time="827733" is_ac="false">Our new friend asked me</p>
  <p time="829133" is_ac="false">for a few minutes' pause because it seems he got lost.</p>
  <p time="831900" is_ac="false">But I’ll take advantage of this to tell you something very important.</p>
  <p time="835300" is_ac="false">Yes, because below the video</p>
  <p time="836500" is_ac="false">I’ve left you a link to try out NORDVPN's new “ULTIMATE” plan,</p>
  <p time="839800" is_ac="false">it’s not just a VPN, but a true digital shield that includes:</p>
  <p time="844133" is_ac="false">NORDVPN, which lets you browse safely and quickly from anywhere in the world;</p>
  <p time="848433" is_ac="false">NORDPASS, to create, protect, and manage all your passwords;</p>
  <p time="851900" is_ac="false">“Threat Protection Pro” to block ads, dangerous sites, and protect you from phishing;</p>
  <p time="856500" is_ac="false">and then “NordLocker,” an encrypted cloud space to protect your most important files.</p>
  <p time="861400" is_ac="false">I always keep it on because it blocks ads,</p>
  <p time="864000" is_ac="false">warns me if I’m entering dangerous sites,</p>
  <p time="866300" is_ac="false">and when my email ended up on the dark web, it protected me</p>
  <p time="868900" is_ac="false">by immediately notifying me so I could take action right away.</p>
  <p time="871633" is_ac="false">Plus, with just one subscription, I can protect up to ten devices,</p>
  <p time="875500" is_ac="false">so my whole family can feel safe.</p>
  <p time="878300" is_ac="false">And as always, even in the most remote part of Pakistan,</p>
  <p time="881200" is_ac="false">I’ve left you a link in the description to try NORDVPN</p>
  <p time="883533" is_ac="false">and finally browse in total safety.</p>
  <p time="885733" is_ac="false">Now let’s get back to driving with our friend.</p>
  <p time="896000" is_ac="false">We stopped for a moment because on the side of the road</p>
  <p time="898400" is_ac="false">there are some colleagues who had a mechanical problem,</p>
  <p time="902700" is_ac="false">so they’re fixing it.</p>
  <p time="905200" is_ac="false">When you see a colleague in trouble, you must always help him.</p>
  <p time="908466" is_ac="false">The guys are explaining to me that these are the typical risks you face</p>
  <p time="912300" is_ac="false">when driving one of the toughest and most treacherous roads in the world,</p>
  <p time="915533" is_ac="false">in fact, due to the heavy weight of the loads they have to transport,</p>
  <p time="920533" is_ac="false">mechanical parts can break or fail,</p>
  <p time="923100" is_ac="false">so this can... can happen.</p>
  <p time="924700" is_ac="false">But now they’re stuck here, and another trucker is coming from Peshawar,</p>
  <p time="929100" is_ac="false">a city 10 hours away from here, to help them.</p>
  <p time="933033" is_ac="false">So now all we can do is support them like this.</p>
  <p time="936300" is_ac="false">In the meantime, I take the opportunity to chat with one of them,</p>
  <p time="938333" is_ac="false">who tells me his story.</p>
  <p time="940400" is_ac="false">My uncle was an immortal truck driver.</p>
  <p time="943400" is_ac="false">He had one of the most colorful trucks in the country.</p>
  <p time="946900" is_ac="false">I was still a child,</p>
  <p time="948100" is_ac="false">but once I finished school,</p>
  <p time="950000" is_ac="false">I had no doubt, I wanted to be like him.</p>
  <p time="952700" is_ac="false">I followed him everywhere to convince him it wasn’t just a whim.</p>
  <p time="955500" is_ac="false">I was determined.</p>
  <p time="957700" is_ac="false">And I remember he said: “Alright, if this is truly what you want, I’ll teach you, but don’t die.”</p>
  <p time="963100" is_ac="false">When you drive on roads like these,</p>
  <p time="966100" is_ac="false">you need to be an experienced truck driver, otherwise you won’t make it home.</p>
  <p time="972700" is_ac="false">If you’re not perfect in every maneuver,</p>
  <p time="975900" is_ac="false">then you can’t drive on these mountains. Better stay in the city.</p>
  <p time="980000" is_ac="false">But we who take the risks, get to see breathtaking views from our windows.</p>
  <p time="982600" is_ac="false">We meet amazing people in the villages.</p>
  <p time="985100" is_ac="false">For us, this is not just a job,</p>
  <p time="987600" is_ac="false">it’s a great journey where you only know</p>
  <p time="990500" is_ac="false">the starting point and the destination,</p>
  <p time="994100" is_ac="false">everything else is a big adventure.</p>
  <p time="1018100" is_ac="false">Incredible, he's showing me his most difficult load.</p>
  <p time="1021900" is_ac="false">There were two...</p>
  <p time="1024300" is_ac="false">two huge blocks of marble</p>
  <p time="1027100" is_ac="false">that he transported from one city to another,</p>
  <p time="1029700" is_ac="false">and he said it was really complex</p>
  <p time="1031200" is_ac="false">to transport them because the truck was completely unbalanced,</p>
  <p time="1033800" is_ac="false">he couldn’t control it and was really scared.</p>
  <p time="1036500" is_ac="false">These are the risks that an...</p>
  <p time="1040000" is_ac="false">an immortal trucker can face.</p>
  <p time="1042800" is_ac="false">And even the journey with Hamza ends here,</p>
  <p time="1045133" is_ac="false">but before we say goodbye, we share a good "chai" at a kind of rest stop</p>
  <p time="1048600" is_ac="false">where, according to him, I’ll have a better chance of finding someone to give me a lift.</p>
  <p time="1074300" is_ac="false">We’re helping this trucker in exchange for a ride. Up north.</p>
  <p time="1084600" is_ac="false">We are heading to Chitral to load some cement. Actually, we don’t know exactly what we’ll find there. It could be that we’ll load steel.</p>
  <p time="1092900" is_ac="false">It’s a hard life, but we like it this way. You’re certainly never bored.</p>
  <p time="1096300" is_ac="false">And thank God it allows us to earn a living for our children.</p>
  <p time="1100800" is_ac="false">It’s more than a job because it blends with our life.</p>
  <p time="1103600" is_ac="false">We are Muslims. Traveling across our great country, Pakistan,</p>
  <p time="1108000" is_ac="false">makes us extremely proud.</p>
  <p time="1110000" is_ac="false">Praise be to God.</p>
  <p time="1112000" is_ac="false">Our truck is like a country house for us,</p>
  <p time="1117300" is_ac="false">big, solid, and welcoming.</p>
  <p time="1121100" is_ac="false">In this vehicle resides our destiny.</p>
  <p time="1123100" is_ac="false">It’s all a matter of fate.</p>
  <p time="1125200" is_ac="false">Because our job is very risky,</p>
  <p time="1126800" is_ac="false">few people know how to drive like I do.</p>
  <p time="1129800" is_ac="false">It requires courage and madness.</p>
  <p time="1131500" is_ac="false">I fear only Allah,</p>
  <p time="1135200" is_ac="false">He will decide when my time comes.</p>
  <p time="1138100" is_ac="false">I could fall into the river down here, off a mountain cliff,</p>
  <p time="1143100" is_ac="false">or have a heart attack while driving.</p>
  <p time="1147200" is_ac="false">It’s all in His hands.</p>
  <p time="1150000" is_ac="false">How do you deal with fear when traveling on such difficult roads?</p>
  <p time="1154900" is_ac="false">When I travel in such dangerous areas,</p>
  <p time="1157000" is_ac="false">with the mountain on one side and the cliff on the other,</p>
  <p time="1159900" is_ac="false">it’s a game of life and death.</p>
  <p time="1162500" is_ac="false">This will be my last stop, but before getting their truck back on the road, they share their concept of happiness with me.</p>
  <p time="1169300" is_ac="false">He taught me to be happy.</p>
  <p time="1171100" is_ac="false">He’s my teacher, but I consider him like a father now.</p>
  <p time="1174200" is_ac="false">He’s teaching me techniques and tricks to become, God willing, a great truck driver.</p>
  <p time="1178700" is_ac="false">But I’m already happy because, thanks to this job, I earn honestly and can help others.</p>
  <p time="1184700" is_ac="false">I can send money to my parents to make them happy and proud of their son.</p>
  <p time="1191800" is_ac="false">Just as you are showing passion and courage in your work,</p>
  <p time="1195800" is_ac="false">it’s the same for me driving my truck.</p>
  <p time="1197700" is_ac="false">It’s the source of my happiness because thanks to it, I feed my children.</p>
  <p time="1200700" is_ac="false">Our bread, clothes, and home, it's all thanks to it.</p>
  <p time="1204400" is_ac="false">I love it for this, and I’m grateful for it.</p>
  <p time="1207100" is_ac="false">Allah sent this truck as a means of halal sustenance,</p>
  <p time="1212500" is_ac="false">and I thank Him every day for this gift.</p>
  <p time="1215200" is_ac="false">Every journey has the power to transform us,</p>
  <p time="1217733" is_ac="false">and this adventure along Pakistan’s most dangerous roads was no exception.</p>
  <p time="1222500" is_ac="false">It was an honor to share the road with the immortal truck drivers,</p>
  <p time="1226400" is_ac="false">who are the beating heart of a country that moves, grows, and evolves.</p>
  <p time="1230833" is_ac="false">Their work, often invisible,</p>
  <p time="1232700" is_ac="false">is the engine that keeps the commerce and transport of an entire nation running.</p>
  <p time="1237033" is_ac="false">Far from the spotlight, they face treacherous roads every day,</p>
  <p time="1240533" is_ac="false">extreme conditions, and unimaginable challenges.</p>
  <p time="1243700" is_ac="false">But they do it with a dignity and strength of spirit that I won’t forget.</p>
  <p time="1247400" is_ac="false">And of course, I won’t forget their wonderful trucks,</p>
  <p time="1250833" is_ac="false">faithful companions and shelters during long nights away from home.</p>
  <p time="1254500" is_ac="false">Every little decoration that adorns their vehicles tells their story,</p>
  <p time="1258833" is_ac="false">representing a part of their life and identity,</p>
  <p time="1262400" is_ac="false">welcoming me into their world with simplicity and generosity,</p>
  <p time="1265500" is_ac="false">they showed me how their work is a metaphor for life.</p>
  <p time="1269100" is_ac="false">Every step of our journey,</p>
  <p time="1270800" is_ac="false">every dangerous curve we face, defines and enriches us.</p>
  <p time="1274933" is_ac="false">And we must never forget to value the journey itself.</p>
  <p time="1278500" is_ac="false">The importance of living it with courage and passion,</p>
  <p time="1282733" is_ac="false">just like them.</p>
</text>
