<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="Chef Max Mariola" date="20250310" date_ts="1741624204" views="43671" title="Il mio Cheeseburger VS quello dei fast food: CHI VINCERÁ? Chef Max Mariola" likes="1790" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="0" is_ac="false">Hey ketchup, I'm not afraid of you! Hamburger...</p>
  <p time="2360" is_ac="false">Inside that sandwich they like them then, when you give them cucumbers like that,</p>
  <p time="5040" is_ac="false">the kids say: "No! No, mom! I can't eat that..."</p>
  <p time="7560" is_ac="false">This is my cheeseburger, guys!</p>
  <p time="9400" is_ac="false">Today I bought a cheeseburger,</p>
  <p time="12000" is_ac="false">the one you normally buy in places in the the street, in short in fast food restaurants.</p>
  <p time="17400" is_ac="false">And look what's inside: so there are two pieces of cucumber,</p>
  <p time="21680" is_ac="false">a slice of cheddar, two small hamburgers and...</p>
  <p time="26400" is_ac="false">And the mustard. Mustard and ketchup. So what will I do with this</p>
  <p time="30320" is_ac="false">sandwich that you normally eat? I don't eat it!</p>
  <p time="35880" is_ac="false">We will make one just as good,</p>
  <p time="38720" is_ac="false">if not better but homemade with all the ingredients we have selected.</p>
  <p time="44280" is_ac="false">Do you know what I'll do to you? This, then,</p>
  <p time="47560" is_ac="false">is what we need to copy and do better.</p>
  <p time="50640" is_ac="false">Today we have fun with this video! So let's start with the ingredients:</p>
  <p time="54710" is_ac="false">we have this which is not a cheddar, it's a Fontina.</p>
  <p time="59280" is_ac="false">This is a meat that I got already minced today,</p>
  <p time="62440" is_ac="false">wonderful. Look! We have Fassone of the Piedmontese breed, therefore very lean.</p>
  <p time="67960" is_ac="false">This is to eat like this... Mmm... Very good!</p>
  <p time="71240" is_ac="false">Look... The burger made with this has a weak point.</p>
  <p time="76960" is_ac="false">When it is too lean the meat should be cooked very rare, but we'll talk about that later.</p>
  <p time="82200" is_ac="false">Then we have the bun, which I got from a bakery. Yummy! We have</p>
  <p time="88040" is_ac="false">some bacon, because what do I want to do?</p>
  <p time="90480" is_ac="false">I want to put some fat in here. Then we have the cucumber. I don't want to use</p>
  <p time="95480" is_ac="false">a ready-made cucumber but I want to make it myself in a quick and easy way.</p>
  <p time="99560" is_ac="false">Then we have the ingredients for the ketchup: so sugar,</p>
  <p time="102760" is_ac="false">potato starch, apple cider vinegar, tomato paste, onion, ground cinnamon...</p>
  <p time="107605" is_ac="false">We have nutmeg, ginger, garlic, sweet paprika and tomato puree.</p>
  <p time="113160" is_ac="false">So... Do you like this challenge? It's not a challenge, it's to see if we can emulate</p>
  <p time="120240" is_ac="false">these myths. No? These are myths.</p>
  <p time="122120" is_ac="false">And to do something better, at least apparently. Of course,</p>
  <p time="125760" is_ac="false">you can't all taste it, only I can taste it.</p>
  <p time="127880" is_ac="false">So we could do the test later. So,</p>
  <p time="130240" is_ac="false">let's start with the onion right away! So I get fresh spring onion.</p>
  <p time="133700" is_ac="false">We cut it thin, very thin. Hey,</p>
  <p time="139360" is_ac="false">can you imagine? Let's make homemade ketchup. Quick, very quick we do it.</p>
  <p time="144560" is_ac="false">This here is the first thing we need to do,</p>
  <p time="145720" is_ac="false">which is the slightly longer one. I like it a little oniony, you know how I am.</p>
  <p time="150920" is_ac="false">Yes! Fresh spring onion from Tropea... I put the delicious Sicilian oil</p>
  <p time="156440" is_ac="false">from my friends Fratelli Licari. And now let's stew this spring onion.</p>
  <p time="161440" is_ac="false">We take fresh ginger, so we start with all fresh ingredients. Okay? So</p>
  <p time="166560" is_ac="false">we'll make a product, a ketchup, that you might not like.</p>
  <p time="170120" is_ac="false">Because we are used to industrial products and therefore we may not even like it.</p>
  <p time="174600" is_ac="false">But, well, this ginger is a little shabby but we recover everything,</p>
  <p time="177800" is_ac="false">we don't waste anything. I like it very gingery...</p>
  <p time="181480" is_ac="false">With a nice grater... So this could also be an idea for our kids, right?</p>
  <p time="188184" is_ac="false">We make them a homemade product, therefore a non-industrial product like,</p>
  <p time="192899" is_ac="false">in this case, ketchup. No?</p>
  <p time="194680" is_ac="false">Okay! Garlic, always grated. A little... So,</p>
  <p time="201800" is_ac="false">go! Mix without letting anything burn. Then we put some of this ground cinnamon.</p>
  <p time="212600" is_ac="false">Let's put some of this sweet paprika. Add a teaspoon of that and</p>
  <p time="219320" is_ac="false">a teaspoon of that. Then the tomato paste, I really like it. Look at this...</p>
  <p time="235400" is_ac="false">So let's try to make this ketchup nice and dark, very dark.</p>
  <p time="240160" is_ac="false">Mmm! Hey, the perfume is there! Nutmeg!</p>
  <p time="252760" is_ac="false">Here, I put half of it, almost. Okay?</p>
  <p time="257240" is_ac="false">Good! And then we immediately pour in the tomato puree...</p>
  <p time="272000" is_ac="false">Since we will then blend everything, okay? Like this! Look at the color already, how beautiful and dark it is. Huh? Do you like it?</p>
  <p time="282440" is_ac="false">Even for tomato puree, you have to choose</p>
  <p time="283800" is_ac="false">a very good product. So you are making a product for yourself.</p>
  <p time="289680" is_ac="false">And, when you do it at home, what should you do? You have to put in all</p>
  <p time="292840" is_ac="false">that love and effort to do it really well, so that people fall in love with it.</p>
  <p time="297160" is_ac="false">Whoever is sitting in front of you. A nice spoon</p>
  <p time="300000" is_ac="false">plenty of brown sugar, even one and a half.</p>
  <p time="304680" is_ac="false">Then a nice spoonful of potato starch... White wine vinegar...</p>
  <p time="314400" is_ac="false">And mix because potato starch or</p>
  <p time="318200" is_ac="false">corn starch are always mixed cold. Okay? Like in this case.</p>
  <p time="323720" is_ac="false">Here it is! Because if you mix it hot, many lumps come out. So</p>
  <p time="329960" is_ac="false">this thing I'm doing is fundamental. Okay?</p>
  <p time="336520" is_ac="false">Then I'm going to put it in here and I'm going to mix everything in such a way that</p>
  <p time="348720" is_ac="false">this will be our - let's say - thickener. Okay?</p>
  <p time="353840" is_ac="false">Let's taste it immediately to see if the sugar dose is ok...</p>
  <p time="361800" is_ac="false">It's missing a little salt but, guys, it's touching! Damn that's good! Tié, a little salt...</p>
  <p time="370760" is_ac="false">So the acidity, the sugar, make this sauce liked by everyone. Sugar tricks you.</p>
  <p time="377880" is_ac="false">When there is sugar and when there is acidity, it makes you want to eat more and more.</p>
  <p time="382200" is_ac="false">This is why ketchup is one of those favorite sauces for all children.</p>
  <p time="387840" is_ac="false">Let's blend everything...</p>
  <p time="393360" is_ac="false">Although it's not mandatory because if you can taste those two pieces of onion,</p>
  <p time="397760" is_ac="false">it would be wonderful. Look how beautiful! Aaaah! How beautiful is this ketchup!</p>
  <p time="408200" is_ac="false">I want to drive Mariuccio crazy today. Today, Mariuccio... Guys,</p>
  <p time="412600" is_ac="false">it's incredibly good. How it came to me is scary! Mmm...</p>
  <p time="420680" is_ac="false">Hey, ketchup, I'm not afraid of you! I made you even better</p>
  <p time="423600" is_ac="false">today! Handsome! Handsome! Handsome! Look how nice and thick it is. Perfect!</p>
  <p time="428280" is_ac="false">That is, if you really want to play,</p>
  <p time="429800" is_ac="false">if you want to be like me and you like doing these little things, doing them different, having fun...</p>
  <p time="435320" is_ac="false">Let's be those who want to eat well, who want to make a hamburger or a cheeseburger for</p>
  <p time="440240" is_ac="false">their child and want to do it for them in this way: perfect, good and homemade.</p>
  <p time="446040" is_ac="false">So we put our gherkins in because we like them. They like them inside that sandwich .</p>
  <p time="450712" is_ac="false">Then, when you give it to the kids like that, they say, "No! No, Mom! I can't eat it..."</p>
  <p time="454440" is_ac="false">Now you eat it! Understood? See how we do it. Look at the gherkins</p>
  <p time="458760" is_ac="false">we make. If it turns out well, I will put this cheeseburger on the menu of my Bistro.</p>
  <p time="465000" is_ac="false">So, when you want to eat a cheeseburger, I feel sorry for the</p>
  <p time="468592" is_ac="false">others but you will come and eat it with me. Where else do you want to eat it?</p>
  <p time="471960" is_ac="false">Brown sugar, like that. A little vinegar, like that. Salt, a little salt...</p>
  <p time="484160" is_ac="false">Let's add a little ginger, right? Look at this... A little more... Do you see</p>
  <p time="490920" is_ac="false">how I grate it? Here it is! And we put a little ginger in it, like this, a little bit everywhere.</p>
  <p time="497160" is_ac="false">So very fresh! So, what do we do? Now let's flip them,</p>
  <p time="501480" is_ac="false">like this. Look, like this, so that it flavors well.</p>
  <p time="505200" is_ac="false">Huh? Look... What a stuff!</p>
  <p time="510000" is_ac="false">I turn off the heat under the ketchup. I put it in a container so it cools quickly.</p>
  <p time="518400" is_ac="false">Look how beautiful, dense! Huh? I put the right amount for</p>
  <p time="523440" is_ac="false">about 500 grams of tomato puree, so I did. Okay?</p>
  <p time="527800" is_ac="false">Mmm... Mmm... Mmmm! What came out of me!</p>
  <p time="534720" is_ac="false">We need to give a little fat to the lean meat,</p>
  <p time="537680" is_ac="false">so I chose and selected a crazy meat. Look, look at the meat I have.</p>
  <p time="542920" is_ac="false">Look at the color! Now: bacon! Let's give it a little fat. So,</p>
  <p time="549520" is_ac="false">look what we do. We chop it with a knife or with a mixer.</p>
  <p time="556240" is_ac="false">I actually make a beat which we then put inside the flab</p>
  <p time="562600" is_ac="false">as it is not in there. There's no fat. Have you seen what it's like?</p>
  <p time="570160" is_ac="false">Like this! Just like a paste, a cream. Do you see? You need at least</p>
  <p time="576560" is_ac="false">30% fat. So out of 500 grams of meat, how many do you need? 150 grams.</p>
  <p time="583280" is_ac="false">Do you see? Like that! Just... Just all crushed, like this, like this. Look...</p>
  <p time="591440" is_ac="false">Aaaah, hey! We don't add salt. And what do we do now?</p>
  <p time="599560" is_ac="false">We work it. Let's get this fat everywhere. No?</p>
  <p time="603680" is_ac="false">And what do we do? I wouldn't even add</p>
  <p time="607400" is_ac="false">salt. I would put it right next. This way you will also have a nicer texture.</p>
  <p time="613440" is_ac="false">We'll put some salt flakes on the meat, it'll be something else! We make our own</p>
  <p time="618600" is_ac="false">burgers, we make them by hand. So, a meat ball, look...</p>
  <p time="627400" is_ac="false">And now I think we'll make them... Look, these here are three 100 gram balls I think.</p>
  <p time="632880" is_ac="false">They were 500 grams of meat, so they will be... Come on, let's do this:</p>
  <p time="637560" is_ac="false">1... And 2! Okay? Maybe it's a little too big, let's make it smaller. What do you say?</p>
  <p time="644040" is_ac="false">But no, let's make it fat, beautiful, like this! Look... Tié! Look at this show!</p>
  <p time="655200" is_ac="false">Extra virgin olive oil on the non-stick pan...</p>
  <p time="665600" is_ac="false">We need to make it nice and caramelized... Meanwhile, let's cut</p>
  <p time="670600" is_ac="false">the cheese. Fontina! Why Fontina?</p>
  <p time="674360" is_ac="false">Because it is a cheese that I find delicious. I cut it too double...</p>
  <p time="686440" is_ac="false">Like this! 1... I find it good, I think it has a wonderful taste. So let's remove the crust...</p>
  <p time="698480" is_ac="false">It melts... Let's turn them... Now we're here! There you have it..</p>
  <p time="711520" is_ac="false">Cheese on top!</p>
  <p time="716000" is_ac="false">Like this! There must be a lot of stuff! Cover it! And now this is going to melt together...</p>
  <p time="724280" is_ac="false">Sandwich... Here it is! Let's heat the bread...</p>
  <p time="735680" is_ac="false">Hey, look what's coming out! Handsome! Handsome! I turn everything off...</p>
  <p time="744960" is_ac="false">Well, I would say: why not use... I would say:</p>
  <p time="751440" is_ac="false">But why not use this good thing? Well, look at this stuff! Look at it!</p>
  <p time="756540" is_ac="false">Let's put it here! This stuff that sits at the bottom of the pan to heat up our sandwich?</p>
  <p time="765600" is_ac="false">Look here: our sandwich! Tié, like this! How do you see it? Well, look at</p>
  <p time="773680" is_ac="false">this stuff! Look at this as it is done: and we will make it the same.</p>
  <p time="777865" is_ac="false">We have... The cucumber... Damn, how beautiful! We have the cucumber,</p>
  <p time="784320" is_ac="false">like this! 1... Drain it well... 2... and 3! Then we have the mustard... Beautiful, like that!</p>
  <p time="800740" is_ac="false">Then the ketchup... Look at the show here!</p>
  <p time="809360" is_ac="false">Go! Then we have our hamburger... Hamburger... Tié! And... get this, man!</p>
  <p time="822920" is_ac="false">Like this! Now... What do you think? Was I really bad? Look at this... And so:</p>
  <p time="833760" is_ac="false">this is my cheeseburger, guys. And this is what you find around. You choose!</p>
  <p time="840320" is_ac="false">Oh my God... Look at this! Look at</p>
  <p time="848840" is_ac="false">the meat cooking! Look at the meat cooking! Look at this stuff! Huh? Beer!</p>
  <p time="855520" is_ac="false">Aaaah... And now let's taste it, guys. Are you ready? The difficulty is this one...</p>
  <p time="870360" is_ac="false">Mmm... Mmm... Mmmm!</p>
  <p time="876080" is_ac="false">“What you put in, you get back.” So,</p>
  <p time="879320" is_ac="false">if we put very high quality stuff in there we will have something superlative.</p>
  <p time="884400" is_ac="false">If this costs €5, how much do you have to pay me for this? Huh? I mean, it's crazy! Absurdly good!</p>
  <p time="893800" is_ac="false">The cooking is perfect. Inside, look how it is: it's humid!</p>
  <p time="896720" is_ac="false">Mmm... Mmm... Mmmm!</p>
  <p time="900080" is_ac="false">Then this cucumber... The ketchup made by us... Guys,</p>
  <p time="904480" is_ac="false">have fun and make it at home. Or you have to come and eat it at my place.</p>
  <p time="907840" is_ac="false">You will find this in my Bistrò menu! Mmm... Mmm... Mmmm! With a beer... But what more do you want?</p>
</text>
