<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="Sara &amp; Paolo Adventures" date="20230217" date_ts="1676653226" views="97557" title="Il VIETNAM è incredibile 🇻🇳 Street food e luoghi unici tra HANOI e HA LONG BAY" likes="2890" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="11700" is_ac="false">Hello everyone and welcome back to the channel! 
After spending three days in Singapore we</p>
  <p time="15480" is_ac="false">reached our final destination: Vietnam! 
We will stay in this beautiful country for</p>
  <p time="19920" is_ac="false">15 days and we have decided to divide
the story of our new adventure into</p>
  <p time="24600" is_ac="false">two videos. We will be based in Hanoi and 
in addition to visiting this city we will move</p>
  <p time="28380" is_ac="false">to different places here in the north of the country! 
Before starting, as always, if you want to</p>
  <p time="31920" is_ac="false">support us, subscribe to the channel and
 now sit down, relax and come with us to Vietnam.</p>
  <p time="42120" is_ac="false">After the first days in Singapore that we already 
told you about in last week's video, now we have</p>
  <p time="47220" is_ac="false">finally arrived in Vietnam, the main
 destination of our trip to Asia. After a</p>
  <p time="53160" is_ac="false">three and a half hour flight we landed in Hanoi 
the capital of the country which will be our home and</p>
  <p time="58260" is_ac="false">base for the next 15 days. In this first video
 we will tell you about two special places:</p>
  <p time="64154" is_ac="false">Hanoi and one of the seven wonders of the natural 
world. You already figured out where we're going right?</p>
  <p time="72900" is_ac="false">We must admit the impact can be 
a bit shocking, it is not the first time</p>
  <p time="76800" is_ac="false">we have visited Southeast Asia and we love
 its well-organized chaos but we have been</p>
  <p time="80820" is_ac="false">missing it for years and we must regain 
confidence with these places, with the</p>
  <p time="84120" is_ac="false">continuous soundtrack of the horns 
and the intense scent of street food</p>
  <p time="90060" is_ac="false">in 5 minutes we arrive at Hoàn Kiếm lake 
which is a bit the hub of the activities</p>
  <p time="94320" is_ac="false">of the inhabitants of Hanoi and around 
which its historic center develops, here is</p>
  <p time="99060" is_ac="false">the beautiful Ngọc Sơn temple, which 
with its Red Bridge it is one of the</p>
  <p time="103140" is_ac="false">most recognizable points of the capital;
 today there are so many people to visit it</p>
  <p time="115935" is_ac="false">Today it's New Year here in Vietnam and Hanoi 
is practically empty, all the shops are closed</p>
  <p time="121380" is_ac="false">there are only locals around who
 are all dressed up and taking family photos. </p>
  <p time="127440" is_ac="false">We then let ourselves be carried away 
by instinct and wander aimlessly</p>
  <p time="130800" is_ac="false">through the streets of the Old Quarter. We immediately 
notice that many houses are tall and narrow and are</p>
  <p time="135420" is_ac="false">called galleries; they were built this way 
since once upon a time taxes were paid based</p>
  <p time="139560" is_ac="false">on the surface area of ​​the house facing 
the street. We also meet many small</p>
  <p time="143640" is_ac="false">temples that sometimes are not even noticed 
because they are squeezed between the tallest houses</p>
  <p time="156000" is_ac="false">One of the most important is the Bạch Mã
 Temple which is said to be the oldest in the city</p>
  <p time="160769" is_ac="false">its wooden entrance doors are splendid, 
the inside is super decorated</p>
  <p time="165060" is_ac="false">with lots of gold and red details and
 the scent of incense is really strong</p>
  <p time="169914" is_ac="false">for Tết so many people are making 
offers and praying for a peaceful new year</p>
  <p time="179693" is_ac="false">For lunch we try our first Phó and some delicious 
Bún chả. The classic recipe for Phó</p>
  <p time="185040" is_ac="false">is with beef, but since I don't eat it, try 
the alternative with chicken and</p>
  <p time="189540" is_ac="false">it's delicious and then I have a great 
passion for soups, this dish is right up my alley</p>
  <p time="195329" is_ac="false">Let's continue an exploration and we pass by the 
Old City Gate, the old gateway to the heart</p>
  <p time="199500" is_ac="false">of the city, even if it has often been
 damaged over the years, it still resists</p>
  <p time="203400" is_ac="false">in all its beauty. Walking through the narrow 
streets, a large square suddenly opens up in front of</p>
  <p time="208020" is_ac="false">us where the neo-Gothic style 
cathedral of Saint Joseph stands out.</p>
  <p time="212340" is_ac="false">It is almost strange to see a structure 
of this type in the center of Hanoi.</p>
  <p time="219000" is_ac="false">We find ourselves on the other side of the
 lake where we can see from near the Turtle Tower</p>
  <p time="223882" is_ac="false">built on a small island in the 
middle of the body of water</p>
  <p time="227874" is_ac="false">As it is almost 6.30pm we head 
towards the Municipal Water Puppet Theater</p>
  <p time="232620" is_ac="false">to attend a unique performance. 
This ancient art originating in</p>
  <p time="236700" is_ac="false">Northern Vietnam dates back to the 11th
 century and was created by rice farmers who</p>
  <p time="241320" is_ac="false">first performed their puppets in villages 
when the rice fields were flooded</p>
  <p time="252271" is_ac="false">It must take a lot of study and 
incredible precision to maneuver them</p>
  <p time="256662" is_ac="false">it is a fantastic show, the music the 
words of the songs tell popular stories of</p>
  <p time="262020" is_ac="false">Vietnamese folklore some choreographies
 are really complex and spectacular, it is</p>
  <p time="267240" is_ac="false">an experience that we recommend! The
 cost of tickets ranges from 3 to 7 euros maximum</p>
  <p time="273960" is_ac="false">When we go out it is already dark and in front of us we 
notice the Red Bridge that leads to Ngọc Sơn all lit up</p>
  <p time="279467" is_ac="false">it is reflected in the water,
 creating an incredible effect and</p>
  <p time="282420" is_ac="false">reminds us a bit of the bridge in the 
film "Spirited Away" by Studio Ghibli.</p>
  <p time="298020" is_ac="false">To celebrate our arrival in this new 
country, we treat ourselves to a dinner</p>
  <p time="301500" is_ac="false">in a restaurant with a panoramic view of 
the lake; it costs a little more than normal by</p>
  <p time="305880" is_ac="false">Vietnamese standards But we eat really
 well! Rolls, morning glory with lots of garlic</p>
  <p time="310920" is_ac="false">and super spicy fried chicken! 
Luckily we brought the Citrosodine</p>
  <p time="315962" is_ac="false">Returning home also the temple that is 
right next to our street all lit up with lanterns</p>
  <p time="320057" is_ac="false">hanging from the trees. Given the time there is 
no one inside and we can go around in peace</p>
  <p time="324900" is_ac="false">it was a long and beautiful day as 
the first day in Vietnam not bad</p>
  <p time="332344" is_ac="false">Welcome to our little house in Hanoi, come!
 This is the entrance which is a kind of small terrace</p>
  <p time="338160" is_ac="false">enclosed by a grate and here is the kitchen, then this 
door is the bathroom which is small but I would say it's</p>
  <p time="346920" is_ac="false">more than fine and this is the room that 
opens with this door glazed; it's huge, it's really</p>
  <p time="355500" is_ac="false">big, we also have a television with Netflix they
 told us, but I don't know if we'll use it and then</p>
  <p time="360720" is_ac="false">read, the very comfortable desk and a sofa
 near the window that overlooks the balcony</p>
  <p time="367918" is_ac="false">is beautiful and we like it a lot, it's super in the center 
therefore negative note: in the evening it is noisy but</p>
  <p time="375060" is_ac="false">oh well you get used to it and we decided to take it for 
all the 15 days we will be staying here in Vietnam</p>
  <p time="381180" is_ac="false">because it was very cheap, so we base ourselves 
here and then we will move on the various days</p>
  <p time="388351" is_ac="false">First stop of today: Train Street, this very
 narrow street where the train passes twice a day</p>
  <p time="393600" is_ac="false">has become famous in recent years, many
 cafes and clubs have also sprung up, since</p>
  <p time="399600" is_ac="false">that the train only passes in the evening and
 we don't want to wait in the crowd of people that</p>
  <p time="403680" is_ac="false">will be there we decided to come in the morning 
to relax a bit; it will be touristic but it is also</p>
  <p time="409380" is_ac="false">very particular here, it's not every day 
that you take a break in a bar built on rails</p>
  <p time="414780" is_ac="false">if you go a little further away there are only the 
houses of the residents who live here 365 days a year</p>
  <p time="421746" is_ac="false">For lunch we try something really simple but
 yummy that we already know we will eat several</p>
  <p time="427200" is_ac="false">times these days! Today we try the Bánh Mì 
which are these small typical Vietnamese baguettes</p>
  <p time="433010" is_ac="false">that were introduced during the French colonial period, 
they are available both with meat and vegetarian and</p>
  <p time="439043" is_ac="false">they cost very little, around €1 each and they look 
delicious. In the place we have chosen for lunch</p>
  <p time="445428" is_ac="false">there are several little dogs, we noticed that 
almost all the dogs here in Hanoi wear t-shirts</p>
  <p time="450360" is_ac="false">and coats and then they are all 
small in size they are really cute!</p>
  <p time="456634" is_ac="false">We then move on to the temple 
of iterature: a Confucian temple </p>
  <p time="459365" is_ac="false">which was the site of the first university in 
the country in 1076. Since there is a lot of chaos</p>
  <p time="464007" is_ac="false">we first visit the area of ​​the very 
small lake Hồ Giám. There are a</p>
  <p time="467580" is_ac="false">lot of stalls selling sweets, toys 
and small objects with loud live music.</p>
  <p time="478680" is_ac="false">The most characteristic thing, however, are certainly 
the stands of the Vietnamese calligraphy center.</p>
  <p time="483339" is_ac="false">There are many people queuing up to have auspicious 
parchments written, the party atmosphere and</p>
  <p time="488760" is_ac="false">general happiness that reigns in these 
days is very nice! Since the sun is setting</p>
  <p time="494880" is_ac="false">and there is much less queue we return to
 the temple of literature. After buying the</p>
  <p time="500280" is_ac="false">30,000 dong ticket, about €1, we enter through
 the main portal which gives access to the five internal </p>
  <p time="506316" is_ac="false">courtyards that make up the complex, one is more 
beautiful than the other, there are temples, ponds, lots</p>
  <p time="512040" is_ac="false">of greenery and painted portals red, it's like an oasis 
in which to relax and keep away the noise of the</p>
  <p time="518280" is_ac="false">city for a while. When the lights come on at sunset
 it becomes even more impressive. Too bad it</p>
  <p time="523980" is_ac="false">closes at 6pm, we were the last to leave!
 The keepers almost dragged us out</p>
  <p time="533617" is_ac="false">For dinner today we decided to try 
the Bánh Cuonh, original rolls right from</p>
  <p time="537900" is_ac="false">North Vietnam and really delicious! 
The rice sheet in which the minced and</p>
  <p time="542640" is_ac="false">very thin mushrooms and pork are wrapped, the lady 
prepares them in front of us and it is nice to see</p>
  <p time="546840" is_ac="false">the whole process, they are fantastic! Just think that 
for two dishes of Bánh Cuonh, a water and a Coca Cola</p>
  <p time="552000" is_ac="false">we spent a total of €2.80! And after an
 evening walk which is already a ritual</p>
  <p time="557940" is_ac="false">now, let's go back to our messed up street; as usual 
we will sleep with dance music in the background</p>
  <p time="569280" is_ac="false">Today is a beautiful day, the wind has
carried away all the mist and the clouds</p>
  <p time="573660" is_ac="false">we see the blue sky, a rarity in these parts!
 We move to a new area of ​​Hanoi</p>
  <p time="579060" is_ac="false">we haven't been to yet, we book a 
taxi with Grab, a very convenient app for</p>
  <p time="583920" is_ac="false">getting around the city and essential if you come to 
Vietnam and we reach the Lotte Center, on the 65th</p>
  <p time="590280" is_ac="false">floor of the skyscraper is the Observation 
Deck, a point from which you can have a</p>
  <p time="595140" is_ac="false">360-degree panorama of the city; walking
 on the transparent glass plates with 272 meters of</p>
  <p time="601440" is_ac="false">emptiness underneath was a bit complicated 
even for me as I don't usually suffer from vertigo</p>
  <p time="614597" is_ac="false">Back to the ground in a few seconds 
thanks to the fastest lift ever taken</p>
  <p time="618660" is_ac="false">we stop to eat a good Phó first to 
continue our day here in West Lake</p>
  <p time="625800" is_ac="false">We pass in front of the great Ho Chi Min 
mausoleum, a funeral monument dedicated</p>
  <p time="629580" is_ac="false">to the Vietnamese leader who
 in 1945 read the declaration</p>
  <p time="634440" is_ac="false">of independence from France in this same square 
which gave rise to the Democratic Republic of Vietnam</p>
  <p time="638741" is_ac="false">We then arrive at Quận Thanh temple,
 beautiful with its all-white entrance</p>
  <p time="642360" is_ac="false">and the small square protected by trees, 
as always these days the temples are</p>
  <p time="646260" is_ac="false">full of people, we are practically the 
only foreigners and we don't mind at all</p>
  <p time="655671" is_ac="false">We walk on the lake and with this 
crazy day it's really nice! There are lots of</p>
  <p time="660360" is_ac="false">people taking the swan-shaped pedal boat, 
someone is running and other ladies are</p>
  <p time="664860" is_ac="false">playing something all in a tight circle. Our
 destination is Trần Quốc, a Buddhist temple</p>
  <p time="670560" is_ac="false">built on a microscopic island in which a 
splendid Chinese-style pagoda stands out</p>
  <p time="675976" is_ac="false">all the rest of the temples and gardens
 that surround it are also really beautiful</p>
  <p time="685193" is_ac="false">Vietnam perhaps not everyone knows but it is also 
famous for its coffee, black and very strong, but</p>
  <p time="690840" is_ac="false">there is also a very particular variant never
 tried before. I had my first Egg Coffee</p>
  <p time="696503" is_ac="false">I haven't tried it yet, it's a coffee I think with some 
kind of eggnog. The thick, super-sweet crema</p>
  <p time="702180" is_ac="false">that covers the black coffee is made with
 egg yolk, sugar, and condensed milk; it is fantastic</p>
  <p time="707574" is_ac="false">and I like it very much perfect for a snack or breakfast. 
Tomorrow morning we will leave Hanoi to</p>
  <p time="713820" is_ac="false">move to a place that we have been waiting to see for a 
long time; tonight for dinner I'm going back to Bún Chả,</p>
  <p time="718620" is_ac="false">my favorite dish so far created right in Hanoi; 
rice noodles, pork meatballs and vegetables</p>
  <p time="723360" is_ac="false">are dipped inside a large bowl of fish sauce,
 a key element in the country's cuisine.</p>
  <p time="728220" is_ac="false">Let's go to bed early because 
tomorrow the alarm goes off at dawn.</p>
  <p time="737580" is_ac="false">This morning a minibus was waiting for us at the 
entrance of our way home which in about two and a half</p>
  <p time="742740" is_ac="false">hours would take us to Ha Long Bay. As expected 
we arrive at the port where there is a small boat</p>
  <p time="747960" is_ac="false">waiting for us that will take us on the Genesis 
Regal Cruise; in the twenty-minute journey</p>
  <p time="752820" is_ac="false">we begin to navigate among the islands 
covered with vegetation that make Ha Long</p>
  <p time="758220" is_ac="false">such a recognizable place, unique in the 
world! After imagining it so much, it's incredible</p>
  <p time="763500" is_ac="false">to be here and with this sunny day! 
In fact, the bay is also famous for being</p>
  <p time="768180" is_ac="false">often foggy, how lucky were we? 
we arrive at our ship and we settle</p>
  <p time="774360" is_ac="false">in the dining room for our first meal on board, 
everything is really perfect, the dishes are</p>
  <p time="779280" is_ac="false">one better than the other, the Fresh Spring
 Rolls with prawns are one of the best things</p>
  <p time="783300" is_ac="false">we have tasted here in Vietnam, until now! 
But even a banal pumpkin cream eaten with</p>
  <p time="788040" is_ac="false">this panorama all around becomes phenomenal. 
After lunch we were finally assigned to our</p>
  <p time="792960" is_ac="false">amazing cabin. Welcome to our room on 
the ship that will host us for the next two days</p>
  <p time="802843" is_ac="false">This is our mega room that we have on 
the ship for the next two days and one night</p>
  <p time="807600" is_ac="false">many ships go around Ha Long Bay while 
we will go to a little bay side where they</p>
  <p time="814620" is_ac="false">told us that we will be quieter and there are
 few ships. The room, as you can see, is gigantic and</p>
  <p time="819720" is_ac="false">very well decorated, but the whole ship is well furnished, 
we like it, one of the nice things about this ship</p>
  <p time="825300" is_ac="false">is that there are only 20 rooms so there are
 not many of us and it is super quiet, but the most</p>
  <p time="831180" is_ac="false">the absolute beauty of the room is the 
private balcony which I will now show you</p>
  <p time="837892" is_ac="false">This is our private balcony and it is fantastic!
 It's fine today among other things, it's sunny and we</p>
  <p time="844080" is_ac="false">were lucky and the view of Ha Long bay is
 crazy and after the wonderful balcony the</p>
  <p time="850140" is_ac="false">bathroom which is huge; on this side there's the 
shower but the really special thing is the tub</p>
  <p time="864151" is_ac="false">We can't relax yet because the 
first activity of the day is right away</p>
  <p time="868671" is_ac="false">What are you doing with the 
orange jacket? It's not to sink!</p>
  <p time="871373" is_ac="false">we get on bamboo canoes to visit 
some caves, accessible only by Bamboo</p>
  <p time="876660" is_ac="false">Boat or canoe here in Lan Hạ Bay; it's a 
fairly short round and we feel a little sorry for</p>
  <p time="881580" is_ac="false">the gentleman who sincerely has to row alone; 
the natural spectacle around us but exciting</p>
  <p time="896507" is_ac="false">Back on the ship and now we can enjoy our
 time here a bit. The sun is going down it's</p>
  <p time="901860" is_ac="false">almost sunset and now there's a little wind 
it's a little cooler; we anchored because in</p>
  <p time="906720" is_ac="false">theory this would be the time to swim in 
the sea but with 10-15 degrees no one did it</p>
  <p time="922588" is_ac="false">The sunset is beautiful and as the sun goes
 down behind one of the many islands in the bay</p>
  <p time="926760" is_ac="false">we still can't believe to our luck
 and the beauty of this place</p>
  <p time="936493" is_ac="false">After a super relaxing bath with a 
panoramic view we go out for dinner</p>
  <p time="939660" is_ac="false">Every dish that is offered to us is 
so tasty, we don't even leave a crumb</p>
  <p time="951609" is_ac="false">We just finished dinner and 
everything was delicious, a better dish</p>
  <p time="955440" is_ac="false">than 'other now they told us to go 
to deck 1 to fish for squid</p>
  <p time="962400" is_ac="false">One thing you surely don't know 
about me is that as a child when I was</p>
  <p time="966300" is_ac="false">5 to 10 I won two fishing competitions: one by 
myself and one with my grandfather! But today...</p>
  <p time="972420" is_ac="false">But today... I haven't caught anything yet! 
And little spoiler nobody caught anything this evening</p>
  <p time="981360" is_ac="false">After a super restful night the alarm goes off 
at 5 to see the sunrise from the bridge and to have</p>
  <p time="986760" is_ac="false">a Tai Chi lesson. Vietnam this 
morning gives us one of the pinkest</p>
  <p time="991500" is_ac="false">and most beautiful sunrises ever seen, it's
 truly incredible! We have no words to describe it</p>
  <p time="1018897" is_ac="false">Sara does 40 minutes of Tai Chi with 
the sky changing color as the minutes pass</p>
  <p time="1023600" is_ac="false">and immediately after we go to have an excellent 
breakfast buffet, at 7.30 am we are already on our way</p>
  <p time="1027920" is_ac="false">to the next activity: an hour of kayaking 
near a fishing village. We can move</p>
  <p time="1032840" is_ac="false">freely and we pass by their 
houseboats and oyster farms</p>
  <p time="1036620" is_ac="false">we also meet some fishermen 
who set up their nets, it is a moment</p>
  <p time="1040760" is_ac="false">of absolute peace and we enjoy it to the
 fullest it was nice to start the day so early</p>
  <p time="1050240" is_ac="false">We return to the ship and after 
some time for us and brunch time, as</p>
  <p time="1054380" is_ac="false">always everything is super good and in the blink 
of an eye it's already time to go back to Hanoi</p>
  <p time="1058973" is_ac="false">other places and other adventures are waiting for us 
here in Vietnam and we can't wait to tell you about them</p>
  <p time="1067580" is_ac="false">And from the beautiful room of the ship 
we say goodbye! We hope you enjoyed</p>
  <p time="1072080" is_ac="false">this first video dedicated to Vietnam! 
After being in the city in Hanoi and by the sea</p>
  <p time="1077540" is_ac="false">here in Ha Long Bay, in the next video we will move 
to the mountains, we hope to find good weather! We are</p>
  <p time="1082940" is_ac="false">curious to read your comments below 
and know if you like it as much as</p>
  <p time="1087860" is_ac="false">we do, or did you prefer Singapore? They are two 
totally different countries but both wonderful</p>
  <p time="1093500" is_ac="false">Before saying goodbye and meeting 
you next week with the second part</p>
  <p time="1096920" is_ac="false">leave us a like and subscribe to the channel 
if you haven't already! See you soon bye!</p>
</text>
