<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="Come To Spain" date="20240203" date_ts="1706986808" views="1495" title="Top 10 Spanish Foods 2025 | What to eat in Spain?" likes="97" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="960" is_ac="false">Hungry from all that walking around visiting Spain, are we?</p>
  <p time="5000" is_ac="false">Well pick up your forks and get ready to feast,</p>
  <p time="7880" is_ac="false">cause I’m gonna show you the Top 10 Spanish Foods that you should definitely try, when you </p>
  <p time="13800" is_ac="false">Come to Spain</p>
  <p time="15719" is_ac="false">Volume 2</p>
  <p time="17320" is_ac="false">Now in our first video, which I will link in the description,</p>
  <p time="20880" is_ac="false">, we touched upon the most known foods of Spain, or at least the most famous ones,</p>
  <p time="25920" is_ac="false">but in this video, we’ll look upon other less known foods, but equal in tasty goodness.</p>
  <p time="32880" is_ac="false">So in no particular order.</p>
  <p time="34960" is_ac="false">Number one</p>
  <p time="36280" is_ac="false">Huevos rotos or Broken Eggs</p>
  <p time="39519" is_ac="false">So yeah, this dish is made with, you guessed it, eggs.</p>
  <p time="43239" is_ac="false">The recipe quite is straight forward, you just fry the egg,</p>
  <p time="46559" is_ac="false">being careful not to break the yolk of course</p>
  <p time="49199" is_ac="false">and then you add them on top of a variety of ingredients,</p>
  <p time="53000" is_ac="false">like jamón ibérico or potatoes, minced chorizo meat,</p>
  <p time="58199" is_ac="false">gulas, which are fish strips made with different fish meat.</p>
  <p time="62760" is_ac="false">Once the eggs are on top, you cut the eggs and mix them with the other ingredients.</p>
  <p time="69239" is_ac="false">Number two: Salmorejo.</p>
  <p time="71320" is_ac="false">Salmorejo is a dish from Andalucía, and more precisely from the region of Cordoba.</p>
  <p time="77239" is_ac="false">It is like a soup with a thick consistency,</p>
  <p time="80400" is_ac="false">made with bread crumbs, garlic, tomatoes, olive oil and salt.</p>
  <p time="86039" is_ac="false">And is typically served with jamón shavings or chopped boiled eggs.</p>
  <p time="91480" is_ac="false">Usually it is served cold and is great in the hot Andalusian summers.</p>
  <p time="97360" is_ac="false">Number three: Cocido Montañés</p>
  <p time="100679" is_ac="false">Cocido Montañes, is a stew originally from region of Cantabria, in the northern part of Spain.</p>
  <p time="108119" is_ac="false">It is similar to the Cocido Madrileño,</p>
  <p time="111119" is_ac="false">but the difference is that this one is made with white beans instead of chickpeas,</p>
  <p time="116519" is_ac="false">and all the ingredients are eaten together, unlike the Cocido Madrileño</p>
  <p time="121280" is_ac="false">which you first have to eat the soup and then the other ingredients.</p>
  <p time="126159" is_ac="false">It also contains chorizo, morcilla, bacon, ribs and collard</p>
  <p time="131800" is_ac="false">and it is typically served hot in the winter months.</p>
  <p time="135920" is_ac="false">Number four: Sobao</p>
  <p time="138320" is_ac="false">Sobao is a type of cake again from the region of Cantabria and more precisely from the Valles Pasiegos</p>
  <p time="146320" is_ac="false">and the peculiarity of this dessert, for all you bakers watching</p>
  <p time="150800" is_ac="false">is that it has equal amounts of butter, flour and sugar in its composition.</p>
  <p time="156639" is_ac="false">It comes in small rectangles packaged in paper.</p>
  <p time="161159" is_ac="false">Its perfect for breakfasts and in Spain is usually dipped in coffee and then eaten.</p>
  <p time="168159" is_ac="false">Number five: Migas</p>
  <p time="170559" is_ac="false">This dish that actually translates to Breadcrumbs, is made with, you guested it, bread crumbs</p>
  <p time="176079" is_ac="false">which are toasted, accompanied by slices of chorizo, bacon, peppers, garlic and eggs.</p>
  <p time="183639" is_ac="false">And it is a traditional dish served at breakfast.</p>
  <p time="187119" is_ac="false">If you enjoy this videos, give it a thumbs up, share and definitely subscribe to watch more amazing content like this.</p>
  <p time="194880" is_ac="false">Number six: Calamares a la romana</p>
  <p time="198119" is_ac="false">Calamares a la romana, is a type of dish made of battered squid rings</p>
  <p time="203159" is_ac="false">rings and served with lemon or mayonnaise</p>
  <p time="205920" is_ac="false">or even in a sandwich, which is very typical in Spain.</p>
  <p time="210320" is_ac="false">Number seven: Morcilla</p>
  <p time="212679" is_ac="false">Morcilla is a type of sausage made with rice, lard onion salt, species</p>
  <p time="218800" is_ac="false">and blood, hence the black color. </p>
  <p time="221199" is_ac="false">But don’t let the blood part scare you,</p>
  <p time="223480" is_ac="false">this sausage is delicious and is actually low on calories, around 200 calories per 100 grams.</p>
  <p time="231119" is_ac="false">You can slice is and warm it in the microwave or in a pan, and that’s it, just eat it and enjoy.</p>
  <p time="238400" is_ac="false">Number eight: Hornazo</p>
  <p time="240480" is_ac="false">Its name comes from the word horno, which means oven,</p>
  <p time="244559" is_ac="false">but it's an augmentative, so the translation would be “huge oven”. </p>
  <p time="249239" is_ac="false">It is a type of empanada filled with meat products, like loin, jamón and chorizo.</p>
  <p time="256119" is_ac="false">It can be found all over Spain, but in every region they give it their particular touch.</p>
  <p time="262880" is_ac="false">Number nine: Cachopo</p>
  <p time="264960" is_ac="false">Cachopo is a dish typical from the Asturian cousin, from the northern part of Spain.</p>
  <p time="270760" is_ac="false">It consists of two beef steaks, between which is added jamón serrano and cheese.</p>
  <p time="277000" is_ac="false">Everything is breaded with egg, flour and breadcrumbs and fried in oil.</p>
  <p time="282159" is_ac="false">Its served hot, garnished with potatoes, peppers or mushrooms.</p>
  <p time="287559" is_ac="false">Number ten: Torrijas</p>
  <p time="289840" is_ac="false">Torrijas is a type of French toast, served around Easter</p>
  <p time="293920" is_ac="false">and consists in adding slices of a particular type of bread, that can hold more liquid,</p>
  <p time="299440" is_ac="false">into milk mixed with sugar and cinnamon, coated in eggs and fried in oil.</p>
  <p time="305679" is_ac="false">They are served with syrup on top or even honey.</p>
  <p time="310840" is_ac="false">So these are the top ten foods you should definitely try in Spain, my name is Alex Moraras,</p>
  <p time="317119" is_ac="false">I hope you enjoyed this video, give it a thumbs up, share</p>
  <p time="320840" is_ac="false">and definitely subscribe, to find you more amazing things, before you, </p>
  <p time="326119" is_ac="false">Come to Spain.</p>
</text>
