<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="Adam Ragusea" date="20250306" date_ts="1741287638" views="637010" title="The truth about cooking on a budget" likes="39550" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="320" is_ac="false">Oh yeah, this is just great, another nouveau riche 
food influencer is going to stand in front of his  </p>
  <p time="6200" is_ac="false">$15,000 new stainless steel refrigerator 
and he's going to lecture you about how  </p>
  <p time="11960" is_ac="false">to cook more economically. Wow. Does anybody need 
that? I don't think so. Nobody needs that, nobody  </p>
  <p time="17360" is_ac="false">wants that. So let's just not do it, right? But 
seeing as how we're both already here, I suppose  </p>
  <p time="24040" is_ac="false">let's just do it. Yes, I did just have to replace 
the refrigerator. Yes, it did cost $15,000. No,  </p>
  <p time="30440" is_ac="false">I do not think it is worth it, but I'll tell you 
why I did it anyway, at the end of this video.
 </p>
  <p time="34840" is_ac="false">There's a perennial internet discourse 
that bubbles up every now and then,  </p>
  <p time="38080" is_ac="false">where people simply observe that if you were 
to try to cook all of your meals at home in  </p>
  <p time="42520" is_ac="false">the way that somebody like me generally cooks on 
the internet, that you would rapidly go broke,  </p>
  <p time="48560" is_ac="false">and that is true. That is definitely a true 
thing. You would go broke if you tried to  </p>
  <p time="52800" is_ac="false">cook fancy meals at home for every single meal 
of the day. And from this, some people end up  </p>
  <p time="57720" is_ac="false">concluding that it might just be cheaper for you 
to simply eat out for most of your meals. Indeed,  </p>
  <p time="62520" is_ac="false">there are lots of options for inexpensive 
takeout these days, from which you can  </p>
  <p time="66360" is_ac="false">feed yourself really, really well for not that 
much money. How's that takeout there, honey?
 </p>
  <p time="70480" is_ac="false">It's delicious.
Do you remember what it cost?
 </p>
  <p time="73400" is_ac="false">$14, I think?
Yeah, that's not bad. Indeed,  </p>
  <p time="76480" is_ac="false">if I were to try to recreate that little takeout 
meal for Lauren at home, it would probably cost  </p>
  <p time="81360" is_ac="false">me way more than $14. That does not mean, however, 
that eating at home is more expensive than eating  </p>
  <p time="88240" is_ac="false">out. You just can't expect to eat the same 
way when you eat at home and also save money.
 </p>
  <p time="93600" is_ac="false">Look at this crayfish. He's almost big enough 
to eat at home right now, but I'm not going to  </p>
  <p time="98200" is_ac="false">because I like him, he's kind of like a dog. Come 
on, you want to be fed? Come on, you want to come  </p>
  <p time="101720" is_ac="false">out? Here, come on. Here, you don't have to 
be scared. Here we go. Come get your food.
 </p>
  <p time="106880" is_ac="false">Anyway, economical restaurant food will always 
be different from economical home cooking,  </p>
  <p time="111640" is_ac="false">because restaurants benefit from different 
economies of scale. I mean, for example,  </p>
  <p time="115760" is_ac="false">think about how I make pizza at home. What I 
normally do is I take my oven, I turn it up to its  </p>
  <p time="121680" is_ac="false">maximum temperature. I put the pizza stone or the 
pizza steel in there to heat up with the oven, and  </p>
  <p time="126520" is_ac="false">then I leave it there at that maximum temperature 
for a long time, a half an hour, or maybe even a  </p>
  <p time="131560" is_ac="false">whole hour to really, really, really heat up that 
stone or that steel. You get a pretty nice result,  </p>
  <p time="136480" is_ac="false">but it is outrageously inefficient, in terms 
of energy cost for getting one pizza out of  </p>
  <p time="142800" is_ac="false">your oven. And if you're wondering if I have 
trouble sleeping at night knowing that I've  </p>
  <p time="146040" is_ac="false">encouraged so many people to be so wasteful with 
finite planetary resources, you'd be right about  </p>
  <p time="151160" is_ac="false">that. I do have trouble sleeping at night. I'm 
going to microwave this water, you'll see why.
 </p>
  <p time="155000" is_ac="false">When I cook pizza at the restaurant at Status 
Dough here in Knoxville, Tennessee, yes,  </p>
  <p time="159360" is_ac="false">pizza is still coming to Status Dough, it's 
been delayed due to physical plant issues,  </p>
  <p time="163160" is_ac="false">but we are coming online soon. We'll talk 
about that soon. Anyway, when I do pizza in  </p>
  <p time="167360" is_ac="false">the oven at Status Dough, what we do is we heat 
up the oven once and then we run lots and lots  </p>
  <p time="172960" is_ac="false">and lots of pizzas through it. And yeah, we 
have to keep powering the oven as we do that,  </p>
  <p time="176600" is_ac="false">but it's far more energy-efficient to make 100 
pizzas out of a hot oven, than it is to make  </p>
  <p time="182120" is_ac="false">one pizza out of a hot oven, because you got 
to get it up to that temperature either way.
 </p>
  <p time="185720" is_ac="false">And it's the same thing with ingredients. 
Restaurants don't buy just like one onion  </p>
  <p time="189480" is_ac="false">or whatever, they buy a whole bag of onions, 
and they break them down, and then they're able  </p>
  <p time="193280" is_ac="false">to make a whole bunch of different things out 
of just that one purchase, whereas you're just  </p>
  <p time="196960" is_ac="false">buying one onion, it's much less efficient. The 
most efficient way to source ingredients at home  </p>
  <p time="201560" is_ac="false">is to look inside your own pantry. Even though 
you might not want to eat any of these things  </p>
  <p time="205720" is_ac="false">that you bought a long time ago, they have 
the advantage of already being owned by you.
 </p>
  <p time="210280" is_ac="false">And of course, dry goods like these beans are 
generally very, very inexpensive because they  </p>
  <p time="214880" is_ac="false">keep for so long and they're easy to transport 
because they're not delicate like fresh produce.  </p>
  <p time="219280" is_ac="false">This one pound, half a kilo of dried beans 
was $1.50 at the Kroger this morning,  </p>
  <p time="225080" is_ac="false">pretty good deal. And if you're in a rush to 
soften them up, you can speed soak them in hot  </p>
  <p time="229560" is_ac="false">water. Rice and beans is like the official food 
of poor people in the Western Hemisphere for a  </p>
  <p time="234880" is_ac="false">reason. It is incredibly delicious and incredibly 
nutritious. You could eat pretty much just this  </p>
  <p time="239920" is_ac="false">and get by reasonably fine, as long as you have 
a few fresh vegetables and stuff in the mix.
 </p>
  <p time="244880" is_ac="false">One of the many reasons why beans and rice 
generally has at least one onion in it,  </p>
  <p time="248440" is_ac="false">is that onion is really rich in vitamin C. 
Vitamin C is like the most delicate of the  </p>
  <p time="253760" is_ac="false">big vitamins that you can think of, like 
chemically delicate. It breaks down a lot,  </p>
  <p time="257640" is_ac="false">and so dried goods that even started off having 
lots of vitamin C tend to not have vitamin C by  </p>
  <p time="262160" is_ac="false">the time you dehydrate them and cook them and 
eat them, whereas fresh things usually have a  </p>
  <p time="266560" is_ac="false">good supply of still intact vitamin C. And that's 
why we're going to put the onion here. If you're  </p>
  <p time="271360" is_ac="false">allergic to onion, a red pepper, great source 
of vitamin C that you can also put in beans.
 </p>
  <p time="275640" is_ac="false">To benefit from economies of scale at home, 
you can't expect to make a different exciting  </p>
  <p time="280600" is_ac="false">meal every single day. You got to make a whole 
lot of one thing and then eat that for several  </p>
  <p time="286680" is_ac="false">days before moving on to the other thing. And 
that creates a new hazard or a new risk that  </p>
  <p time="291680" is_ac="false">people throughout human history have had to 
deal with, which is that when you're eating  </p>
  <p time="295000" is_ac="false">only one thing at a time for long stretches 
of time, it makes it all the more likely that  </p>
  <p time="299760" is_ac="false">you're going to not get all of your vitamins 
and minerals and stuff, because generally, you  </p>
  <p time="304160" is_ac="false">need to eat a variety of foods to make sure that 
you have all of your nutritional bases covered.
 </p>
  <p time="308680" is_ac="false">The odds are, if you're within the sound of my 
voice right now, you live in a country where  </p>
  <p time="312560" is_ac="false">you've probably never even met a person who had 
rickets or scurvy or something like that. There's  </p>
  <p time="317880" is_ac="false">a reason for that, it's because we've nearly 
eradicated major nutritional deficiency diseases  </p>
  <p time="322840" is_ac="false">in the developed world, significantly through 
having everybody have such a varied diet with lots  </p>
  <p time="328400" is_ac="false">of different things. Even if you eat crappy food, 
if you eat lots of different kinds of crappy food,  </p>
  <p time="332480" is_ac="false">especially ones with artificially enriched flours 
and stuff, which for some reason are getting a  </p>
  <p time="336560" is_ac="false">bad rap these days, but they provide you with 
nutrients that keep you from getting rickets,  </p>
  <p time="340160" is_ac="false">right? Even if you eat a large variety of 
prepackaged foods, you're probably still going  </p>
  <p time="344840" is_ac="false">to get most of your nutritional needs basically 
met, to the point where you're not going to get a  </p>
  <p time="348960" is_ac="false">serious nutritional deficiency disease. If you're 
eating one food at a time for many days at a time,  </p>
  <p time="354720" is_ac="false">you have to be a little bit more intentional 
about making sure that you get your vitamins.
 </p>
  <p time="358000" is_ac="false">Well, look, the beans have already swollen 
up a whole lot, look at that. Yeah,  </p>
  <p time="361000" is_ac="false">if you ate rice and beans without any fresh 
produce in it, gradually you would get scurvy,  </p>
  <p time="366040" is_ac="false">which is something that people aboard ships where 
they didn't have access to fresh produce, that's  </p>
  <p time="370760" is_ac="false">something they found out the hard way, right?
Thanks to advances in science and technology,  </p>
  <p time="375360" is_ac="false">now we can find out all kinds of important things 
about our health the easy way and one of the easy  </p>
  <p time="379960" is_ac="false">ways is a Lumen, sponsor of this video. Lumen 
is the world's first hand-held metabolic coach.  </p>
  <p time="386880" is_ac="false">It's basically a miniaturized version of a 
thing from medicine that they call a metabolic  </p>
  <p time="390640" is_ac="false">cart. You breathe into it and based upon the 
relative concentration of CO₂ in your breath,  </p>
  <p time="396920" is_ac="false">it can tell what percentage of the energy that 
you're burning at that moment is carbs versus  </p>
  <p time="402400" is_ac="false">fats. All right, I'm mostly burning carbs right 
now. That's not surprising because I've already  </p>
  <p time="406080" is_ac="false">done my workout and had my breakfast today, 
so I'm still processing my food, and that's  </p>
  <p time="410320" is_ac="false">generally going to be an indication that you're 
burning more carbs than fat, unless you've had a  </p>
  <p time="415400" is_ac="false">super high-fat meal, a super high-fat meal.
Now, if you do these little tests regularly,  </p>
  <p time="419160" is_ac="false">the Lumen app here will figure out a personalized 
nutrition and workout plan for you to help you  </p>
  <p time="424520" is_ac="false">reach whatever your fitness goals are. Also, 
it can help you to increase what they call your  </p>
  <p time="428240" is_ac="false">metabolic flexibility, that is your ability 
to go in between fats versus carbs as a food  </p>
  <p time="433680" is_ac="false">source. There's some evidence indicating that 
people with more metabolic flexibility are less  </p>
  <p time="438280" is_ac="false">likely to get certain metabolic diseases like 
type two diabetes, but to me, the main benefit  </p>
  <p time="442160" is_ac="false">of the Lumen is it's kind of a gamified way for me 
to keep myself honest about my night snacking. I  </p>
  <p time="448360" is_ac="false">eat pretty nutritiously during the day, at night 
I go crazy and I eat whole sleeves full of-
 </p>
  <p time="453320" is_ac="false">Brand name redacted.
... it's not good. And if I do that,  </p>
  <p time="457080" is_ac="false">I'll wake up the next morning and on empty 
stomach, I'll do my Lumen test and I will  </p>
  <p time="460720" is_ac="false">still be burning primarily carbs and 
not fats. And that's an indication  </p>
  <p time="464120" is_ac="false">that I ate way too many carbs last night. 
And because I don't want that to happen,  </p>
  <p time="469600" is_ac="false">I don't want to see myself get my bad score on 
my Lumen in the morning, that provides me with  </p>
  <p time="474320" is_ac="false">some extra motivation to not eat the cookies. So 
if you want to take your next step to a fitter,  </p>
  <p time="478760" is_ac="false">healthier version of yourself, go to 
lumen.me/ragusea, or just click my  </p>
  <p time="484360" is_ac="false">link below to get 20% off your Lumen. 20% off 
with my link downstairs. Thank you, Lumen.
 </p>
  <p time="490440" is_ac="false">Anyway, eating cheaply at home. Yes, this whole 
pound of dried beans was only a $1.50 at the  </p>
  <p time="495640" is_ac="false">grocery store. This onion was also $1.50, which is 
weird because this is way less food than this is,  </p>
  <p time="500800" is_ac="false">but this is more expensive because it's 
fresh food. Fresh food is more expensive,  </p>
  <p time="504360" is_ac="false">but it's a worthy investment because of the 
vitamins. It sucks that when you're poor you  </p>
  <p time="508360" is_ac="false">have to put more effort and intentionality into 
what you eat in order to not only afford to eat,  </p>
  <p time="514080" is_ac="false">but also to be healthy. That sucks. I mean, you 
might not think that I know anything about that,  </p>
  <p time="519280" is_ac="false">me being a rich food YouTuber. But I'll 
remind you that I was poor before I was rich,  </p>
  <p time="523920" is_ac="false">and that was only six years ago, so I used to be 
right there with you. Being poor sucks. It sucks  </p>
  <p time="528880" is_ac="false">that when you're poor, you can't have a new and 
interesting meal every day of the week. You have  </p>
  <p time="533760" is_ac="false">to eat the same thing days on end. That's not 
very nice, it's just kind of a reality, right?
 </p>
  <p time="539040" is_ac="false">And of course, the fact that it sucks to be poor 
is at least a little bit by design. Personally,  </p>
  <p time="543960" is_ac="false">I'm kind glad that I live in an economic 
system that incentivizes people to work hard  </p>
  <p time="549560" is_ac="false">and or be more inventive and to make more 
money, because when they make more money,  </p>
  <p time="553120" is_ac="false">they get to eat more interesting food, among other 
things. And it's good to have an economic system  </p>
  <p time="557360" is_ac="false">that incentivizes either working harder or working 
smarter. I also have a personal political belief  </p>
  <p time="563360" is_ac="false">that tells me that I think that the fruits... 
See, it's a fruit, not a vegetable, that the  </p>
  <p time="568360" is_ac="false">fruits of our economic system should probably be 
distributed more equitably than they are right  </p>
  <p time="572320" is_ac="false">now. I don't think that poor people should 
have to eat as spartan as they do right now,  </p>
  <p time="576520" is_ac="false">but because things are the way they are, I'm 
going to show you how to make these beans.
 </p>
  <p time="579960" is_ac="false">I will say, green bell peppers are usually 
a lot less expensive than the red ones. You  </p>
  <p time="583720" is_ac="false">could do a green one or you could skip it 
entirely. I think this was like a $2 pepper,  </p>
  <p time="587680" is_ac="false">which is kind of a lot. We got plenty of vitamin 
C from the onion, we're not going to get scurvy.  </p>
  <p time="592040" is_ac="false">And if you're really poor, I would advise 
against draining away the bean soak water.  </p>
  <p time="596480" is_ac="false">I'm just going to pour this directly into the 
pot because it contains a ton of calories,  </p>
  <p time="600760" is_ac="false">just sugars from the beans, starches that would 
otherwise just go down the drain. And if you're  </p>
  <p time="604880" is_ac="false">trying to get as much food energy as you can for 
the dollar, just leave the calories in there.
 </p>
  <p time="609280" is_ac="false">There is some really, really limited evidence 
that suggests that throwing away the soak water  </p>
  <p time="615520" is_ac="false">can lessen the gas and other digestive distress 
that you might encounter when eating beans. But A,  </p>
  <p time="621520" is_ac="false">that's really weak evidence, we don't even 
really know if that's true. And B, two, not B,  </p>
  <p time="626840" is_ac="false">I'm bad at indexing. Anyway, and two, your body, 
your system will actually adjust to eating this  </p>
  <p time="633320" is_ac="false">many legumes in time. You will eventually be able 
to digest them all just fine if you keep at it.
 </p>
  <p time="639040" is_ac="false">That's just plain water in there, by the way, 
enough to cover the beans. You could use stock,  </p>
  <p time="643160" is_ac="false">by the way, but we're doing this on the cheap and 
plus this is going to be vegan. And speaking of  </p>
  <p time="646720" is_ac="false">vegetarians and vegans, think about the entire 
Indian subcontinent where a lot of people don't  </p>
  <p time="651880" is_ac="false">eat meat either for religious reasons or 
because they just can't afford it. What do  </p>
  <p time="655680" is_ac="false">they subsist on? Well, beans and lentils and 
other pulses. Pulse is the term that they use  </p>
  <p time="660080" is_ac="false">for those kinds of things there, and they get 
by just fine and they're not constantly blowing  </p>
  <p time="664880" is_ac="false">ass over in India, their systems adjust.
Just bring that up to a boil. And of course,  </p>
  <p time="669400" is_ac="false">beans are a relatively high-protein food that's 
much less expensive than meat, the really  </p>
  <p time="674880" is_ac="false">high-protein food. Why is meat so expensive even 
in a country like the United States where the meat  </p>
  <p time="679960" is_ac="false">industry is subsidized in various indirect and 
direct ways from the government, and I'm not sure  </p>
  <p time="685040" is_ac="false">how I feel about that? But even in the United 
States where meat is super cheap, it's still  </p>
  <p time="689440" is_ac="false">way more expensive than something like beans, it's 
because meat is like a secondary product, right?  </p>
  <p time="694600" is_ac="false">The primary product is the plants that you grow 
in order to feed the animals that you then grow  </p>
  <p time="699400" is_ac="false">into meat. You could skip the middleman there and 
just eat the plants that come out of the ground  </p>
  <p time="704640" is_ac="false">before you feed them to the animal, and that 
would be a much more efficient system and also  </p>
  <p time="708800" is_ac="false">probably a lot more environmentally sustainable.
I also have trouble sleeping at night knowing that  </p>
  <p time="712560" is_ac="false">I've encouraged so much meat eating over the 
course of my career, but I try to emphasize  </p>
  <p time="717040" is_ac="false">as I go, that meat ought to be regarded as a 
special treat, not a staple food. Beans are  </p>
  <p time="722840" is_ac="false">like the ultimate staple food, especially in 
a modern diet where we generally eat too many  </p>
  <p time="727400" is_ac="false">carbohydrates and not enough protein. This is 
still a lot of carbs but a lot of protein too.
 </p>
  <p time="732760" is_ac="false">And I will at this stage, put in some salt, just 
to get some seasoning penetrating into the center  </p>
  <p time="737960" is_ac="false">of the bean. But for my herbs and spices 
and stuff, which are a lot more expensive,  </p>
  <p time="742280" is_ac="false">you're going to get more flavor out of these 
relative to the amount you put in if you put  </p>
  <p time="746040" is_ac="false">them in more toward the end. You put them in 
early, a lot of the flavor kind of boils out  </p>
  <p time="750040" is_ac="false">as delicious smells, and it's just less 
efficient use of an expensive product.
 </p>
  <p time="754160" is_ac="false">All right, after a couple hours of simmering, 
there we are. Use as little water as possible if  </p>
  <p time="758760" is_ac="false">you want thick beans, but if they're too thin, you 
can just boil some of the water out right now. Oh,  </p>
  <p time="764720" is_ac="false">this looks like it could be a thumbnail. Okay, so 
when the beans are soft, they're done. Actually,  </p>
  <p time="774200" is_ac="false">it's good to get them slightly more soft than 
you want them because when they cool down,  </p>
  <p time="779200" is_ac="false">they're going to firm up a little bit. And 
also, we're going to put some acid in here,  </p>
  <p time="782000" is_ac="false">which is going to have the effect of firming 
them up, and by that I mean vinegar.
 </p>
  <p time="785560" is_ac="false">White distilled vinegar. This was $2 at Kroger 
this morning, this entire gallon of it, because  </p>
  <p time="790840" is_ac="false">it sold at least as much as a cleaning product 
as it's sold as a food. But it's perfectly food  </p>
  <p time="796240" is_ac="false">grade. And let me tell you, in a heavily spiced 
dish that's cooked, you really cannot tell the  </p>
  <p time="802880" is_ac="false">difference of one vinegar to another. I'm sorry, 
really, you're just tasting the acetic acid,  </p>
  <p time="807800" is_ac="false">which is the core of what vinegar is. The 
more subtle flavors that distinguish the  </p>
  <p time="811840" is_ac="false">finer kinds of vinegar are completely lost 
on most things other than a salad dressing.  </p>
  <p time="817520" is_ac="false">White distilled vinegar is completely fine.
I would guess a couple of tablespoons, we'll see.  </p>
  <p time="822440" is_ac="false">Balance it with the sugar. This isn't cheating, 
if you want something sweeter, you can add sugar.  </p>
  <p time="827520" is_ac="false">Just like if you want something more umami-y, 
you add soy sauce, or if you want something more  </p>
  <p time="833080" is_ac="false">acidic, you add vinegar or lemon juice. It's just 
sugar, it's fine. Garlic powder, cumin, oregano,  </p>
  <p time="840200" is_ac="false">lots of it. Went a little heavy on the sugar even 
for me, but actually it needs a lot more salt  </p>
  <p time="845320" is_ac="false">anyways, so that'll balance it out and we should 
be good. Very serviceable, Cuban style black bean.  </p>
  <p time="852160" is_ac="false">Cubans have had to make a lot with a little for a 
number of years now, they're awfully good at it.
 </p>
  <p time="857000" is_ac="false">Now, because I just don't need that many 
carbohydrates in my diet. I would probably  </p>
  <p time="860560" is_ac="false">just eat this by itself as a bean soup. I wouldn't 
even make rice with it. Beans are about two-thirds  </p>
  <p time="867800" is_ac="false">carbs, one-third protein in their macronutrient 
profile, and that's a pretty good set of macros  </p>
  <p time="874760" is_ac="false">for my particular strength goals. This is when the 
Jim Bros point out that beans are deficient in the  </p>
  <p time="880960" is_ac="false">essential amino acid, methionine, and therefore 
it's not a good complete protein. Well, that is  </p>
  <p time="886200" is_ac="false">technically true, but as we have discussed on the 
channel previously, it just probably isn't really  </p>
  <p time="890440" is_ac="false">a deal in practice, especially not if you're going 
to eat a lot of beans as someone doing strength  </p>
  <p time="894680" is_ac="false">training would be doing if they were trying to get 
some serious amount of protein from beans. And so,  </p>
  <p time="899240" is_ac="false">it's all just going to work out in the wash.
Also, if you're like a resident of a developed  </p>
  <p time="902720" is_ac="false">country and you probably are, it's just 
you're going to get your methionine elsewhere,  </p>
  <p time="906400" is_ac="false">it'd be pretty hard not to. So, that's like 
six good meals that I can just put into the  </p>
  <p time="910720" is_ac="false">fridge and then eat for two days and be fed for 
$7 in groceries, I'd say, something like that.
 </p>
  <p time="919560" is_ac="false">Oh, why do I have a $15,000 refrigerator? You 
remember, you're listening to a man with a  </p>
  <p time="924640" is_ac="false">$15,000 refrigerator. You probably shouldn't pay 
attention to a damn thing he says. And honestly,  </p>
  <p time="929800" is_ac="false">I'm kind of freaked out about it, but it's kind of 
a good example about how once you start spending  </p>
  <p time="935160" is_ac="false">money, it can end up leading you into spending 
more money in ways that you would not have  </p>
  <p time="940720" is_ac="false">expected and not even wanted to, and here it is.
So we bought this house. It came with a really,  </p>
  <p time="946800" is_ac="false">really fancy refrigerator, but it was from the 
year 2000. It was really old and it was dying  </p>
  <p time="952520" is_ac="false">rapidly and so we had to replace it. We went to 
the fancy store. That is the only place where  </p>
  <p time="957440" is_ac="false">you can buy this kind of fancy refrigerator. And 
we had to go there because the people who fancied  </p>
  <p time="963800" is_ac="false">up this house many, many years ago went with 
this kind of refrigerator and only this kind  </p>
  <p time="968880" is_ac="false">of refrigerator is big enough for a cabinet space 
like this. And so we're kind of locked into it,  </p>
  <p time="973960" is_ac="false">unless we wanted to bring in a cabinet maker to 
completely redo all of this. And I just felt like  </p>
  <p time="979080" is_ac="false">we should just go ahead and replace it, that'd 
be the easiest thing to do. And there we were,  </p>
  <p time="983200" is_ac="false">suddenly rationalizing buying a refrigerator that 
costs more than my first new car. Anyways, that's  </p>
  <p time="994360" is_ac="false">how this kind of thing can get out of control.
Hey, don't feel bad if you're poor or, I mean,  </p>
  <p time="1001600" is_ac="false">feel bad because being poor sucks, but don't 
feel bad about yourself because you're poor.  </p>
  <p time="1006480" is_ac="false">It's probably not your fault. A lot of studies 
has been done about rich people versus poor  </p>
  <p time="1012440" is_ac="false">people in terms of their cognitive abilities 
or self-regulation and that kind of stuff.  </p>
  <p time="1016560" is_ac="false">And it just isn't as big of a difference 
as you would expect. It's often really,  </p>
  <p time="1019560" is_ac="false">really negligible. We don't have a really 
equitable economic system in this world,  </p>
  <p time="1025760" is_ac="false">I don't think. And not everybody gets 
paid what they're worth. I hope I've  </p>
  <p time="1030400" is_ac="false">given you some of what you're worth today in 
addressing this very common internet topic.
 </p>
  <p time="1035920" is_ac="false">Yes, absolutely. Cooking at home can be much 
cheaper than eating out, but you don't get to  </p>
  <p time="1041680" is_ac="false">eat the same stuff., Because being poor sucks. 
And it sucks that lots of people are poor.
 </p>
  <p time="1049480" is_ac="false">And it's a nice refrigerator, but it's not 
$15,000 nice. I mean, a normal refrigerator  </p>
  <p time="1056240" is_ac="false">does all the things that you want a refrigerator 
to do. In order to convert normal things into  </p>
  <p time="1060320" is_ac="false">luxury things, they generally just add a bunch 
of stuff that you don't even really want.</p>
</text>
