<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="Alison Roman" date="20210518" date_ts="1621353625" views="474110" title="Easy Roast Chicken Dinner with Crispy Leeks | Home Movies with Alison Roman" likes="6299" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="160" is_ac="false">In the Spring, it's like the 
first peak of vegetables after  </p>
  <p time="3200" is_ac="false">the Winter when it's like potato, 
potato, carrot, potato, so...  </p>
  <p time="10480" is_ac="false">What? Stop! No, I like that. This 
is gonna be a long day of laughter.</p>
  <p time="21360" is_ac="false">Hello, welcome to Home Movies. I'm Alison Roman 
and today I am going to be roasting a chicken,  </p>
  <p time="27840" is_ac="false">but not just any chicken, a Spring chicken. 
What's a spring chicken? A spring chicken  </p>
  <p time="32960" is_ac="false">is a chicken that you roast in the Spring-ish time 
but to me it's like equal parts celebration of the  </p>
  <p time="39200" is_ac="false">chicken and the vegetables that are around in the 
Springtime. It's asparagus, it's teeny potatoes,  </p>
  <p time="47040" is_ac="false">it's beautiful radishes, and it is leeks. It 
is leeks? So I love this recipe because it is  </p>
  <p time="55680" is_ac="false">less about like roasting the chicken and 
more about what you eat it with. The things  </p>
  <p time="60560" is_ac="false">that I like to serve it with I feel like 
really make it feel like a full special  </p>
  <p time="64000" is_ac="false">spring dinner. It's like spring chicken dinner 
rather than just like a chicken with some stuff.  </p>
  <p time="67440" is_ac="false">Basically the things that we're going to 
serve our chicken with are a garlicky aioli,  </p>
  <p time="70800" is_ac="false">our leek top sort of saucy salsa verde e 
situation, and then whatever kind of spring  </p>
  <p time="75840" is_ac="false">vegetable you have on hand and you can serve it 
raw or boiled. I'm gonna boil the potatoes, blanch  </p>
  <p time="80400" is_ac="false">the asparagus, the radishes I'm gonna serve raw 
because they're gorgeous, and they want to be raw  </p>
  <p time="84880" is_ac="false">and that's that. At a time when vegetables 
start to come out, you need to do so little  </p>
  <p time="89520" is_ac="false">to them that all they want is to just be like 
eaten with little bits of like perfectly salted,  </p>
  <p time="95600" is_ac="false">very juicy chicken and that's exactly what we're 
gonna do. I feel like just generally speaking  </p>
  <p time="99840" is_ac="false">this whole thing is a celebration of simplicity. 
I would say that this is actually Nothing Fancy.  </p>
  <p time="104240" is_ac="false">Yeah it's truly Nothing Fancy. It's not in the 
book, which you can buy here, no I'm just kidding.  </p>
  <p time="109120" is_ac="false">Another reason I like this is because while you're 
doing it, you really kind of can't do anything  </p>
  <p time="113760" is_ac="false">else. Like your attention should be focused on 
this dinner, there's not a ton of down time,  </p>
  <p time="117440" is_ac="false">it's like a genuine Sunday activity um but 
it could be done on any day of the week.</p>
  <p time="121520" is_ac="false">First things first, going to preheat our oven 
to 425, we'll talk about our chicken and then  </p>
  <p time="125520" is_ac="false">we'll move on to our vegetables so I'm just gonna 
set these aside. The chicken is gonna get roasted  </p>
  <p time="129360" is_ac="false">with leeks because leeks just like to me really do 
it all. They have texture, they're deeply savory,  </p>
  <p time="135920" is_ac="false">they get really tender, but they also get 
really crispy on the edges so to roast this  </p>
  <p time="139760" is_ac="false">along with the chicken I think is fulfilling 
its true destiny. We're gonna roast this chicken  </p>
  <p time="144560" is_ac="false">in a cast iron skillet. Um it doesn't 
really matter the size of your skillet  </p>
  <p time="147680" is_ac="false">as long as your chicken fits. This 
is a uh just shy of four pound bird  </p>
  <p time="152480" is_ac="false">um and it's definitely going to fit 
in the skillet along with our leeks.</p>
  <p time="156320" is_ac="false">I originally call for one large leek, which looks 
something like this. This is a large leek. This  </p>
  <p time="163440" is_ac="false">is something else entirely. I don't even know what 
to call it. I'm honestly shocked and surprised  </p>
  <p time="173280" is_ac="false">this leek is literally the size of a small infant. 
The fact that I was able to procure two of these  </p>
  <p time="179600" is_ac="false">size leeks is even more shocking and this is not 
a joke, this is not a bit, I didn't seek these  </p>
  <p time="185520" is_ac="false">out. This wasn't, this isn't like a gag, like 
I ordered leeks from a grocery delivery service  </p>
  <p time="192880" is_ac="false">and this is what came my way. These are 
organic, they're local and they're large.  </p>
  <p time="199920" is_ac="false">We made a joke earlier that I was 
going to use these on my Peloton.  </p>
  <p time="203200" is_ac="false">I'm going to attempt to use just one of these 
leeks. I'm going to use the big leek. For whatever  </p>
  <p time="208960" is_ac="false">reason in a lot of recipes, they'll tell you 
only to use the white and light green parts, but  </p>
  <p time="214240" is_ac="false">I really enjoy using the dark leafy green 
parts and that's not just for potato like soup,  </p>
  <p time="218560" is_ac="false">you can watch over here it's for roasting too 
or sauteing, like I think the green has a really  </p>
  <p time="223600" is_ac="false">interesting texture, it definitely doesn't get 
as soft as the white and light green parts,  </p>
  <p time="227600" is_ac="false">but that's why I like it especially in the context 
of this dish. We are going to trim these off, but  </p>
  <p time="232480" is_ac="false">we're going to save them and we're going to treat 
them like an herb and we're going to turn them  </p>
  <p time="235520" is_ac="false">into a salsa verde. So half the leeks get roasted 
with the bird and the other half are gonna get  </p>
  <p time="239920" is_ac="false">turned into a sauce. I'll save that, that'll be 
for our thing later. So they should be about this  </p>
  <p time="246000" is_ac="false">thick. I like to leave the root intact 
so they stay intact while I wash them.</p>
  <p time="251120" is_ac="false">We're taking this chicken out of its little 
bag. She's a beaut. She's a beaut. She's like  </p>
  <p time="256240" is_ac="false">very like well bdsm. The reason I like to take 
off the string if it comes with the chicken  </p>
  <p time="262880" is_ac="false">is because there's a lot of chicken that is sort 
of bound tightly by the string that is not going  </p>
  <p time="267680" is_ac="false">to get seasoning unless I undo the string and redo 
it. So that goes for leg of lamb for pork shoulder  </p>
  <p time="273360" is_ac="false">for any type of meat that you purchase from a 
butcher or a grocery store that is pre-tied. I  </p>
  <p time="279280" is_ac="false">always recommend untying it and re-tying because 
otherwise there's going to be like a lot of that  </p>
  <p time="285120" is_ac="false">meat that isn't getting properly seasoned 
in my opinion. I'm just uh patting it dry.  </p>
  <p time="291040" is_ac="false">My little son. This actually 
has a lot of very funny visuals.  </p>
  <p time="295680" is_ac="false">Grow up David. The nice thing also about 
roasting a chicken in like a very casual way,  </p>
  <p time="302240" is_ac="false">you can just kind of roast it with whatever 
it is that you have on hand. I have  </p>
  <p time="306240" is_ac="false">like this weird piece of lemon and like a 
shallot that I peeled and never used and  </p>
  <p time="310880" is_ac="false">this old fennel bulb and instead of wasting any of 
these things or letting them go bad in the fridge,  </p>
  <p time="315920" is_ac="false">I'm going to use them to stuff my chicken. Maybe 
I won't use the funnel, the fennel I don't feel  </p>
  <p time="319200" is_ac="false">like it's actually going to do anything. This 
maybe like a dumb question, what is stuffing a  </p>
  <p time="322800" is_ac="false">chicken do?Cutting this lemon open, putting in the 
chicken, the lemon's gonna give off its juices.  </p>
  <p time="328240" is_ac="false">Those juices will infuse the chicken fat and like 
season the leeks and like when you use that to  </p>
  <p time="332400" is_ac="false">spoon the chicken like it you're gonna taste it. 
I can't wait. It's gonna be great. Same thing with  </p>
  <p time="336000" is_ac="false">the shallot. Roasting a chicken is one of those 
things that people have so many opinions on: this  </p>
  <p time="340400" is_ac="false">is what you do for a crispy chicken, this is what 
you do, you have to grind, you have to salt it,  </p>
  <p time="343760" is_ac="false">you have to do this, you have to do temperature 
for this, you have to flip it, you have to do  </p>
  <p time="346400" is_ac="false">this, it's like you have to start it with a 
hot cast iron and then put it on. It's like  </p>
  <p time="351280" is_ac="false">okay, I'm sure any of those things will give you 
a very good chicken. Chicken is stuffed. I'm gonna  </p>
  <p time="356160" is_ac="false">season with salt and pepper on all sides. Not to 
sound like a broken record but teaspoon per pound  </p>
  <p time="361600" is_ac="false">and I like to like open the wings really kind 
of get in to each little crevice. Open the legs.  </p>
  <p time="369760" is_ac="false">And we'll flip her. So I am going to twine 
this because I want to and I feel like  </p>
  <p time="377440" is_ac="false">it is not something that anyone should have to 
do, but I think for this specific dinner because  </p>
  <p time="381920" is_ac="false">chicken is like truly like the celebrated sort of 
guest of honor here, I feel like we should make  </p>
  <p time="387920" is_ac="false">it feel special. There's a bunch of fancy ways 
to tie or truss a chicken. I don't care, like  </p>
  <p time="393520" is_ac="false">I'm not that interested to be honest. So I take 
the string and I just tie it around the chicken  </p>
  <p time="398560" is_ac="false">and then I tie a bow like that. By tying the legs 
like that, you lift up the thighs and give all of  </p>
  <p time="404080" is_ac="false">this a better chance to get brown in the oven. 
Some people will take your wings and they'll  </p>
  <p time="409920" is_ac="false">tuck them behind the bird like that, which can be 
nice. I really like the way that these wingtips  </p>
  <p time="417040" is_ac="false">get crispy so I like to let them loose. And then 
the leeks get scattered around your chicken. These  </p>
  <p time="422080" is_ac="false">will shrink slightly so you can kind of like fill 
it. Loves washing. I'm going to roast this chicken  </p>
  <p time="429200" is_ac="false">at 425 and the reason I'm doing 425 is because 
the inclusion of vegetables under the chicken  </p>
  <p time="435120" is_ac="false">is gonna slow down the roasting process. If I just 
put a chicken in the oven alone with nothing else,  </p>
  <p time="440400" is_ac="false">it's going to brown and roast much faster. There's 
just no additional vegetables creating steam or  </p>
  <p time="446080" is_ac="false">that need more attention from the heat. That 
sort of slows everything down. So by doing 425,  </p>
  <p time="451200" is_ac="false">everything gets as brown as it can be and 
everything stays as juicy as it should be.  </p>
  <p time="455680" is_ac="false">To me it is like a very foolproof way to not only 
roast chicken but roast vegetables along with your  </p>
  <p time="461040" is_ac="false">chicken at the same time. Everything's gonna get 
drizzled with some olive oil. If you wanted to  </p>
  <p time="464320" is_ac="false">prepare this in advance, you could just prepare 
this and like throw it in the fridge and then put  </p>
  <p time="470320" is_ac="false">it in the oven in six hours and that way when you 
get home from wherever you are, you can just kind  </p>
  <p time="475600" is_ac="false">of drizzle with olive oil and throw in the oven 
and everything's done and you want to give like  </p>
  <p time="479440" is_ac="false">your chicken and your leeks all something to talk 
about here. You don't need that much oil because  </p>
  <p time="484320" is_ac="false">your chicken is going to give off some fat, but 
I always like to give my chicken a head start.  </p>
  <p time="490800" is_ac="false">Now I'm out of pepper. Yeah I don't have any in 
here. Into the oven it goes. And I'm not gonna  </p>
  <p time="495360" is_ac="false">even look at it for 30 minutes. Nothing's gonna 
happen, I don't need, it's gonna start smelling  </p>
  <p time="499440" is_ac="false">good and you're gonna want to be tempted to 
like fuss with it but you really don't need to.</p>
  <p time="505520" is_ac="false">I'm gonna boil potatoes and asparagus 
separately. While I'm doing the other things,  </p>
  <p time="509840" is_ac="false">I'm just gonna get a pot of water on, 
salted water. I'm gonna go with this guy.</p>
  <p time="517360" is_ac="false">I'm gonna do the leek top salsa verde thing, so 
I'm gonna rinse these just like I did the bottoms.  </p>
  <p time="522000" is_ac="false">And if for whatever reason you were finding 
leeks that didn't have the tops, you could  </p>
  <p time="525520" is_ac="false">just compensate with something like chives or 
scallions. The idea being that like you're doing  </p>
  <p time="529840" is_ac="false">like a garlicky raw number ramps if you've had 
them if there's any pieces of the leek top that  </p>
  <p time="534800" is_ac="false">look a little worse for wear, you don't have to 
feel pressure to consume them, but this feels good  </p>
  <p time="539200" is_ac="false">to me. I like these and typically I'll cut them 
into really thin strips. You do want this to be  </p>
  <p time="543920" is_ac="false">pretty small but this is like just you know, just 
like you're chopping an herb or anything, you're  </p>
  <p time="550080" is_ac="false">not looking for like perfect little squares. And 
you can also just go a little bit more rustic with  </p>
  <p time="554480" is_ac="false">it by thinly slicing and chopping like that. 
These leeks I'm gonna put in the freezer and  </p>
  <p time="560560" is_ac="false">next time I make sock, sock, the next time I make 
soup or stock, I'm gonna add this to the broth.</p>
  <p time="566400" is_ac="false">I like to serve this chicken with anchovies these 
are Cantabrian anchovies. I would call this a nice  </p>
  <p time="573440" is_ac="false">tin. Nice tin. They're a little bit more expensive 
than the anchovies that I typically just cook with  </p>
  <p time="578800" is_ac="false">but again like just like I trust the chicken, 
I'm sort of like springing, no pun intended,  </p>
  <p time="583760" is_ac="false">for the nice tin of anchovies. I'm gonna be 
eating them raw, we're celebrating the chicken,  </p>
  <p time="588240" is_ac="false">I feel like this is a gift to the chicken. 
This shows how much I respect the chicken. The  </p>
  <p time="593120" is_ac="false">fact that I'm willing to open the nice tin for 
the chicken. But if you have regular anchovies  </p>
  <p time="599840" is_ac="false">this will also work beautifully in here. Also 
if you hate anchovies, just leave them out.  </p>
  <p time="604960" is_ac="false">Wow these anchovies were packed by Monica, 
that's tight. I'm gonna save most of them  </p>
  <p time="609840" is_ac="false">to eat raw with chicken but I'll take, you know, 
two or three fillets. You can tell a good anchovy  </p>
  <p time="614960" is_ac="false">because they're like firm and pink 
and uniform. They don't smell fishy,  </p>
  <p time="618800" is_ac="false">they just smell meaty and salty, they're 
fantastic. I'm gonna finely chop these.</p>
  <p time="624560" is_ac="false">If you want to include a little 
finely grated raw garlic in this,  </p>
  <p time="627120" is_ac="false">I highly recommend. You could also use a bunch 
of chives you could. Like I feel like the more  </p>
  <p time="630960" is_ac="false">allium flavor here the better. We're gonna 
sort of treat it almost like a really saucy  </p>
  <p time="635040" is_ac="false">like thicker vinaigrette by adding some 
vinegar and some olive oil but before that,  </p>
  <p time="639600" is_ac="false">I'm not gonna use regular garlic. I'm gonna use 
Spring garlic because it's a Spring chicken.  </p>
  <p time="643920" is_ac="false">This is not a must-have ingredient. So in the 
ground garlic grows. In the ground garlic grows,  </p>
  <p time="649680" is_ac="false">gather around children. In the ground, when garlic 
grows, it starts off like this and as it grows up  </p>
  <p time="656480" is_ac="false">it turns into this, so this is basically baby aka 
spring garlic typically once the garlic grows,  </p>
  <p time="664160" is_ac="false">the stock no longer becomes edible. Becomes really 
fibrous. It dries out and that's why you never see  </p>
  <p time="668800" is_ac="false">it sold with the stem. You only ever see it sold 
as a bulb. But while it's still young enough,  </p>
  <p time="673200" is_ac="false">basically the whole thing is kind of edible. Even 
like these you know more fibrous tops like this.  </p>
  <p time="679360" is_ac="false">So these are just going to get thinly 
sliced. I think that like the ability to grow  </p>
  <p time="684160" is_ac="false">interesting things that you cannot find in grocery 
stores and like just seek them out at a farmer's  </p>
  <p time="688480" is_ac="false">market is so special. Season with salt and pepper. 
I'm out of pepper so I'm just gonna season it with  </p>
  <p time="694160" is_ac="false">salt. I'll use a little bit of this pepper, 
we're improvising here. You could use fresh  </p>
  <p time="697920" is_ac="false">lemon or white wine vinegar but because I'm gonna 
season my aiolI with white distilled vinegar. I'm  </p>
  <p time="702080" is_ac="false">gonna use it in this as well. And some olive 
oil. This is a very olive oil positive dinner  </p>
  <p time="708080" is_ac="false">but as you know, I'm very olive oil positive, 
if you want more olive oily you can,  </p>
  <p time="713040" is_ac="false">but to me that's like beautiful and perfect. This 
can also stay for a few days so like if you were  </p>
  <p time="717920" is_ac="false">gonna do that chicken tomorrow, you could still 
make this today and set it aside it'd be great.</p>
  <p time="721200" is_ac="false">I bought some asparagus this 
morning at the farmers market.  </p>
  <p time="723840" is_ac="false">These are from two different farms. Basically like 
what you can find and what you have access to,  </p>
  <p time="728960" is_ac="false">I'd say this is on the you know medium side. This 
is on the thinner side. I'm more of a fan of like  </p>
  <p time="733520" is_ac="false">a small elegant, thin asparagus but both are fun 
to eat here. I'm actually gonna blanch both of  </p>
  <p time="738240" is_ac="false">these because I'm gonna eat them later for dinner. 
To prep asparagus, you can snap off the ends and  </p>
  <p time="743120" is_ac="false">if you want to just sort of snap them where they 
naturally bend. That's a good way to determine,  </p>
  <p time="748800" is_ac="false">you know like a thick fibrous stem. If you want 
to also just do it this way, that works too. I'm  </p>
  <p time="754720" is_ac="false">not gonna peel it or anything, that feels silly 
to me. This isn't Le Cirque. So I just I tried  </p>
  <p time="760320" is_ac="false">to like find like the most outdated restaurant I 
could possibly find. Gonna blanch this asparagus  </p>
  <p time="764800" is_ac="false">for like literally 30 seconds. You're looking for 
them to be like super nice bright the green. The  </p>
  <p time="772080" is_ac="false">salt in the water does it. That's why you blanch 
in salted water. You're basically seasoning it as  </p>
  <p time="775680" is_ac="false">you blanch it. Of course like squirting lemon 
over it and a little flaky salt afterwards  </p>
  <p time="780320" is_ac="false">to serve it is what we'll do but when it comes 
out of the water there's no need to season it.  </p>
  <p time="787360" is_ac="false">No, I don't have an ice maker, I don't have 
an ice machine, I'm not buying ice just to  </p>
  <p time="791840" is_ac="false">shock a vegetable so spreading it out on a sheet 
pan letting them cool as quickly as possible,  </p>
  <p time="797040" is_ac="false">that's sort of my answer to a ice bath and that's 
year round. And if you're not using asparagus,  </p>
  <p time="801760" is_ac="false">you could use green beans, same thing. Just blanch 
them until they're like very al dente, pull them,  </p>
  <p time="806880" is_ac="false">spread them onto a sheet pan, you're 
good to go. Potatoes on the other hand  </p>
  <p time="810480" is_ac="false">are gonna actually get boiled, so I'm 
gonna put them in the same pot of water,  </p>
  <p time="814320" is_ac="false">I'm not going to change it, there's 
no need and I'm going to boil them for  </p>
  <p time="817920" is_ac="false">10 to 15 minutes. These are pretty small so 
I think these will go closer to 10 minutes.  </p>
  <p time="822000" is_ac="false">Oh there's a piece of garlic skin in there, 
cool. The chicken timer just went off.  </p>
  <p time="826480" is_ac="false">For what, was that 30 minutes? Yes, you want to 
see what it looks like after 30 minutes? Nothing's  </p>
  <p time="830800" is_ac="false">gonna happen. She's browning but she's definitely 
not ready. Can you set it for another 20 please?  </p>
  <p time="838240" is_ac="false">See these are already pretty like cool and they 
still have enough snap to be considered al dente.</p>
  <p time="845360" is_ac="false">As for you little radish, typically to like 
serve radishes I will always leave the tops  </p>
  <p time="849760" is_ac="false">on. I will kind of break away some of these leaves 
if they're looking a little worse for wear or they  </p>
  <p time="854800" is_ac="false">feel like especially thorny. I think the tops are 
delicious, that said, I'm not asking you to like  </p>
  <p time="860480" is_ac="false">eat the entire top of this but the leaves are 
good to nibble on I think. So I'm just going  </p>
  <p time="867200" is_ac="false">to set these aside, our potatoes will go here or 
whatever. We'll deal with those later. These can  </p>
  <p time="870720" is_ac="false">also get saved. I happen to have a lot of radish 
tops right now so I'm just going to compost these.</p>
  <p time="877920" is_ac="false">And our third and final sort of step here 
is to make an aiolI and I'm going to do that  </p>
  <p time="881760" is_ac="false">with an egg yolk, a little bit of mustard, some 
vinegar, garlic, and of course oil. I'm going to  </p>
  <p time="885920" is_ac="false">use a blend of olive oil and neutral oil. For this 
particular dish, I'm not going full classic aioli,  </p>
  <p time="894000" is_ac="false">which I think would be like heavier on the garlic 
and heavier on the olive oil to neutral oil  </p>
  <p time="898000" is_ac="false">ratio. Because everything that I'm serving with 
it is kind of delicate. It's like raw asparagus,  </p>
  <p time="902560" is_ac="false">boiled potatoes, simple chicken like everything 
is kind of more quiet so I'm not gonna make  </p>
  <p time="908400" is_ac="false">this like an especially loud aioli. I'm gonna 
start with a little bit of finely grated garlic  </p>
  <p time="914720" is_ac="false">and by a little bit I mean an entire clove. If 
you're sensitive to raw garlic, this is not the  </p>
  <p time="920400" is_ac="false">meal for you because it appears nearly everywhere. 
I'm using a spoonful of dijon mustard for this.  </p>
  <p time="926400" is_ac="false">It really helps the aiolI stay together. Mmm I 
love mustard. And then an egg yolk. So garlic,  </p>
  <p time="933840" is_ac="false">dijon, and one egg yolk. The biggest mistake you 
can make when making an aiolI is adding too much  </p>
  <p time="940880" is_ac="false">oil at the beginning. I'm going to do about three 
quarters of a cup of neutral and a quarter cup of  </p>
  <p time="945840" is_ac="false">olive oil. Sometimes if I'm doing something like 
a grilled lamb or something that I feel like has  </p>
  <p time="950720" is_ac="false">more assertive flavor, I want more olive oil-iness 
to the aiolI and I'll use a higher ratio of olive  </p>
  <p time="956000" is_ac="false">oil to neutral oil. For this particular dish I'm 
using more neutral oil. That said, one cup of oil  </p>
  <p time="961760" is_ac="false">one egg yolk is my general aiolI ratio. you would 
literally start with like a tiny, tiny drizzle at  </p>
  <p time="968160" is_ac="false">a time. That's like half a teaspoon. You make sure 
that it's completely incorporated before you even  </p>
  <p time="973680" is_ac="false">think about adding the other tiny, tiny drizzle. 
By the time we've used about half of this oil,  </p>
  <p time="979040" is_ac="false">we will be able to start adding more at a time, so 
don't worry it's not going to take you forever to  </p>
  <p time="983760" is_ac="false">make this but it is something that you need to be 
taking your time with. You can see it's lighter in  </p>
  <p time="987840" is_ac="false">color, it's thickening up, but it doesn't look 
greasy or grainy or broken. The reason I like  </p>
  <p time="992960" is_ac="false">this bowl for aioli is that it's taller than 
it is wide. So at this point we've added about  </p>
  <p time="999200" is_ac="false">a third of a cup of oil and it's looking really 
thick. It's looking like you know gloopy gloppy  </p>
  <p time="1004960" is_ac="false">like mayonnaise. In an effort to make 
sure that this doesn't break, we're  </p>
  <p time="1008720" is_ac="false">actually gonna counter-intuitively add some liquid 
in the form of white distilled vinegar. It's about  </p>
  <p time="1014080" is_ac="false">a teaspoon. And this is gonna smooth it out. 
And it's gonna allow us to keep adding more oil.  </p>
  <p time="1023360" is_ac="false">So it's looking a little thick again right? 
Great. And taste it. Definitely needs to be  </p>
  <p time="1028960" is_ac="false">tangier. Definitely need salt. Another splash 
of vinegar. And I'm gonna keep adding my oil.  </p>
  <p time="1035680" is_ac="false">To me this is like one of the more 
satisfying things you can do in your  </p>
  <p time="1038160" is_ac="false">kitchen, it's like truly magical. 
And that is the last of our oil.  </p>
  <p time="1045760" is_ac="false">I'm gonna add a little bit more 
salt and actually splash my vinegar.  </p>
  <p time="1049840" is_ac="false">I think it actually wants another garlic clove 
personally. Personal preference. You could use  </p>
  <p time="1056640" is_ac="false">the green garlic that you got to use for the salsa 
verde but it's just harder to chop really finely  </p>
  <p time="1060960" is_ac="false">and it's honestly not as pungent as real 
garlic or adult garlic rather. Oh my god.  </p>
  <p time="1074640" is_ac="false">Yum. I love this vinegar. I love this product. I 
think it is so underrated in seasoning your food.  </p>
  <p time="1082880" is_ac="false">I texted my friend Lauren who makes a perfect 
aiolI and I texted her I said oh my god, I started  </p>
  <p time="1089200" is_ac="false">seasoning my aioli with white distilled vinegar 
and she's like yeah that's how I do it and like  </p>
  <p time="1094400" is_ac="false">that's what I've been and I was like oh that's 
why I thought it was like, I'd seen her do it and  </p>
  <p time="1099520" is_ac="false">I was so obsessed with her aioli, that I then was 
like I absorb, I don't know it's like I dreamt it,  </p>
  <p time="1105760" is_ac="false">incepted it, yeah I incepted it but it's not an 
original thought. But seasoning your aioli with  </p>
  <p time="1110240" is_ac="false">white distilled vinegar is really wonderful 
because it gives you acidity without flavor  </p>
  <p time="1114960" is_ac="false">so it doesn't taste overly lemony and sometimes 
when you season aioli, even if there was a little  </p>
  <p time="1118960" is_ac="false">bit of lemon juice in it, I would cut it with some 
distilled vinegar if you wanted like lemon flavor  </p>
  <p time="1123600" is_ac="false">but without so much acid. Big shout out to Lauren. 
Lauren Schaefer, one of the best cooks I know.</p>
  <p time="1130560" is_ac="false">All right, aioli is done, 
this green sauce is done,  </p>
  <p time="1134480" is_ac="false">our vegetables are blanched, our potatoes 
are ready, so I'm going to take those out.  </p>
  <p time="1137680" is_ac="false">They're tender, they're creamy, they're 
going to be really good with this aioli.  </p>
  <p time="1143200" is_ac="false">I was right. And our chicken's 
ready let's take it out of the oven  </p>
  <p time="1146640" is_ac="false">because it needs to rest, we're not going to 
like go straight from oven, oven to table,  </p>
  <p time="1150240" is_ac="false">we're gonna like let it rest for a minute. So I 
have not touched this chicken, this chicken has  </p>
  <p time="1153680" is_ac="false">just been in the oven for about an hour. Oh. This 
chicken looks so good, are you kidding me? NSFW.</p>
  <p time="1162000" is_ac="false">What I want to do is walk you through these 
leeks also. Some of them are like crispy like  </p>
  <p time="1166480" is_ac="false">a chip and some of them are like tender 
and jammy and very melty. This chicken  </p>
  <p time="1171520" is_ac="false">did exactly what I wanted it to do. This aiolI 
performed exactly how I wanted it to perform.  </p>
  <p time="1175600" is_ac="false">I feel like everything is happening here for 
me today. This just needs to kind of hang out  </p>
  <p time="1180800" is_ac="false">for like 15 to 20 minutes. It's too hot to carve. 
I'm not gonna risk it. My hands are already, I've  </p>
  <p time="1185920" is_ac="false">seen, it's I've been through a lot. We're just 
gonna let this rest here for 15 to 20 minutes,  </p>
  <p time="1190240" is_ac="false">let it cool down a little bit and then we'll 
carve it and serve it with all of our bounty.</p>
  <p time="1196800" is_ac="false">It's like a little rock. Rock? Just ate a rock. 
That was a peppercorn. So our chicken's out of the  </p>
  <p time="1203520" is_ac="false">oven, our sauces are made, our vegetables are 
prepped, we're ready to go. I've been letting  </p>
  <p time="1208160" is_ac="false">this rest for a little bit and that brings me 
to something that I want to talk about. I think  </p>
  <p time="1213440" is_ac="false">a lot of you are going to be upset about what I'm 
about to say. Many people spend their whole life  </p>
  <p time="1218720" is_ac="false">roasting a chicken for crispy skin. 
When this chicken came out of the oven  </p>
  <p time="1222880" is_ac="false">the skin was arguably crispy. As the skin sits, 
even for the past 10 minutes, it softens because  </p>
  <p time="1230880" is_ac="false">this chicken is juicy. At the end of the day 
once you carve it and put on the plate, the skin  </p>
  <p time="1235760" is_ac="false">is not crispy. If you want crispy chicken, eat 
fried chicken. Thank you for coming to my talk.</p>
  <p time="1243600" is_ac="false">I'm just gonna put the vegetables on their 
own plate assuming you don't have a plate  </p>
  <p time="1246640" is_ac="false">big enough. This doesn't have to be fancy or 
artfully arranged or anything, I'm literally  </p>
  <p time="1250880" is_ac="false">just taking a regular size dinner plate and 
putting asparagus on it and the radishes just so,  </p>
  <p time="1256480" is_ac="false">encouraging people to snack on them. This is a 
serving platter. I'm going to keep the potatoes  </p>
  <p time="1261680" is_ac="false">in the bowl. I'm going to keep the sauces in the 
bowls that I made them in because why not. Um the  </p>
  <p time="1267520" is_ac="false">anchovies can go right there maybe. I'll take the 
I feel like I'm going to cut myself on this tin.  </p>
  <p time="1273680" is_ac="false">Tins are scary. I'm going to transfer this chicken 
to the cutting board. In this instance where I  </p>
  <p time="1277760" is_ac="false">know that I'm gonna be eating everything in the 
skillet, like all the chicken juices, all of the  </p>
  <p time="1281920" is_ac="false">fat, all the leeks. I'll tilt my chicken and kind 
of let any juices from the inside run out of the  </p>
  <p time="1287920" is_ac="false">bird because otherwise they'll end up on your 
cutting board and they're harder to wrangle,  </p>
  <p time="1293520" is_ac="false">so this little juicy friend will stay there. These 
parts of the leeks are almost like a braised leek,  </p>
  <p time="1300400" is_ac="false">they're really tender, they're juicy they're super 
like jammy in texture, and then the leeks on the  </p>
  <p time="1306320" is_ac="false">outside here are like papery and almost chip like 
and crispy and that's like to me the best of every  </p>
  <p time="1311920" is_ac="false">single world. Not necessary but I do like to use a 
fish spatula to kind of make sure that I've gotten  </p>
  <p time="1318320" is_ac="false">all of the bits. I'm just gonna let that sit well. 
The twine is really easy to just kind of snip off.  </p>
  <p time="1325360" is_ac="false">Use your scissors or just peel it off depending 
on how tightly you bound this chicken. And the  </p>
  <p time="1328640" is_ac="false">way that I like to do this no matter how I've 
roasted a chicken or what I've rubbed it with,  </p>
  <p time="1332320" is_ac="false">I do the legs first. Oh you know what? Something 
that I forgot to do. Slicing the legs open  </p>
  <p time="1338720" is_ac="false">in the skillet and let that juice come out rather 
than it running all over the cutting board. So  </p>
  <p time="1342960" is_ac="false">I'll do the legs first, the nicely cooked 
roast chicken should just kind of let you  </p>
  <p time="1349920" is_ac="false">know where it wants to be broken down but if 
you want to separate the leg from the thigh.  </p>
  <p time="1359120" is_ac="false">And then carving the breast. Again this skin 
is delicious. It is brown. It's not crispy and  </p>
  <p time="1364560" is_ac="false">that's fine. I'm not upset about that this is so 
much easier to do when the chicken is not hot.  </p>
  <p time="1371680" is_ac="false">This is why I'm hot. It tastes really good.  </p>
  <p time="1375040" is_ac="false">And obviously we're going to save this chicken 
to make broth with. These are all going in this  </p>
  <p time="1379200" is_ac="false">pot because I'm going to stock up. Deal with 
that later. And then the breast I just slice.  </p>
  <p time="1392720" is_ac="false">Then our leeks nestled in and around the 
chicken. We're taking care. We're caring.  </p>
  <p time="1399600" is_ac="false">The reason I also like to use this fish 
spatulas because I can make sure that all  </p>
  <p time="1403120" is_ac="false">the juices are kind of accounted for. Nothing's 
getting left behind. And then you can take this  </p>
  <p time="1409600" is_ac="false">jus. Another reason why you 
shouldn't actually care that  </p>
  <p time="1411920" is_ac="false">much about crispy chicken because we're 
just pouring liquid over it at the end.</p>
  <p time="1415360" is_ac="false">This looks great. and there she is there's 
our beautiful Spring chicken with our  </p>
  <p time="1419360" is_ac="false">stunning spring vegetables. If I were serving 
this to like one person or three to four people,  </p>
  <p time="1425120" is_ac="false">I'd just put out plates, everything can kind of 
like be served family-ish style. But I'm a wing  </p>
  <p time="1431520" is_ac="false">person. I'm gonna get a wing for myself. I'm gonna 
get this leek which is both crispy and tender.  </p>
  <p time="1437520" is_ac="false">This is a personal preference. And then maybe 
I'll put a few pieces of asparagus on my plate.  </p>
  <p time="1442640" is_ac="false">And then maybe a radish or two. But I feel like  </p>
  <p time="1445680" is_ac="false">the radish and the asparagus plate are 
almost like a chips and dip situation.  </p>
  <p time="1451600" is_ac="false">You just sit at the table and snack from the 
plate. I guess it depends on how well you know the  </p>
  <p time="1455920" is_ac="false">people you're eating with. This get spooned over 
your chicken. This I would just sort of serve.  </p>
  <p time="1463200" is_ac="false">Next with the cute little potatoes. And then 
obviously an anchovy or two, to eat with the  </p>
  <p time="1469120" is_ac="false">chicken. I feel like I'm ready to go. Like to me, 
this is the exact thing that I want. Maybe you  </p>
  <p time="1476400" is_ac="false">give somebody a knife so they don't have to tear 
the chicken with their bare hands like I did but  </p>
  <p time="1485040" is_ac="false">it's so good, it's so simple, but it's like any 
other introduction of flavor in like the form of  </p>
  <p time="1491760" is_ac="false">a spice or an herb, I think would just honestly 
be too much. Like there's so much going on. And  </p>
  <p time="1495760" is_ac="false">to me like eating this entire meal is almost like 
an activity, it's like playing cards. Like like  </p>
  <p time="1500480" is_ac="false">we're eating dinner, it feels like an activity, 
it feels like theater, it doesn't feel like we're  </p>
  <p time="1505280" is_ac="false">just feeding ourselves, it feels like this is 
something that we're like engaging in and this is,  </p>
  <p time="1510640" is_ac="false">this is the entertainment, this is the activity. 
I hope you all make this chicken, I hope you make  </p>
  <p time="1514640" is_ac="false">it all year long not just in Springtime. And we 
can talk about other vegetables swap with it,  </p>
  <p time="1518880" is_ac="false">but like leeks and chicken together forever. 
Oh yeah they're having like a brunch. A brunch?  </p>
  <p time="1525040" is_ac="false">Yeah they're definitely brunching. We're at 
home and part of being at home is hearing  </p>
  <p time="1529040" is_ac="false">your neighbors having a bbq, children screaming, 
I mean laughing, children laughing. I love kids.</p>
</text>
