<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="World Wild Hearts" date="20230114" date_ts="1673722807" views="631123" title="MOROCCO TRAVEL (2023) | 10 Beautiful Places To Visit In Morocco (+ Itinerary Suggestions)" likes="6846" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="4620" is_ac="false">What's up guys! We're here in Morocco and 
in this video we're going to show you the  </p>
  <p time="10260" is_ac="false">best places to visit in the country. 
It's actually a bigger country than you  </p>
  <p time="13620" is_ac="false">might think and we had some difficulty 
ourselves deciding where to go when we  </p>
  <p time="16920" is_ac="false">were planning it. So at the end of 
this video, we're going to give you  </p>
  <p time="19680" is_ac="false">some itinerary options to help save you 
time for your trip. So hope you enjoy it.</p>
  <p time="28740" is_ac="false">Morocco is located in the northwest corner 
of Africa. Thanks to its stunning landscapes,  </p>
  <p time="34020" is_ac="false">colorful cities, year-round pleasant weather, 
and unique cuisine, Morocco is a popular travel  </p>
  <p time="39960" is_ac="false">destination. And although the country is 
rapidly modernizing, it still retains much  </p>
  <p time="44580" is_ac="false">of its ancient architecture and even more 
of its traditional customs. In this video,  </p>
  <p time="49320" is_ac="false">we'll highlight 10 amazing places that you 
should visit in Morocco. So let's dive in!</p>
  <p time="55140" is_ac="false">We're Zac and Ine. We make helpful videos about  </p>
  <p time="58020" is_ac="false">destinations around the world so you 
can easily plan your own adventures.</p>
  <p time="62360" is_ac="false">Located in northern Morocco, Fez is one of the 
most ancient cities in the country. Rich in  </p>
  <p time="77520" is_ac="false">culture, traditions, and history, Fez is often 
referred to as the country's cultural capital.  </p>
  <p time="84000" is_ac="false">Spend a day or two exploring the chaotic 
medina that is filled with madrasas, palaces,  </p>
  <p time="89580" is_ac="false">residences, mosques, and other structures 
that date back to as early as the 9th century.  </p>
  <p time="96060" is_ac="false">But also make sure to venture outside the old 
town to see what Fez has developed into today.  </p>
  <p time="101460" is_ac="false">Check out our video about the best 
things to do in Fez for more details.</p>
  <p time="123480" is_ac="false">At number nine we have Essaouira, a bohemian 
city situated along the Atlantic Coast.  </p>
  <p time="129360" is_ac="false">Known as the windy city of North Africa, lots 
of surfers, kite surfers, and windsurfers find  </p>
  <p time="135180" is_ac="false">their way here. But visitors also enjoy 
strolling through the fortified medina,  </p>
  <p time="139740" is_ac="false">walking along the beach boulevard, 
or simply relaxing at the hotel.  </p>
  <p time="143760" is_ac="false">But if you're just looking for sunbathing and 
swimming, you might want to look at other beach  </p>
  <p time="147600" is_ac="false">destinations along the Atlantic Coast. We've put 
some other options on the screen here for you.</p>
  <p time="159540" is_ac="false">Another beautiful place to visit 
in Morocco is Dades Valley.  </p>
  <p time="163500" is_ac="false">Located in the south, it's often nicknamed 
the "valley of a thousand kasbahs",  </p>
  <p time="167880" is_ac="false">because this valley is dotted with palm trees and 
mud brick palaces. But what makes the landscape  </p>
  <p time="173940" is_ac="false">really unique is its red rock formations and 
the serpentine road at the end of the gorge.  </p>
  <p time="179640" is_ac="false">It's best to take in this incredible scenery 
by driving through the valley and making a  </p>
  <p time="184020" is_ac="false">few photo stops. If you have more time we 
recommend hiking to the Monkey Fingers.</p>
  <p time="189660" is_ac="false">There's a lot of hiking in this valley. 
We're actually in the Monkey Fingers  </p>
  <p time="199980" is_ac="false">Canyon ourselves. But keep in mind that the 
trails are really not marked here at all,  </p>
  <p time="205080" is_ac="false">so you need to use maps.me or AllTrails. And we'll  </p>
  <p time="208320" is_ac="false">leave links in the description for 
some really good trails in this area.</p>
  <p time="211160" is_ac="false">At number seven, we have the 
small town of Chefchaouen,  </p>
  <p time="221400" is_ac="false">set amidst the Rif Mountains in the northwest 
of Morocco. It's also nicknamed the "Blue City"  </p>
  <p time="227460" is_ac="false">because of picturesque streets filled with 
houses painted in different shades of blue.  </p>
  <p time="232260" is_ac="false">And while it's still a mystery as to 
why all the houses are painted blue,  </p>
  <p time="235380" is_ac="false">it's a fun experience to simply walk around 
and get lost in the alleyways. Apart from that,  </p>
  <p time="241200" is_ac="false">there are also some other interesting places 
that are worth a visit. Including the Spanish  </p>
  <p time="245340" is_ac="false">Mosque for sunset, the washing stations of Ras 
el Ma, and the Kasbah Museum. Learn more about  </p>
  <p time="252600" is_ac="false">this intriguing city in our other video all 
about the best things to do in Chefchaouen.</p>
  <p time="269520" is_ac="false">The most popular place to visit in Morocco is 
undoubtedly the bustling city of Marrakech,  </p>
  <p time="282060" is_ac="false">located in the center of the country. 
There's something for everyone here,  </p>
  <p time="286500" is_ac="false">whether you like to enjoy the diverse food scene, 
explore the historic palaces and sites, or stroll  </p>
  <p time="292740" is_ac="false">around the peaceful gardens. Start your journey at 
the Jemaa el-Fna Square in the heart of the city.  </p>
  <p time="298800" is_ac="false">Most tourist attractions are 
walking distance from here.  </p>
  <p time="301980" is_ac="false">But if you want to learn more about 
the local life and city history,  </p>
  <p time="304680" is_ac="false">we highly recommend going on a guided walking 
tour of the medina. You can check out our video  </p>
  <p time="310320" is_ac="false">all about the best things to do in Marrakech 
to learn more about the city's highlights.</p>
  <p time="328560" is_ac="false">Located 160 kilometers or 100 miles to the east 
of Marrakech, the Ouzoud Waterfalls are a true  </p>
  <p time="334920" is_ac="false">escape from the hustle and bustle of the city. 
With a height of 110 meters or 360 feet, these  </p>
  <p time="341580" is_ac="false">are the tallest and most spectacular waterfalls 
in the country. We visited this beautiful place  </p>
  <p time="346500" is_ac="false">as a day trip for Marrakech, which allowed us 
to spend about four hours at the falls. The tour  </p>
  <p time="352020" is_ac="false">included a guided walk down to the base of the 
falls, with plenty of time to take in the beauty.  </p>
  <p time="356940" is_ac="false">And we also encountered some monkeys 
along the way who inhabit this area.  </p>
  <p time="361140" is_ac="false">Overall, we really enjoyed this day tour and 
we left a link to the one that we joined in  </p>
  <p time="365760" is_ac="false">the description below. But be aware that this 
place can get very busy during the high season.</p>
  <p time="388260" is_ac="false">Running parallel to the Dades Valley, Todra 
Gorge is another beautiful natural sight to see  </p>
  <p time="393600" is_ac="false">in Morocco. Here, a river carved its way through 
the orange limestone for centuries. As a result,  </p>
  <p time="399660" is_ac="false">canyon walls reach over 400 meters or 1,300 
feet high in some places. There are many ways  </p>
  <p time="406500" is_ac="false">to enjoy the gorge, whether you're an avid hiker, 
rock climber, mountain biker, or prefer to simply  </p>
  <p time="412980" is_ac="false">enjoy the scenery and soak up the culture. 
We did a half-day hike into the canyon and  </p>
  <p time="418200" is_ac="false">over its rocky walls, which we really enjoyed. We 
even spotted some nomadic camps along the trail.</p>
  <p time="445260" is_ac="false">At number three, we have the picturesque village 
of Aït Ben Haddou, located along the former  </p>
  <p time="450600" is_ac="false">Caravan Route between the Sahara and Marrakech. 
It's known for its historic clay buildings  </p>
  <p time="456000" is_ac="false">which is a great example of Moroccan earthen 
architecture. And while most of the village  </p>
  <p time="461040" is_ac="false">has been abandoned in recent years, there's still 
a lot left for travelers to explore. Some of the  </p>
  <p time="466680" is_ac="false">main highlights include watching the sunrise 
and sunset from one of the many viewpoints,  </p>
  <p time="471600" is_ac="false">walking up to the ancient grain store on top of 
the village, and visiting one of the Kasbahs.</p>
  <p time="477720" is_ac="false">In the town here, you can see all these 
traditional houses that are made of mud,  </p>
  <p time="481260" is_ac="false">straw, and wood. And you can 
actually visit some of them  </p>
  <p time="484200" is_ac="false">for just a small fee and then you can 
really see how intricate it all looks.</p>
  <p time="493380" is_ac="false">If you have more time, we also recommend 
exploring nearby or Ouarzazate.  </p>
  <p time="498900" is_ac="false">This city has been welcoming Hollywood directors 
since the 60s and is the movie capital. We did a  </p>
  <p time="504840" is_ac="false">guided tour of the Atlas Studios, where films like 
Cleopatra, the Mummy, and Gladiator were shot.  </p>
  <p time="511320" is_ac="false">Find a day tour to both places 
via the link in the description.</p>
  <p time="521700" is_ac="false">As North Africa's highest mountain range, the 
High Atlas is a paradise for trekkers and skiers.  </p>
  <p time="528120" is_ac="false">Stretching from the Atlantic Ocean in the west 
to the Moroccan Algerian Border in the east,  </p>
  <p time="533280" is_ac="false">this region covers approximately 740 kilometers or 
460 miles. The most impressive part is undoubtedly  </p>
  <p time="540900" is_ac="false">Toubkal National Park, which is easily 
accessible from Marrakech by car or bus.  </p>
  <p time="546540" is_ac="false">And the beautiful village of Imlil is the starting 
and ending point of most hiking circuits in the  </p>
  <p time="552000" is_ac="false">park. We joined a three-day trek across the 
three valleys and traditional Berber villages.  </p>
  <p time="557640" is_ac="false">But it's also possible to go on 
a day hike here from Marrakech.</p>
  <p time="584700" is_ac="false">The most beautiful place to visit in Morocco in 
our opinion is the Sahara Desert, which spans the  </p>
  <p time="590160" is_ac="false">south of the country mainly along the border with 
Algeria. Here, you can enjoy the orange dunes,  </p>
  <p time="595860" is_ac="false">blue skies, camel trekking, camping under the 
stars, and much more. And while there are various  </p>
  <p time="602700" is_ac="false">desert options in Morocco, we explored the popular 
Erg Chebbi Dunes at the edge of the town of  </p>
  <p time="607740" is_ac="false">Merzouga. Get a taste of what the nomadic life in 
the desert is truly like by spending at least two  </p>
  <p time="613380" is_ac="false">to three days here. You can learn all about our 
three-day safari experience in our Merzouga video.</p>
  <p time="629280" is_ac="false">As we promised at the beginning of our 
video, we'll now share three things we  </p>
  <p time="640440" is_ac="false">learned that will help your own trip around 
Morocco. First, we only recommend driving a  </p>
  <p time="645660" is_ac="false">rental car if you're comfortable with long 
distances. There's also a large number of  </p>
  <p time="650220" is_ac="false">police checkpoints and we got multiple fines 
during our road trip, so be careful. Second,  </p>
  <p time="655500" is_ac="false">we recommend spending more time in nature rather 
than the chaotic cities, like Marrakech or Fez.  </p>
  <p time="661320" is_ac="false">Cities in Morocco have a reputation for people who 
offer a service that you haven't requested, which  </p>
  <p time="666000" is_ac="false">can be exhausting at times. Finally, the Wi-Fi 
connection was poor when we were there so it's  </p>
  <p time="671460" is_ac="false">best to get a SIM card upon arrival. Get Moroc 
Telecom for the best coverage and connection.</p>
  <p time="677280" is_ac="false">We also included a few itinerary options on the  </p>
  <p time="679860" is_ac="false">screen here in case you want to 
use them to guide your own trip.</p>
  <p time="683100" is_ac="false">If you want a detailed Morocco itinerary that 
includes all the best things to do, where to stay,  </p>
  <p time="688200" is_ac="false">where to eat, and directions to each place, 
check out the complete itinerary guide.  </p>
  <p time="693900" is_ac="false">We left a link in the description below for that.</p>
  <p time="696960" is_ac="false">If you have more time in Morocco or would like 
to explore more cities and beaches, it's worth  </p>
  <p time="701760" is_ac="false">checking out other beautiful destinations 
that we didn't mention. We've included a  </p>
  <p time="705540" is_ac="false">short list on the screen here. And that's it 
for our top 10 places to visit in Morocco.  </p>
  <p time="711000" is_ac="false">We hope you enjoyed the video and 
we included links for all the things  </p>
  <p time="714180" is_ac="false">that you'll need in the description. 
We'll catch you on the next adventure!</p>
</text>
