<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<text uploader="World Wild Hearts" date="20221119" date_ts="1668884412" views="653473" title="EDINBURGH, SCOTLAND (2023) | 10 BEST Things To Do In Edinburgh" likes="6817" format="srv3" autocaption="false">
  <p time="497" is_ac="false">[Music]</p>
  <p time="900" is_ac="false">What's up guys we're here in Edinburgh, 
Scotland, and in this video we're going  </p>
  <p time="15120" is_ac="false">to show you the best things to do in 
and around the city. Hope you enjoy it!</p>
  <p time="24560" is_ac="false">Edinburgh  </p>
  <p time="25560" is_ac="false">is located in southeastern Scotland. As 
one of the most-visited cities in Europe,  </p>
  <p time="30000" is_ac="false">Edinburgh is known for its whisky heritage, 
striking architecture, and intriguing history.  </p>
  <p time="35400" is_ac="false">Not to mention its beautiful natural scenery and 
buzzing pub scene. The city is big enough that  </p>
  <p time="41880" is_ac="false">you'll be entertained but compact enough 
that you can explore everything on foot.  </p>
  <p time="46860" is_ac="false">In this video, we highlight 10 of 
the best things to do in the city,  </p>
  <p time="50460" is_ac="false">which are best combined in a three 
to four day visit. So let's dive in.</p>
  <p time="55200" is_ac="false">We're Zac and Ine. We make helpful videos about  </p>
  <p time="58800" is_ac="false">destinations around the world so you 
can easily plan your own adventures.</p>
  <p time="72600" is_ac="false">The old town of Edinburgh is the bustling heart 
of the city. Built up in the Middle Ages when  </p>
  <p time="77940" is_ac="false">the fear of attack was persistent, it's home 
to centuries-old buildings and narrow alleys.  </p>
  <p time="83700" is_ac="false">This area will most likely be your first 
area to see when visiting Edinburgh,  </p>
  <p time="87480" is_ac="false">and it's also a great place to stay. The 
best way to learn about this intriguing  </p>
  <p time="92220" is_ac="false">part of the city is by joining a free walking 
tour.Tours usually run multiple times a day.  </p>
  <p time="98580" is_ac="false">But if you're not into history, there are 
also Ghost and Harry Potter Tours available.  </p>
  <p time="103560" is_ac="false">You can find links to all of these walking 
tour options in the description below.</p>
  <p time="127440" is_ac="false">Sitting on an extinct volcanic rock, Edinburgh 
Castle is the most iconic site in the old town  </p>
  <p time="133020" is_ac="false">and the entire city for that matter. With a rich 
history as a royal residence, military garrison,  </p>
  <p time="139380" is_ac="false">prison, and fortress, the castle is full of 
surprises and you can easily spend a full  </p>
  <p time="145440" is_ac="false">day here. Some of the highlights include the 
Great Hall, the Prisons of War Exhibition,  </p>
  <p time="151920" is_ac="false">the Crown Jewel, and the National War Museum. 
Entry to these museums are all included in the  </p>
  <p time="158580" is_ac="false">ticket price. And while the castle itself 
is not free, the view from the top is.  </p>
  <p time="164280" is_ac="false">If you like the view from the castle, just wait 
until we show you the view from Calton Hill.</p>
  <p time="169560" is_ac="false">Every day at 1pm here at the 
Castle they shoot the time gun,  </p>
  <p time="173160" is_ac="false">except for on Sundays. We actually just 
missed it, but it's definitely worth  </p>
  <p time="177540" is_ac="false">checking out. They've been doing this 
for hundreds of years because people,  </p>
  <p time="181020" is_ac="false">sailors and just people in the town, they 
used to set the clocks because of this sound.</p>
  <p time="192600" is_ac="false">Stretching one mile between Edinburgh Castle 
and the Palace of Holyrood House, the Royal  </p>
  <p time="197880" is_ac="false">Mile is the focal point of Edinburgh's Old Town. 
A walk down the Royal Mile will allow you to see  </p>
  <p time="203940" is_ac="false">plenty of traditional pubs, churches, and other 
historic buildings. Make sure to try the national  </p>
  <p time="209940" is_ac="false">dish of Scotland here, called "haggis", at one 
of the local pubs. It's the sheep's liver, heart,  </p>
  <p time="215940" is_ac="false">and lungs mixed with a few other ingredients. It 
tastes better than it sounds. Besides the pubs,  </p>
  <p time="221880" is_ac="false">you can also find many souvenir and whisky 
shops along the Royal Mile. But if you're  </p>
  <p time="227340" is_ac="false">looking for a unique Scotland souvenir, then you 
should check out the sponsor of today's video.</p>
  <p time="234000" is_ac="false">Established Titles sells souvenir 
plots of land, which then gives  </p>
  <p time="238080" is_ac="false">you the honorific title of Laird, Lord, or 
Lady, based on a historic Scottish custom.  </p>
  <p time="244320" is_ac="false">We got ours from Established Titles 
online, but we were able to drive to  </p>
  <p time="248760" is_ac="false">our actual piece of land in Eddleston 
which is a short drive from Edinburgh.  </p>
  <p time="253080" is_ac="false">Established Titles is a fun and novel way to 
preserve the natural woodlands of Scotland,  </p>
  <p time="257940" is_ac="false">while helping global reforestation efforts. The 
company plants a tree with every order around  </p>
  <p time="263760" is_ac="false">the world and works with global charities, such 
as One Tree Planted and Trees for the Future.</p>
  <p time="269820" is_ac="false">So we made it to my souvenir plot of land here 
at Eddleston. It's actually one square foot here  </p>
  <p time="274980" is_ac="false">on dedicated private land. My dad actually 
did a DNA test recently and it turns out one  </p>
  <p time="280620" is_ac="false">quarter of his DNA comes from Scotland, so this 
piece of land and this Title has a little bit of  </p>
  <p time="285900" is_ac="false">family meaning for me. I have to say that this 
really does make a nice, fun last-minute gift.  </p>
  <p time="290820" is_ac="false">Established Titles is the sponsor of today's video 
and they're actually offering a 10% discount for  </p>
  <p time="296700" is_ac="false">anyone who's watching this video for a limited 
time only. You can find more information about  </p>
  <p time="300960" is_ac="false">this as well as how to get your own plot of 
land in the link in the description below.</p>
  <p time="304860" is_ac="false">And as an added bonus, the first 200 
people to purchase a title pack using  </p>
  <p time="309780" is_ac="false">our link in the description will 
effectively be next to my plot.</p>
  <p time="313800" is_ac="false">Located in the middle of the Royal Mile, St. Giles 
Cathedral has been a working church for centuries.  </p>
  <p time="325020" is_ac="false">It has therefore a witness Scotland's turbulent 
religious history and played an important role in  </p>
  <p time="330780" is_ac="false">the Scottish Reformation. Today, you can admire 
the beautiful architecture and stained glass  </p>
  <p time="336600" is_ac="false">windows on the inside. It's free to visit and 
the perfect spot to hide out when it's raining.</p>
  <p time="354660" is_ac="false">Scotland  </p>
  <p time="359220" is_ac="false">is famous for its whisky and you'll find a 
number of bars and shops dedicated to this drink.  </p>
  <p time="366480" is_ac="false">If you don't have much knowledge of this 
sophisticated drink or its history, then you  </p>
  <p time="370680" is_ac="false">should join a tasting tour. During the session 
you'll be able to taste a variety of whiskys,  </p>
  <p time="376500" is_ac="false">from relatively delicate and subtle flavors of the 
Lowlands to the bold and robust tastes of Islay.  </p>
  <p time="383460" is_ac="false">You can find a link to a whisky tasting 
experience in the description below.</p>
  <p time="397740" is_ac="false">The best view of Edinburgh's Old Town is 
undoubtedly from Colton Hill. Only a short hike  </p>
  <p time="409140" is_ac="false">away from the Old and New Town, Carlton Hill is 
filled with interesting monuments. One of the most  </p>
  <p time="415320" is_ac="false">striking is the National Monument, inspired by the 
Parthenon in Athens. But what most visitors enjoy  </p>
  <p time="421980" is_ac="false">are the incredible views from the Dugald Stewart 
Monument. The best time to come here is during  </p>
  <p time="427740" is_ac="false">sunset, but keep in mind that it can get very busy 
on a clear day. If you want to find a viewpoint  </p>
  <p time="433620" is_ac="false">with more open space that's also free, you can 
check out Arthur Seat, which we'll cover shortly.</p>
  <p time="458820" is_ac="false">Next to the old town you can 
find the New Town of Edinburgh.  </p>
  <p time="462660" is_ac="false">This central part of the city was built between 
the 18th and 19th century and retains much of  </p>
  <p time="468240" is_ac="false">its original Neoclassical and Georgian period 
architecture. Today, the area is filled with  </p>
  <p time="474480" is_ac="false">designer shops, hip bars, and amazing restaurants. 
It's the place to go for shopping and dining.</p>
  <p time="497160" is_ac="false">Located alongside the busiest 
shopping street in the New Town,  </p>
  <p time="500220" is_ac="false">Princes Street Gardens is a beautiful green 
space in Edinburgh. The park is completely  </p>
  <p time="506100" is_ac="false">free to visit and offers some of the best 
views of the Old Town and Edinburgh Castle.  </p>
  <p time="511500" is_ac="false">You can also find one of the city's most 
notable monuments here, named Scott Monument.</p>
  <p time="540600" is_ac="false">Situated just a 10 minute walk 
from the end of Princes Street,  </p>
  <p time="546480" is_ac="false">you can find one of the most 
picturesque neighborhoods of Edinburgh.  </p>
  <p time="550860" is_ac="false">Dean Village was once home to 11 mills working 
and supporting Edinburgh until the 19th century.  </p>
  <p time="557880" is_ac="false">And while you can still see some remnants of 
the mills, Dean Village is now a tranquil oasis.  </p>
  <p time="563820" is_ac="false">It's a perfect place for enjoying a blend 
of nature with picturesque architecture.</p>
  <p time="582180" is_ac="false">So if you come and explore Dean Village,  </p>
  <p time="583860" is_ac="false">you should definitely check out the Water of 
Leith Walkway, because it's really peaceful.  </p>
  <p time="587460" is_ac="false">You can hear the water just flowing by you and 
it's a nice little break away from the city.</p>
  <p time="606060" is_ac="false">The ultimate break from urban 
life is a hike to Arthur's Seat,  </p>
  <p time="610200" is_ac="false">a dormant volcano and one of 
the highest points in Edinburgh.  </p>
  <p time="614400" is_ac="false">Located in Holyrood Park, there are different 
routes that take you to the summit. The most  </p>
  <p time="619560" is_ac="false">common trail starts near Holyrood Palace and 
takes about 30 to 60 minutes to reach the peak.  </p>
  <p time="625800" is_ac="false">From the top, you have 360-views of Edinburgh 
and the Port of Leith. Combine your visit with  </p>
  <p time="632520" is_ac="false">the Palace of Holyrood House if you're 
interested in Scottish Royal history.</p>
  <p time="653160" is_ac="false">There are a few other things to do in Edinburgh 
that we didn't mention and we've included a list  </p>
  <p time="659280" is_ac="false">of those on the screen here for you. If you're 
planning your Scotland trip, we recommend keeping  </p>
  <p time="664980" is_ac="false">things organized with our interactive travel 
planner. Find a discount code below. We also  </p>
  <p time="670740" is_ac="false">included important links that you'll need 
for your Edinburgh trip in the description,  </p>
  <p time="674340" is_ac="false">such as a full travel guide with where to stay, 
where to eat, and an interactive map so you  </p>
  <p time="680520" is_ac="false">can get to each spot that we mentioned. 
We'll catch you on the next adventure.</p>
</text>
